<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Anonymous on DDoSecrets Wiki</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/anonymous/</link><description>Recent content in Anonymous on DDoSecrets Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/anonymous/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accent Capital</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/accent_capital/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/accent_capital/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Accent Capital 365,000 emails from Accent Capital, a commercial real-estate investment firm. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 211 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
365,000 emails from Accent Capital, a commercial real-estate investment firm. In contrast with many other real-estate investment firms, Accent Capital owns or is directly involved with the management of many of the properties its clients invest in.</description></item><item><title>Achinsk City Government</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/achinsk_city_government/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/achinsk_city_government/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Achinsk City Government Over 7,000 emails from the Achinsk city government. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 8.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 7,000 emails from the Achinsk city government.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Acs Law Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/acs_law_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/acs_law_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
ACS Law emails Emails from the ACS lawfirm, hacked in retaliation to anti-piracy measures. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United Kingdom TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 365.3 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES The Register EDITOR NOTES
Emails from the ACS lawfirm, hacked in retaliation to anti-piracy measures.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=ACS_Law_emails&amp;amp;oldid=551&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Corporate Anonymous</description></item><item><title>Aerogas</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aerogas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aerogas/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Aerogas Approximately 100,000 emails from Aerogas, an engineering company which specializes in the oil and gas industry. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 145 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 100,000 emails from Aerogas, an engineering company which specializes in the oil and gas industry. Aerogas&amp;rsquo; clients include Rosneft, NOVATEK, Volgagaz, Purneft and others.</description></item><item><title>Aqaba Company For Ports Operation &amp; Management, Jordan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aqaba_company_for_ports_operation__management_jordan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aqaba_company_for_ports_operation__management_jordan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Aqaba Company for Ports Operation &amp;amp; Management, Jordan Over 50,000 emails from Jordan&amp;rsquo;s ports management company DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Jordan TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 27.8 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link
EDITOR NOTES
Over 50,000 emails from Jordan Aqaba Company for Ports Operation &amp;amp; Management, sent mostly between November 2019 and April 2022.
In 2004, the state-run Aqaba Development Corporation (ADC) acquired and took over the management and operation of the port on behalf of the Aqaba Special Economic Zone Authority (ASEZA).</description></item><item><title>Australia Queensland</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/australia_queensland/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/australia_queensland/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Australia Queensland Miscellaneous Australia materials hacked and released by Anonymous. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Australia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 82 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Miscellaneous Australia materials hacked and released by Anonymous.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Australia_Queensland&amp;amp;oldid=1133&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Australia Hack Anonymous</description></item><item><title>Blagoveshchensk City Administration</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/blagoveshchensk_city_administration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/blagoveshchensk_city_administration/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Blagoveshchensk City Administration / Благове́щенск 230,000 emails from the Blagoveshchensk City Administration / Благове́щенск from 2019 through 2022. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 150 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
230,000 emails from the Blagoveshchensk City Administration / Благове́щенск from 2019 through 2022.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Blueleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/blueleaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/blueleaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
BlueLeaks BLUELEAKS Situational awareness bulletins, training materials and fusion center reports for more than 200 law enforcement agencies. dated August 1996 to June 2020. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 269 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link IPFS QmdUQ2d2PGA5q1L4pDhd9fek1ejzowbZKTMCnAYR2EgViA MORE REFERENCES Small Wars and Insurgencies EDITOR NOTES Type brief description here BlueLeaks, sometimes referred to by the hashtag #BlueLeaks, is 269 gigabytes of internal U.</description></item><item><title>Capital Legal Services</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/capital_legal_services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/capital_legal_services/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Capital Legal Services Approximately 200,000 emails hacked from the Russian law firm Capital Legal Services, which practices law in a variety of areas. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 65 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 200,000 emails hacked from the Russian law firm Capital Legal Services, which practices law in a variety of areas.</description></item><item><title>Ceiec</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ceiec/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ceiec/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
CEIEC Described by the source as an alleged hack of China National Electronics Import &amp;amp; Export Corporation. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY China TYPE Hack SOURCE Popov FILE SIZE 1009.6 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES Emma Best EDITOR NOTES Igor Maksym Popov is a hacker, former FBI informant and a self-described contractor for Russia and Ukraine. Described by the source as an alleged hack of China National Electronics Import &amp;amp; Export Corporation.</description></item><item><title>Cellebrite Mobilogy</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cellebrite_mobilogy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cellebrite_mobilogy/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Cellebrite Mobilogy 3.6 TB of backend data from Cellebrite Mobilogy, previously Cellebrite&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Lifecycle Division. Mobilogy software can be used for device diagnostics, content transfer, backup and restorations. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 3.6 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
3.6 TB of backend data from Cellebrite Mobilogy, previously Cellebrite&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Lifecycle Division. Mobilogy software can be used for device diagnostics, content transfer, backup and restorations.</description></item><item><title>Cellebrite Team Foundation Server</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cellebrite_team_foundation_server/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cellebrite_team_foundation_server/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Cellebrite Team Foundation Server Backup files for Cellebrite&amp;rsquo;s Team Foundation Server, a collaboration environment that&amp;rsquo;s since been replaced by the Azure DevOps Server. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 430 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Backup files for Cellebrite&amp;rsquo;s Team Foundation Server, a collaboration environment that&amp;rsquo;s since been replaced by the Azure DevOps Server.
Limited Distribution Due to the potential for abuse, this data is only being made available to journalists and researchers at this time.</description></item><item><title>Central Bank Of Russia</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/central_bank_of_russia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/central_bank_of_russia/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Central Bank of Russia Thousands of files allegedly hacked from the Central Bank of Russia by Thblckrbbtworld, who claims affiliation with Anonymous. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 22.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of files allegedly hacked from the Central Bank of Russia by Thblckrbbtworld, who claims affiliation with Anonymous.</description></item><item><title>Chamber Of Mines (South Africa)</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chamber_of_mines_south_africa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chamber_of_mines_south_africa/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Chamber of Mines (South Africa))]
A small hack of files from the Chamber of Mines of South Africa, previously released by Anonymous and Par:AnoIA.
RELEASE
Chamber of Mines of South Africa A small hack of files from the Chamber of Mines of South Africa, previously released by Anonymous and Par:AnoIA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY South Africa TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 16.7 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Chamber Of Mines Of South Africa</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chamber_of_mines_of_south_africa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chamber_of_mines_of_south_africa/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
A small hack of files from the Chamber of Mines of South Africa, previously released by Anonymous and Par:AnoIA.
RELEASE
Chamber of Mines of South Africa A small hack of files from the Chamber of Mines of South Africa, previously released by Anonymous and Par:AnoIA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY South Africa TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 16.7 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Chinese Ministry Of Commerce</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chinese_ministry_of_commerce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chinese_ministry_of_commerce/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
Documents released through Par:AnoIA, allegedly containing details about deals with Russia, Ukraine and Belarus. The documents are partly in English, Russian and Chinese. One document, obtained from the Chinese foreign office in Minsk indicates relations between the notorious Russian mob boss Marat Balagula and high ranking Ukrainian politicians.
RELEASE
Chinese Ministry of Commerce Documents released through Par:AnoIA, allegedly containing details about deals with Russia, Ukraine and Belarus.</description></item><item><title>Chinga La Migra</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chinga_la_migra/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chinga_la_migra/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Chinga La Migra A series of hacks against Arizona and Texas law enforcement by Anonymous-affiliated group LulzSec/AntiSec. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE LulzSec/AntiSec FILE SIZE DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link MAGNET (II) Link MAGNET (III) Link MAGNET (IV) Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A series of hacks against Arizona and Texas law enforcement by Anonymous-affiliated group LulzSec/AntiSec.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Chinga_La_Migra&amp;amp;oldid=2137&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Continent Express</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/continent_express/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/continent_express/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Continent Express Nearly 400 GB of files and databases from Continent Express, a Russian travel agency. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE NB65 FILE SIZE 399 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 400 GB of files and databases from Continent Express, a Russian travel agency.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Corpmsp</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/corpmsp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/corpmsp/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | CorpMSP | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Over 480 GB and 75,000 files, | | | emails and disk images from | | | CorpMSP, a federal institution | | | providing support to small and | | | medium-sized businesses. The | | | controlling shareholder of | | | CorpMSP is the Russian | | | Federation.</description></item><item><title>Corruptbrazil</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/corruptbrazil/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/corruptbrazil/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
CorruptBrazil A cache of evidence revealing government coverup of a corruption investigation involving the CIA, the Brazilian telecom industry, and multiple US corporations. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 4.7 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Freezenet EDITOR NOTES
A cache of evidence revealing government coverup of a corruption investigation involving the CIA, the Brazilian telecom industry, and multiple US corporations.</description></item><item><title>Dept Of Education Of The Strezhevoy City District Administration</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dept_of_education_of_the_strezhevoy_city_district_administration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dept_of_education_of_the_strezhevoy_city_district_administration/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Dept of Education of the Strezhevoy City District Administration 250,000 emails from the Deptartment of Education of the Strezhevoy (Стрежево́й) City District Administration. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 221 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
250,000 emails from the Deptartment of Education of the Strezhevoy (Стрежево́й) City District Administration.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Ecm</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ecm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ecm/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from ECM)]
RELEASE
Elektrocentromontazh 1.23 million emails from Elektrocentromontazh (ECM) / Электроцентромонтаж, the chief power organization of Russia since 1940. ECM designs, builds, installs and maintains electrical equipment in power generation and transmission facilities in over 25 regions of Russia. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 1.7 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Elektrocentromontazh</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/elektrocentromontazh/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/elektrocentromontazh/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Elektrocentromontazh 1.23 million emails from Elektrocentromontazh (ECM) / Электроцентромонтаж, the chief power organization of Russia since 1940. ECM designs, builds, installs and maintains electrical equipment in power generation and transmission facilities in over 25 regions of Russia. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 1.7 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Embassy Of Ecuador, Moscow</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/embassy_of_ecuador_moscow/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/embassy_of_ecuador_moscow/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Embassy of Ecuador, Moscow Over 30,000 emails ranging from 2018 to March, 2022 and 40,000 files from the Embassy of Ecuador, Moscow. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 53.3 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES The Daily Dot EDITOR NOTES
Over 30,000 emails ranging from 2018 to March, 2022 and 40,000 files from the Embassy of Ecuador, Moscow.</description></item><item><title>Enerpred</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/enerpred/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/enerpred/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Enerpred 645,000 emails from Enerpred / Энерпред, the largest producer of hydraulic tools in Russia and the CIS, specializing in the energy, petrochemical, coal, gas and construction industries. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 432 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
645,000 emails from Enerpred / Энерпред, the largest producer of hydraulic tools in Russia and the CIS, specializing in the energy, petrochemical, coal, gas and construction industries.</description></item><item><title>Epik</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/epik/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/epik/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Epik User, registration, forwarding and other information behind the &amp;ldquo;privacy&amp;rdquo; web hosting and registrar service Epik, known for hosting fascist, white supremacist and other right-wing content as well as harassment and doxing websites. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 180 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Part 1, Part 2 TORRENT Part 1, Part 2, Part 3 DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Daily Dot, HuffPost, The Record EDITOR NOTES The files were initially released by the hackers independent of DDoSecrets and are presented as-is.</description></item><item><title>Equifax</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/equifax/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/equifax/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Equifax Hundreds of thousands of invoices from Equifax, courtesy of Anonymous Chile. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Chile TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 9 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Not to be confused with the 2017 Equifax breach. Hundreds of thousands of invoices from Equifax, courtesy of Anonymous Chile. Not to be confused with the 2017 breach.</description></item><item><title>Ethiopia Financial Intelligence Service</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ethiopia_financial_intelligence_service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ethiopia_financial_intelligence_service/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ethiopia Financial Intelligence Service Approximately 19,000 emails from Ethiopia&amp;rsquo;s Financial Intelligence Service DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Ethiopia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 45 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 19,000 emails from Ethiopia&amp;rsquo;s Financial Intelligence Service, previously known as the Financial Intelligence Center, the government agency responsible for monitoring suspicious financial transactions in the country.
Embargo During an initial embargo, the data was shared with the Platform to Protect Whistleblowers in Africa (PPLAAF), which shared its findings with various media partners: Bloomberg in the United States; Süddeutsche Zeitung in Germany; Tamedia in Switzerland; and The Continent in South Africa.</description></item><item><title>Forest</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/forest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/forest/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Forest 37,500 emails from Forest / Форест, a Russian logging and wood manufacturing firm and associated companies. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 35.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
37,500 emails from Forest / Форест, a Russian logging and wood manufacturing firm and associated companies.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Fuck Fbi Friday</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fuck_fbi_friday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fuck_fbi_friday/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fuck FBI Friday A series of hacks against United States law enforcement agencies and contractors by Anonymous-affiliated group Lulzsec/Antisec. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Lulzsec/Antisec FILE SIZE 5.28 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link MAGNET (III) Link MAGNET (IV) Link MAGNET (V) Link MAGNET (VI) Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A series of hacks against the Federal Bureau of Investigation, law enforcement agencies, and contractors by Anonymous-affiliated group Lulzsec/Antisec.</description></item><item><title>FundaçÃO Nacional De Artes</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/funda%C3%A7%C3%A3o_nacional_de_artes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/funda%C3%A7%C3%A3o_nacional_de_artes/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fundação Nacional de Artes Over 1 million emails from Fundação Nacional de Artes (Funarte), the Brazilian government&amp;rsquo;s National Arts Foundation. Funarte develops policies to promote the arts, including music, dance, theater and the circus. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 302 GB How to Request Access MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 1 million emails from Fundação Nacional de Artes (Funarte), the Brazilian government&amp;rsquo;s National Arts Foundation.</description></item><item><title>Gazprom Linde Engineering</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gazprom_linde_engineering/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gazprom_linde_engineering/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Gazprom Linde Engineering 768,000 emails from Gazprom Linde Engineering, which specializes in designing gas and petrochemical processing facilities and oil refineries. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 728 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
768,000 emails from Gazprom Linde Engineering, which specializes in designing gas and petrochemical processing facilities and oil refineries.</description></item><item><title>Gazregion</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gazregion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gazregion/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Gazregion Emails and files from Gazregion, a construction company specializing in gas pipelines and facilities. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous, NB65, Porteur FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES This release consists of three submissions from three sources about the same company. Emails, files and decryption keys from Gazregion, a construction company specializing in gas pipelines and facilities.</description></item><item><title>German Chambers Of Commerce</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/german_chambers_of_commerce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/german_chambers_of_commerce/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
DATASET NAME Documents allegedly acquired from the delegate of German economy in Ukraine, Alexander Marcus and his wife, a Russian citizen and FSB operative DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Germany TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 2.7 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
According to the source, the 2.7 Gigabyte of internal documents have been acquired through their offices in Ukraine and Azerbaijan, from the delegate of German economy in Ukraine, Alexander Marcus and his wife, a Russian citizen and FSB operative.</description></item><item><title>Gqleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gqleaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gqleaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GQLeaks 120 GB of emails hacked from the Centro Nacional de la Informatización de la Administración Pública de Guinea Ecuatorial (CNIAPGE) or Equatorial Guinea&amp;rsquo;s National Center for the Computerization of Public Administration. The emails are dated between 2017 and early 2022. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Equatorial Guinea TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 120 GB DOWNLOADS (How to request access) MORE REFERENCES Diario Rombe EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Guov I Gs General Dept. Of Troops And Civil Construction</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/guov_i_gs_-_general_dept._of_troops_and_civil_construction/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/guov_i_gs_-_general_dept._of_troops_and_civil_construction/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GUOV i GS - General Dept. of Troops and Civil Construction 15,600 emails from GUOV I GS - the General Dept. of Troops and Civil Construction, a construction company that works on projects in the interests of the Russian Ministry of Defense. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Porteur FILE SIZE 9.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Hbgary</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hbgary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hbgary/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
HBGary Over 70,000 emails from key people at the private intelligence firm HBGary. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 7 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES KrebsOnSecurity EDITOR NOTES
Over 70,000 emails from key people at the private intelligence firm HBGary. The emails show, among other things, plots to discredit their enemies.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=HBGary&amp;amp;oldid=2170&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Anonymous Corporate Hack</description></item><item><title>Integrity Initiative</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/integrity_initiative/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/integrity_initiative/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Integrity Initiative Integrity Initiative is a non-profit that counters Russian propaganda. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United Kingdom TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE (Parts 1-6) 91.5 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET (Parts 1-6) Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Integrity Initiative EDITOR NOTES
Integrity Initiative was a non-profit that counters Russian propaganda. It appeared to have confirmed the hack, but has not reviewed the individual documents.</description></item><item><title>Italian State Police</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/italian_state_police/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/italian_state_police/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Italian State Police 1.35 Gigabyte of hacked from the Italian State Police, including details about wiretaps. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Italy TYPE Hack SOURCE Unknown FILE SIZE 1.1 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
1.35 Gigabyte of hacked from the Italian State Police, including details about wiretaps from Telcom Italia and confidential technical information about interception devices. The materials were ostensibly hacked by Anonymous.</description></item><item><title>Jhonlin Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jhonlin_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jhonlin_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Jhonlin Group Over 600,000 hacked emails from the Jhonlin Group, a mining and palm oil plantation conglomerate. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Indonesia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 513 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [Link] TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 600,000 hacked emails from the Jhonlin Group, a mining and palm oil plantation conglomerate.
The conglomerate is known for using police to intimidate journalists and activists.</description></item><item><title>Llc Capital</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/llc_capital/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/llc_capital/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
LLC Capital 31,990 emails from LLC Capital / ООО Капитал, a specialized accounting firm which works with SAFMAR Group and its assets, including PJSC RussNeft. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 20.4 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
31,990 emails from LLC Capital / ООО Капитал, a specialized accounting firm which works with Mikhail Gutseriev&amp;rsquo;s SAFMAR Group and its assets, including PJSC RussNeft.</description></item><item><title>Marathon Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/marathon_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/marathon_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Marathon Group 62,000 emails from the Marathon Group, an investment firm owned by Alexander Vinokurov, who is under EU sanctions for &amp;ldquo;providing a substantial source of revenue to the Government of Russia.&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 51.9 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
62,000 emails from the Marathon Group, an investment firm owned by Alexander Vinokurov, who is under EU sanctions for &amp;ldquo;providing a substantial source of revenue to the Government of Russia.</description></item><item><title>Mashoil</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mashoil/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mashoil/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MashOil Nearly 140,000 emails from MashOil, which designs, manufactures and maintains equipment used in the drilling, mining and fracking industries. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 110 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 140,000 emails from MashOil, which designs, manufactures and maintains equipment used in the drilling, mining and fracking industries.</description></item><item><title>Mclanahan Russia</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mclanahan_russia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mclanahan_russia/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
McLanahan Russia 311,122 emails from McLanahan Russia, a mining equipment and services company with its origin and corporate headquarters in Hollidaysburg, Pennsylvania. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia, United States of America TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 302 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
311,122 emails from McLanahan Russia, a mining equipment and services company with its origin and corporate headquarters in Hollidaysburg, Pennsylvania.</description></item><item><title>Metprom Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/metprom_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/metprom_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Metprom Group Emails from a metallurgic engineering and investment group involved in dozens of projects with ArcelorMittal, PAO NLMK, EVRAZ group enterprises, PAO Mechel plants, PAO Severstal, Isfahan metallurgical plant, Helwan metallurgical plant and others. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE B00da, Porteur, Wh1t3 Sh4d0w FILE SIZE 184 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Part One, Part Two TORRENT Part One, Part Two DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Ministerio De Justicia Of Chile</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministerio_de_justicia_of_chile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministerio_de_justicia_of_chile/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ministerio de Justicia of Chile Over 384,000 emails from the Ministerio de Justicia (Ministry of Justice) of Chile. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Chile TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 67 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES Ciper EDITOR NOTES
Over 384,000 emails from the Ministerio de Justicia (Ministry of Justice) of Chile.
Limited Distribution Due to the sensitivity of the data, the data is only being provided to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Ministry Of Communications And It Of Azerbaijan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministry_of_communications_and_it_of_azerbaijan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministry_of_communications_and_it_of_azerbaijan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ministry of Communications and IT of Azerbaijan The documents contain a variety of information showing interesting ties between various corporations, government agencies and officials. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Azerbaijan TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 1.4 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
The documents contain a variety of information showing interesting ties between various corporations, government agencies and officials.</description></item><item><title>Ministry Of Culture Of The Russian Federation</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministry_of_culture_of_the_russian_federation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministry_of_culture_of_the_russian_federation/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ministry of Culture of the Russian Federation / Минкультуры России 230,000 emails from the Ministry of Culture of the Russian Federation / Министерство культуры Российской Федерации, which is responsible for state policy regarding art, cinematography, archives, copyright, cultural heritage, and censorship. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 446 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Ministry Of Foreign Affairs Of Cambodia</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministry_of_foreign_affairs_of_cambodia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministry_of_foreign_affairs_of_cambodia/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ministry of Foreign Affairs of Cambodia Hacked materials from the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of Cambodia. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Cambodia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 382.6 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Hacked materials from the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of Cambodia. Documents are in English, Hindi, Khmer and Russian.
Disclaimer The dataset was originally published on Par:AnoIA, and journalists have found files that do not appear to have be from the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of Cambodia.</description></item><item><title>Mosekspertiza</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mosekspertiza/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mosekspertiza/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Mosekspertiza Over 150,000 emails, 8,200 files and several hundred gigabytes of databases from Mosekspertiza, a state-owned company created by the Moscow Chamber of Commerce to provide expert services and consultations to Russian businesses. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE NB65 FILE SIZE 483.3 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Email, File, Database TORRENT Email, File, Database DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Neocom Geoservice</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/neocom_geoservice/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/neocom_geoservice/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Neocom Geoservice 87,500 emails from Neocom Geoservice, an engineering firm specializing in exploring oil and gas fields and providing drilling support. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 107 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
87,500 emails from Neocom Geoservice, an engineering firm specializing in exploring oil and gas fields and providing drilling support.</description></item><item><title>Npo Vs</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/npo_vs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/npo_vs/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
NPO VS Over one million emails from NPO VS / НПО ВС, a Russian IT company that specializes in data automation and security, including the processing and protection of state secrets. NPO VS&amp;rsquo; clients include the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs and the Ministry of Defence. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 759 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Odebrecht</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odebrecht/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odebrecht/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Odrebrecht 390,000 application (non-employee) emails ranging from 2008 to 2022 and 365 fserver emails ranging from April 2021 to early May 2022 from Novonor, previously Odebrecht S.A. The fserver emails contain details of SWIFT transfers, including payments to their employees and lawyers in the United States. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil, Dominican Republic, United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 12.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Office Of Industrial Economics, Thailand</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/office_of_industrial_economics_thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/office_of_industrial_economics_thailand/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Office of Industrial Economics, Thailand 831,722 emails from Thailand&amp;rsquo;s Office of Industrial, a department of the Ministry of Industry responsible for guidance on industry growth, economics and IT systems. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Thailand TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 197 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
831,722 emails from Thailand&amp;rsquo;s Office of Industrial, a department of the Ministry of Industry responsible for guidance on industry growth, economics and IT systems.</description></item><item><title>Pacoleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pacoleaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pacoleaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
PacoLeaks Thousands of hacked files taken from the Carabineros de Chile (Chilean national police). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Chile TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 8.8 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Chile Today EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of hacked files taken from the Carabineros de Chile (Chilean national police), including information on officials, the weapons that some units have, as well as &amp;ldquo;targets of interest&amp;rdquo; for police intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Petrofort</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/petrofort/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/petrofort/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Petrofort Approximately 300,000 emails from Petrofort, one of the largest office spaces and business centers in Saint Petersburg. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 244 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 300,000 emails from Petrofort, one of the largest office spaces and business centers in Saint Petersburg.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Polar Branch Of The Russian Federal Research Institute Of Fisheries And Oceanography</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/polar_branch_of_the_russian_federal_research_institute_of_fisheries_and_oceanography/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/polar_branch_of_the_russian_federal_research_institute_of_fisheries_and_oceanography/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Polar Branch of the Russian Federal Research Institute of Fisheries and Oceanography 466 GB of emails from the Polar Branch of the Russian Federal Research Institute of Fisheries and Oceanography, whose studies determine the total allowable catch of different forms of commercial sea life. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE B00da, Porteur FILE SIZE 466 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Part One, Part Two, Part Three, Part Four TORRENT Part One, Part Two, Part Three, Part Four DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Port And Railway Projects Service Of Jsc Ummc</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/port_and_railway_projects_service_of_jsc_ummc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/port_and_railway_projects_service_of_jsc_ummc/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Port and Railway Projects Service of JSC UMMC 77,500 emails from Port and Railway Projects Service of JSC UMMC / Служба по портовым и железнодорожным проектам (ОАО УГМК), which operates the two largest ports in Russia specializing in coal shipments. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 106 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Prime Minister Of Iraq'S Office</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/prime_minister_of_iraqs_office/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/prime_minister_of_iraqs_office/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Prime Minister of Iraq&amp;rsquo;s office 2,500 emails from the Prime Minister of Iraq&amp;rsquo;s office DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Iraq TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 1.2 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link
EDITOR NOTES
2,500 emails from the Prime Minister of Iraq&amp;rsquo;s office sent between March 2021 and April 2022. The emails document the daily business of the office while Mustafa Al-Kadhimi (مصطفى عبد اللطيف مشتت) held it.</description></item><item><title>Private Office Of Sheikh Hazza Bin Zayed Al Nahyan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/private_office_of_sheikh_hazza_bin_zayed_al_nahyan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/private_office_of_sheikh_hazza_bin_zayed_al_nahyan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Private Office of Sheikh Hazza bin Zayed Al Nahyan 153,584 emails from the Private Office of Sheikh Hazza bin Zayed Al Nahyan, the former National Security Advisor of the United Arab Emirates (UAE) and the brother of the UAE&amp;rsquo;s newly appointed President. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United Arab Emirates TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 280.9 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Pscb</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pscb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pscb/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
PSCB 229,000 emails and 630,000 files from the Petersburg Social Commercial Bank / Петербургский социальный коммерческий банк, one of the top 100 Russian banks in terms of net assets. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE NB65 FILE SIZE 542 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
229,000 emails and 630,000 files from the Petersburg Social Commercial Bank / Петербургский социальный коммерческий банк, one of the top 100 Russian banks in terms of net assets.</description></item><item><title>Pt Rea Kaltim Plantations And Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pt_rea_kaltim_plantations_and_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pt_rea_kaltim_plantations_and_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
PT Rea Kaltim Plantations and Group 314,055 hacked emails from PT Rea Kaltim Plantations and Group, which has been the subject of a number of protests, conflicts and allegations of human rights violations. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Indonesia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 277 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Enlace Hacktivista simultaneously published the data 314,055 hacked emails from PT Rea Kaltim Plantations and Group, a palm oil company in Indonesia which has been the subject of a number of protests, conflicts and allegations of human rights violations.</description></item><item><title>Public Chamber Of The Krasnoyarsk</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/public_chamber_of_the_krasnoyarsk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/public_chamber_of_the_krasnoyarsk/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Public Chamber of the Krasnoyarsk 69,000 emails from the Public Chamber of the Krasnoyarsk, the largest city in Krasnoyarsk Krai, Russia. Krasnoyarsk is an important junction of the Trans-Siberian Railway, and is one of the largest producers of aluminium in the country. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Porteur, B00da FILE SIZE 41.1 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [Link] TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Rosatom</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/rosatom/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/rosatom/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Rosatom / Росатом 15 gigabytes of files allegedly hacked from the Rosatom State Nuclear Energy Corporation, including information on Techsnabexport / Техснабэкспорт, commonly known as TENEX. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 15.3 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
15 gigabytes of files allegedly hacked from the Rosatom State Nuclear Energy Corporation, including information on Techsnabexport / Техснабэкспорт, commonly known as TENEX, which exports uranium and provides uranium enrichment services for foreign reactors.</description></item><item><title>Roskomnadzor</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/roskomnadzor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/roskomnadzor/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Roskomnadzor / Роскомнадзор | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Over 360,000 files from | | | Roskomnadzor, the Russian agency | | | responsible for monitoring, | | | controlling and censoring Russian | | | mass media. | | | | | | | | | Более 360,000 файлов | | | Роскомнадзора, Российского | | | агентства, отвечающего за | | | наблюдение, контроль и цензуру | | | СМИ России.</description></item><item><title>Rosoboronexport</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/rosoboronexport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/rosoboronexport/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE Image Here ROSOBORONEXPORT Described by the source as dealing with &amp;ldquo;ROSOBORONEXPORT sales to India.&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Popov FILE SIZE 1.1 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES Emma Best EDITOR NOTES Igor Maksym Popov is a hacker, former FBI informant and a self-described contractor for Russia and Ukraine. Described by the source as dealing with &amp;ldquo;ROSOBORONEXPORT sales to India.</description></item><item><title>Rostproekt</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/rostproekt/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/rostproekt/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
RostProekt 2.4 gigabytes of emails allegedly hacked from the Russian construction company RostProekt / РостПроект. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 2.4 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
2.4 gigabytes of emails allegedly hacked from the Russian construction company RostProekt / РостПроект.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Salvini Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/salvini_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/salvini_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Salvini emails Thousands of emails from Italy&amp;rsquo;s fascist Deputy Prime Minister, Matteo Salvini and the Noi con Salvini political party. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Italy TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 5 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Motherboard, CyberGuerilla EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of emails from Italy&amp;rsquo;s fascist Deputy Prime Minister, Matteo Salvini and the Noi con Salvini political party.</description></item><item><title>Sawatzky</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sawatzky/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sawatzky/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Sawatzky 575,000 emails from a property management company. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 432 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
575,000 emails from a property management company.
Sawatzky&amp;rsquo;s clients include Du Pont, Lenovo, Whirlpool, Aveva, Wella, Johnson + Johnson, Cisco, Google, Swatch, Avito, Samsung, Microsoft, Western Union, Saint-gobain, Turkish Airlines, and British American Tobacco.</description></item><item><title>Shooting Sheriffs Saturday</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/shooting_sheriffs_saturday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/shooting_sheriffs_saturday/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Shooting Sheriffs Saturday An AntiSec hack of sheriffs&amp;rsquo; offices. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE AntiSec FILE SIZE 7.4 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES PasteBin EDITOR NOTES
An AntiSec hack of sheriffs&amp;rsquo; offices.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Shooting_Sheriffs_Saturday&amp;amp;oldid=2237&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Anonymous Hack United States of America</description></item><item><title>Socar Energoresource</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/socar_energoresource/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/socar_energoresource/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
SOCAR Energoresource 116,500 emails SOCAR Energoresource / ООО Сокар энергоресурс, which operates the Antipinsky Refinery and several oilfields. SOCAR Energoresource works directly with Gazprom, Rosneft and Lukoil and is partially owned by the State Oil Company of Azerbaijan Republic (SOCAR). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 130 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Special State Protection Service Of Azerbaijan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/special_state_protection_service_of_azerbaijan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/special_state_protection_service_of_azerbaijan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Special State Protection Service of Azerbaijan Passport scans, reports, confidential shareholder documents, account statements, letters of credit, and details of oil drilling technologies. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Azerbaijan TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 1 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Files hacked by Anonymous and originally posted to the now-defunct Par:AnoIA leak platform. The cache contains passport scans, reports, confidential shareholder documents, account statements, letters of credit, and details of oil drilling technologies.</description></item><item><title>Special:Categories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialcategories/</guid><description>Help
The following categories exist on the wiki, and may or may not be unused. Also see wanted categories.
[Categories]
[Display categories starting at:]
[Show]
(first | last) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Allegations of State Sponsorship‏‎ (22 members) Angola‏‎ (1 member) Anonymous‏‎ (86 members) Argentina‏‎ (4 members) Australia‏‎ (4 members) Azerbaijan‏‎ (2 members) Bahamas‏‎ (0 members) Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box‏‎ (25 members) Belarus‏‎ (2 members) Belgium‏‎ (1 member) Bolivia‏‎ (1 member) Brazil‏‎ (11 members) Bulgaria‏‎ (1 member) Cambodia‏‎ (1 member) Canada‏‎ (4 members) Cayman Islands‏‎ (1 member) Chile‏‎ (6 members) China‏‎ (2 members) Colombia‏‎ (6 members) Cook Islands‏‎ (1 member) Corporate‏‎ (136 members) Cyberwar‏‎ (54 members) Cyprus‏‎ (1 member) Dominican Republic‏‎ (1 member) Ecuador‏‎ (3 members) El Salvador‏‎ (3 members) Environmental‏‎ (41 members) Estonia‏‎ (1 member) Ethiopia‏‎ (1 member) European Union‏‎ (2 members) Extractivist Leaks‏‎ (7 members) Fascist‏‎ (23 members) France‏‎ (3 members) Fuerzas Represivas‏‎ (7 members) Germany‏‎ (5 members) Guatemala‏‎ (2 members) Guinea Ecuatorial‏‎ (1 member) Hack‏‎ (216 members) Iceland‏‎ (1 member) India‏‎ (1 member) Indonesia‏‎ (4 members) Iran‏‎ (4 members) Iraq‏‎ (1 member) Italy‏‎ (6 members) Jordan‏‎ (1 member) Leak‏‎ (24 members) Leak Markets‏‎ (3 members) Limited Distribution‏‎ (84 members) Mexico‏‎ (1 member) MilicoLeaks‏‎ (2 members) (first | last) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Special:Mostlinkedcategories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialmostlinkedcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialmostlinkedcategories/</guid><description>Showing below up to 50 results in range #1 to #50.
View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Hack‏‎ (216 members) Corporate‏‎ (136 members) Anonymous‏‎ (86 members) Limited Distribution‏‎ (84 members) United States of America‏‎ (72 members) Russia‏‎ (65 members) Cyberwar‏‎ (54 members) Ransomware‏‎ (53 members) Environmental‏‎ (41 members) Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box‏‎ (25 members) Leak‏‎ (24 members) Organization‏‎ (24 members) Fascist‏‎ (23 members) Allegations of State Sponsorship‏‎ (22 members) Brazil‏‎ (11 members) Researchers‏‎ (10 members) Ukraine‏‎ (8 members) Extractivist Leaks‏‎ (7 members) Fuerzas Represivas‏‎ (7 members) Italy‏‎ (6 members) Chile‏‎ (6 members) Scrape‏‎ (6 members) Colombia‏‎ (6 members) Germany‏‎ (5 members) Australia‏‎ (4 members) Iran‏‎ (4 members) Argentina‏‎ (4 members) United Kingdom‏‎ (4 members) Myanmar‏‎ (4 members) Indonesia‏‎ (4 members) Canada‏‎ (4 members) Thailand‏‎ (3 members) Syria‏‎ (3 members) Turkey‏‎ (3 members) France‏‎ (3 members) Paraguay‏‎ (3 members) Peru‏‎ (3 members) Leak Markets‏‎ (3 members) El Salvador‏‎ (3 members) Ecuador‏‎ (3 members) China‏‎ (2 members) European Union‏‎ (2 members) Azerbaijan‏‎ (2 members) Panama‏‎ (2 members) Venezuela‏‎ (2 members) Belarus‏‎ (2 members) Guatemala‏‎ (2 members) MilicoLeaks‏‎ (2 members) Angola‏‎ (1 member) Bulgaria‏‎ (1 member) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Special:Uncategorizedcategories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialuncategorizedcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialuncategorizedcategories/</guid><description>Help
Showing below up to 50 results in range #1 to #50.
View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Allegations of State Sponsorship Angola Anonymous Argentina Australia Azerbaijan Bahamas Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box Belarus Belgium Bolivia Brazil Bulgaria Cambodia Canada Cayman Islands Chile China Colombia Cook Islands Corporate Cyberwar Cyprus Dominican Republic Ecuador El Salvador Environmental Estonia Ethiopia European Union Extractivist Leaks Fascist France Fuerzas Represivas Germany Guatemala Guinea Ecuatorial Hack Iceland India Indonesia Iran Iraq Italy Jordan Leak Leak Markets Limited Distribution Mexico MilicoLeaks View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Stratfor Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/stratfor_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/stratfor_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Stratfor emails 5 million emails hacked from Stratfor by Anonymous and provided to WikiLeaks. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 23.6 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Archive produced by WikiLeaks and presented as-is. 5 million emails hacked from Stratfor by Anonymous and provided to WikiLeaks.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Stratfor_emails&amp;amp;oldid=2243&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Allegations of State Sponsorship Anonymous Hack Organization</description></item><item><title>Synesis Surveillance System</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/synesis_surveillance_system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/synesis_surveillance_system/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Synesis Surveillance System 1.2 GB of videos and data on the Synesis and Kipod surveillance system and software deployed in Belarus in elsewhere. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Belarus TYPE Scrape SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 1.2 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Although this data is included in the Cyberwar category due to its categorical application, it appears unrelated.</description></item><item><title>Syria Files</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/syria_files/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/syria_files/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Syria files A partial set of Syrian emails hacked by LulzSec, consisting only of the emails in the archive released by WikiLeaks. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Syria TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 6.5 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Daily Dot, Emma.Best EDITOR NOTES The archive contains only a portion of the Syria emails released on WikiLeaks&amp;rsquo; website, which itself is missing over 1,000,000 emails provided to WikiLeaks by Anonymous.</description></item><item><title>Syrian Ministry Of Foreign Affairs</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/syrian_ministry_of_foreign_affairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/syrian_ministry_of_foreign_affairs/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Syrian Ministry of Foreign Affairs Internal government emails from the Syrian Ministry of Foreign Affair, including details about cargo flights from Russia, each containing 30 tons of Syrian cash. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Syria TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 685 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hacker News EDITOR NOTES
Internal government emails from the Syrian Ministry of Foreign Affair, including details about cargo flights from Russia, each containing 30 tons of Syrian cash.</description></item><item><title>Technotec</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/technotec/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/technotec/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Technotec 495,000 emails from the Russian firm Technotec, which provides oil and gas field services to companies including Rosneft and Gazprom Neft. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 440 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
495,000 emails from the Russian firm Technotec, which has provided oil and gas field services along with chemical reagents used in oil production and transportation to companies including Rosneft and Gazprom Neft since 1995.</description></item><item><title>Tendertech</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tendertech/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tendertech/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Tendertech 426,000 emails from Tendertech / Тендертех, a firm specializing in processing financial and banking documents on behalf of businesses and entrepreneurs. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 160 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
426,000 emails from Tendertech / Тендертех, a firm specializing in processing financial and banking documents on behalf of businesses and entrepreneurs.</description></item><item><title>Tetraedr</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tetraedr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tetraedr/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Tetraedr | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | .thumbinner style=&amp;ldquo;width:302px;&amp;rdquo;} | | | [![Anonymous Liberland and the | | | Pwn-Bär Hack Team Pom-Bear Mascot | | | About us Greetings citizens of | | | the world. Let us introduce | | | ourselves&amp;hellip; We are the Pwn-Bär | | | international hack team. We stand | | | for equal opportunity pwnage and | | | unrestricted access to | | | information.</description></item><item><title>Thozis Corp</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thozis_corp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thozis_corp/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Thozis Corp. 5,500 emails from Thozis Corp., a Russian investment firm owned by Zakhar Smushkin, which is involved in the project to build a satellite city in Saint Petersburg. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 5.9 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
5,500 emails from Thozis Corp., a Russian investment firm owned by Zakhar Smushkin (number 2,674 on Forbes&amp;rsquo; billionaire list), which is involved in the project to build the Yuzhny satellite city in Saint Petersburg.</description></item><item><title>Transneft</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/transneft/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/transneft/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Transneft / Транснефть 79,000 emails from the OMEGA Company, the R&amp;amp;D department of Russia&amp;rsquo;s state-controlled pipeline company, Transneft. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 79 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES American Sanctions EDITOR NOTES Dedicated by the source to Hillary Clinton 79,000 emails from the OMEGA Company, the R&amp;amp;D department of Russia&amp;rsquo;s state-controlled pipeline company, Transneft / Транснефть.</description></item><item><title>Truth Will Out Films Customer Database</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/truth_will_out_films_customer_database/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/truth_will_out_films_customer_database/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Truth Will Out Films Customer Database A 2019 database containing full customer information for the neo-Nazi film shop, Truth Will Out Films. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 89 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A 2019 database containing full customer information for the neo-Nazi film shop, Truth Will Out Films.
Due to the PII in the dataset, it is only being offered to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Turkish Takedown Thursday</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/turkish_takedown_thursday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/turkish_takedown_thursday/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Turkish Takedown Thursday The hack and defacement of 74 Turkish sites by AntiSec. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Turkey TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 21.8 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES The Hacker News EDITOR NOTES
The hack and defacement of 74 Turkish sites by AntiSec.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Turkish_Takedown_Thursday&amp;amp;oldid=1750&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Turkey Anonymous</description></item><item><title>Ukraine General Prosecutor Offices</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ukraine_general_prosecutor_offices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ukraine_general_prosecutor_offices/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ukraine General Prosecutor offices Described by the source as an alleged hack of the Ukraine General Prosecutor offices. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Ukraine TYPE Hack SOURCE Popov FILE SIZE 5.3 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES Emma Best EDITOR NOTES Igor Maksym Popov is a hacker, former FBI informant and a self-described contractor for Russia and Ukraine. Described by the source as an alleged hack of the Ukraine General Prosecutor offices.</description></item><item><title>Vgtrk</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/vgtrk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/vgtrk/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
VGTRK Over 20 years and 900,000 emails from VGTRK / ВГТРК (All-Russia State Television and Radio Broadcasting Company / Всероссийская государственная телевизионная и радиовещательная компания), a Russian state-owned broadcaster which operates five national TV stations, two international networks, five radio stations, and over 80 regional TV and radio networks. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE NB65 FILE SIZE 786.2 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Mail, Files TORRENT Mail, Files DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Vyberi Radio</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/vyberi_radio/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/vyberi_radio/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Vyberi Radio 1.5 million emails from the Vyberi Radio / Выбери Радио group, which operates around 100 radio stations in 18 cities throughout Russia, with over 8 million listeners. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 823 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
1.5 million emails from the Vyberi Radio / Выбери Радио group of companies, which operates around 100 radio stations in 18 cities throughout Russia, with over 8 million listeners.</description></item><item><title>Worldwide Invest</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/worldwide_invest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/worldwide_invest/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Worldwide Invest Nearly 250,000 emails from Worldwide Invest / ВОРЛДВАЙД ИНВЕСТ АС, an investment firms with ties to Estonia and Russian railways. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 130 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 250,000 emails from Worldwide Invest / ВОРЛДВАЙД ИНВЕСТ АС, an investment firms with ties to Estonia and Russian railways.</description></item><item><title>Роскомнадзор</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BC%D0%BD%D0%B0%D0%B4%D0%B7%D0%BE%D1%80/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BC%D0%BD%D0%B0%D0%B4%D0%B7%D0%BE%D1%80/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Роскомнадзор)]
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Roskomnadzor / Роскомнадзор | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Over 360,000 files from | | | Roskomnadzor, the Russian agency | | | responsible for monitoring, | | | controlling and censoring Russian | | | mass media. | | | | | | | | | Более 360,000 файлов | | | Роскомнадзора, Российского | | | агентства, отвечающего за | | | наблюдение, контроль и цензуру | | | СМИ России.</description></item></channel></rss>