<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Banker's
Box on DDoSecrets Wiki</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/bankers-box/</link><description>Recent content in Banker's
Box on DDoSecrets Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/bankers-box/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>29 Leaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/29_leaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/29_leaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.
RELEASE
#29 Leaks Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes and other documents from UK-based Formations House (&amp;ldquo;The London Office&amp;rdquo;) and related companies. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Multiple TYPE Various SOURCE FILE SIZE 400 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES OCCRP EDITOR NOTES Pronounced &amp;ldquo;Number 29 Leaks&amp;rdquo; Contents [1] [Background] [2] [Timeline] [3] [Findings] [4] [References] [5] [Research] Background Formations House, now The London Office, facilitates international money laundering by taking advantage of the lax regulatory framework of the United Kingdom and many of its former colonies.</description></item><item><title>Accent Capital</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/accent_capital/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/accent_capital/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Accent Capital 365,000 emails from Accent Capital, a commercial real-estate investment firm. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 211 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
365,000 emails from Accent Capital, a commercial real-estate investment firm. In contrast with many other real-estate investment firms, Accent Capital owns or is directly involved with the management of many of the properties its clients invest in.</description></item><item><title>Banco De PoupançA E CréDito</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/banco_de_poupan%C3%A7a_e_cr%C3%A9dito/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/banco_de_poupan%C3%A7a_e_cr%C3%A9dito/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Banco de Poupança e Crédito Several megabytes from Banco de Poupança e Crédito, a government-owned, full service bank in Angola. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Angola TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBit FILE SIZE 17 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Several megabytes from Banco de Poupança e Crédito, a government-owned, full service bank in Angola. The data was first released by LockBit under the bank&amp;rsquo;s old name, Banco Comercial de Angola.</description></item><item><title>Cayman National Bank And Trust</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cayman_national_bank_and_trust/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cayman_national_bank_and_trust/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Cayman National Bank and Trust)]
RELEASE
Sherwood Copies of the servers of the Cayman National Bank and Trust (Isle of Man). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Cayman Islands TYPE Hack SOURCE Phineas Fisher FILE SIZE 2.26 TB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Unicorn Riot EDITOR NOTES
Copies of the servers of the Cayman National Bank and Trust (Isle of Man) via the hacktivist sometimes known as Phineas Fisher.</description></item><item><title>Central Bank Of Russia</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/central_bank_of_russia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/central_bank_of_russia/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Central Bank of Russia Thousands of files allegedly hacked from the Central Bank of Russia by Thblckrbbtworld, who claims affiliation with Anonymous. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 22.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of files allegedly hacked from the Central Bank of Russia by Thblckrbbtworld, who claims affiliation with Anonymous.</description></item><item><title>Ernst &amp; Young</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ernst__young/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ernst__young/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ernst &amp;amp; Young Internal files from the accounting firm Ernst &amp;amp; Young (EY). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 2 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Two terabytes of internal files from the accounting firm Ernst &amp;amp; Young (EY). Ernst &amp;amp; Young primarily provides accounting, tax, consulting and advisory services.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Ethiopia Financial Intelligence Service</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ethiopia_financial_intelligence_service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ethiopia_financial_intelligence_service/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ethiopia Financial Intelligence Service Approximately 19,000 emails from Ethiopia&amp;rsquo;s Financial Intelligence Service DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Ethiopia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 45 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 19,000 emails from Ethiopia&amp;rsquo;s Financial Intelligence Service, previously known as the Financial Intelligence Center, the government agency responsible for monitoring suspicious financial transactions in the country.
Embargo During an initial embargo, the data was shared with the Platform to Protect Whistleblowers in Africa (PPLAAF), which shared its findings with various media partners: Bloomberg in the United States; Süddeutsche Zeitung in Germany; Tamedia in Switzerland; and The Continent in South Africa.</description></item><item><title>Innwa Bank</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/innwa_bank/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/innwa_bank/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Innwa Bank
Nearly 20,000 files from Innwa Bank, which is owned by the Myanmar Economic Corporation (MEC) and is used to pay salaries and transfer funds for military officers and units, and military controlled businesses.
DATASET DETAILS
COUNTRIES Myanmar
TYPE Hack
SOURCE Sugondese Electronic Army
FILE SIZE 49 MB
DOWNLOADS (How to Download)
MAGNET [[[[Link]]]]
TORRENT Link
MORE
REFERENCES
Justice For Myanmar
EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Llc Capital</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/llc_capital/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/llc_capital/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
LLC Capital 31,990 emails from LLC Capital / ООО Капитал, a specialized accounting firm which works with SAFMAR Group and its assets, including PJSC RussNeft. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 20.4 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
31,990 emails from LLC Capital / ООО Капитал, a specialized accounting firm which works with Mikhail Gutseriev&amp;rsquo;s SAFMAR Group and its assets, including PJSC RussNeft.</description></item><item><title>Marathon Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/marathon_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/marathon_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Marathon Group 62,000 emails from the Marathon Group, an investment firm owned by Alexander Vinokurov, who is under EU sanctions for &amp;ldquo;providing a substantial source of revenue to the Government of Russia.&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 51.9 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
62,000 emails from the Marathon Group, an investment firm owned by Alexander Vinokurov, who is under EU sanctions for &amp;ldquo;providing a substantial source of revenue to the Government of Russia.</description></item><item><title>Meritservus And Meritkapital</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/meritservus_and_meritkapital/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/meritservus_and_meritkapital/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MeritServus and MeritKapital Over 400,000 files and 72,000 emails from MeritServus and MeritKapital, which provide corporate registration and administration, asset management and holding company services along with golden passport services. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Cyprus TYPE Hack SOURCE F R E A K Y FILE SIZE 500 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 400,000 files and 72,000 emails from MeritServus and MeritKapital, which provide corporate registration, administration, asset management and holding company services along with golden passport services.</description></item><item><title>Mk Brokers</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mk_brokers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mk_brokers/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MK Brokers 23 gigabytes hacked from the Bulgarian investment firm MK Brokers, including nearly 150,000 files. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Bulgaria TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBit FILE SIZE 8.15 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
23 gigabytes hacked from the Bulgarian investment firm MK Brokers, including nearly 150,000 files.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=MK_Brokers&amp;amp;oldid=2194&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box Bulgaria Corporate Hack Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Myanmar Financials</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myanmar_financials/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myanmar_financials/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Myanmar Financials Hundreds of thousands of records relating to the corporate ownership and for companies in Myanmar. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Myanmar TYPE Scrape SOURCE donk_enby FILE SIZE 330.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Business Insider EDITOR NOTES
Hundreds of thousands of records relating to the corporate ownership and for companies in Myanmar from the offices of myco.</description></item><item><title>Myanmar Investments</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myanmar_investments/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myanmar_investments/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Myanmar Investments Thousands of confidential documents and investment proposals and approvals hacked from the Myanmar Investment Commission. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Myanmar TYPE Hack SOURCE Sugondese separatist Bofa FILE SIZE 156 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Justice for Myanmar EDITOR NOTES Source statement Contents [1] [Description] [2] [Burmese Translation] [3] [Research] [4] [Aftermath] [5] [Source Information] [6] [See Also] Description Thousands of confidential documents and investment proposals and approvals hacked from the Myanmar Investment Commission.</description></item><item><title>Newbridge Securities</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/newbridge_securities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/newbridge_securities/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Newbridge Securities Corporation Approximately 90 gigabytes from Newbridge Securities, a securities brokerage, investment banking and wealth management services firm. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Marketo FILE SIZE 93 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 90 gigabytes from Newbridge Securities, a securities brokerage, investment banking and wealth management services firm.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Odebrecht</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odebrecht/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odebrecht/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Odrebrecht 390,000 application (non-employee) emails ranging from 2008 to 2022 and 365 fserver emails ranging from April 2021 to early May 2022 from Novonor, previously Odebrecht S.A. The fserver emails contain details of SWIFT transfers, including payments to their employees and lawyers in the United States. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil, Dominican Republic, United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 12.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Patron Papers</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/patron_papers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/patron_papers/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Patrón Papers Reports Paraguay&amp;rsquo;s Secretariat for the Prevention of Money or Property Laundering which include an investigation into tobacco smuggling and payments made to public officials by companies linked to former president Horacio Cartes. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Paraguay TYPE Leak SOURCE FILE SIZE 500 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [Link] DIRECT DOWNLOAD [Link] EDITOR NOTES
Documents from Seprelad, Paraguay&amp;rsquo;s Secretariat for the Prevention of Money or Property Laundering.</description></item><item><title>Pricewaterhousecoopers</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pricewaterhousecoopers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pricewaterhousecoopers/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from PricewaterhouseCoopers)]
RELEASE
PWC Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Pscb</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pscb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pscb/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
PSCB 229,000 emails and 630,000 files from the Petersburg Social Commercial Bank / Петербургский социальный коммерческий банк, one of the top 100 Russian banks in terms of net assets. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE NB65 FILE SIZE 542 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
229,000 emails and 630,000 files from the Petersburg Social Commercial Bank / Петербургский социальный коммерческий банк, one of the top 100 Russian banks in terms of net assets.</description></item><item><title>Pwc</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pwc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pwc/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
PWC Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Rossi + Mps</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/rossi_+_mps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/rossi_+_mps/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Rossi + MPS The files from the investigation of the murder of David Rossi, the communications director at Monte dei Paschi di Siena. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Italy TYPE Leak SOURCE Val Broeksmit FILE SIZE 2.8 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Telegraph, Daily Telegraph, Bloomberg EDITOR NOTES Val Broeksmit (deceased) was an FBI informant. The FBI had no known involvement in the leak.</description></item><item><title>Sberbank Of Russia</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sberbank_of_russia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sberbank_of_russia/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Sberbank of Russia Over 13,500 files hacked from Sberbank of Russia&amp;rsquo;s translation bureau. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States, Russia, Ukraine TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 2.1 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Over 13,500 files hacked from Sberbank of Russia&amp;rsquo;s translation bureau, providing a unique insight into the interests of the bank and its clients. Translations include political analysis, military sales, and open source reporting.</description></item><item><title>Sherwood</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sherwood/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sherwood/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Sherwood Copies of the servers of the Cayman National Bank and Trust (Isle of Man). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Cayman Islands TYPE Hack SOURCE Phineas Fisher FILE SIZE 2.26 TB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Unicorn Riot EDITOR NOTES
Copies of the servers of the Cayman National Bank and Trust (Isle of Man) via the hacktivist sometimes known as Phineas Fisher.</description></item><item><title>Special:Categories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialcategories/</guid><description>Help
The following categories exist on the wiki, and may or may not be unused. Also see wanted categories.
[Categories]
[Display categories starting at:]
[Show]
(first | last) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Allegations of State Sponsorship‏‎ (22 members) Angola‏‎ (1 member) Anonymous‏‎ (86 members) Argentina‏‎ (4 members) Australia‏‎ (4 members) Azerbaijan‏‎ (2 members) Bahamas‏‎ (0 members) Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box‏‎ (25 members) Belarus‏‎ (2 members) Belgium‏‎ (1 member) Bolivia‏‎ (1 member) Brazil‏‎ (11 members) Bulgaria‏‎ (1 member) Cambodia‏‎ (1 member) Canada‏‎ (4 members) Cayman Islands‏‎ (1 member) Chile‏‎ (6 members) China‏‎ (2 members) Colombia‏‎ (6 members) Cook Islands‏‎ (1 member) Corporate‏‎ (136 members) Cyberwar‏‎ (54 members) Cyprus‏‎ (1 member) Dominican Republic‏‎ (1 member) Ecuador‏‎ (3 members) El Salvador‏‎ (3 members) Environmental‏‎ (41 members) Estonia‏‎ (1 member) Ethiopia‏‎ (1 member) European Union‏‎ (2 members) Extractivist Leaks‏‎ (7 members) Fascist‏‎ (23 members) France‏‎ (3 members) Fuerzas Represivas‏‎ (7 members) Germany‏‎ (5 members) Guatemala‏‎ (2 members) Guinea Ecuatorial‏‎ (1 member) Hack‏‎ (216 members) Iceland‏‎ (1 member) India‏‎ (1 member) Indonesia‏‎ (4 members) Iran‏‎ (4 members) Iraq‏‎ (1 member) Italy‏‎ (6 members) Jordan‏‎ (1 member) Leak‏‎ (24 members) Leak Markets‏‎ (3 members) Limited Distribution‏‎ (84 members) Mexico‏‎ (1 member) MilicoLeaks‏‎ (2 members) (first | last) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Special:Mostlinkedcategories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialmostlinkedcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialmostlinkedcategories/</guid><description>Showing below up to 50 results in range #1 to #50.
View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Hack‏‎ (216 members) Corporate‏‎ (136 members) Anonymous‏‎ (86 members) Limited Distribution‏‎ (84 members) United States of America‏‎ (72 members) Russia‏‎ (65 members) Cyberwar‏‎ (54 members) Ransomware‏‎ (53 members) Environmental‏‎ (41 members) Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box‏‎ (25 members) Leak‏‎ (24 members) Organization‏‎ (24 members) Fascist‏‎ (23 members) Allegations of State Sponsorship‏‎ (22 members) Brazil‏‎ (11 members) Researchers‏‎ (10 members) Ukraine‏‎ (8 members) Extractivist Leaks‏‎ (7 members) Fuerzas Represivas‏‎ (7 members) Italy‏‎ (6 members) Chile‏‎ (6 members) Scrape‏‎ (6 members) Colombia‏‎ (6 members) Germany‏‎ (5 members) Australia‏‎ (4 members) Iran‏‎ (4 members) Argentina‏‎ (4 members) United Kingdom‏‎ (4 members) Myanmar‏‎ (4 members) Indonesia‏‎ (4 members) Canada‏‎ (4 members) Thailand‏‎ (3 members) Syria‏‎ (3 members) Turkey‏‎ (3 members) France‏‎ (3 members) Paraguay‏‎ (3 members) Peru‏‎ (3 members) Leak Markets‏‎ (3 members) El Salvador‏‎ (3 members) Ecuador‏‎ (3 members) China‏‎ (2 members) European Union‏‎ (2 members) Azerbaijan‏‎ (2 members) Panama‏‎ (2 members) Venezuela‏‎ (2 members) Belarus‏‎ (2 members) Guatemala‏‎ (2 members) MilicoLeaks‏‎ (2 members) Angola‏‎ (1 member) Bulgaria‏‎ (1 member) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Special:Uncategorizedcategories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialuncategorizedcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialuncategorizedcategories/</guid><description>Help
Showing below up to 50 results in range #1 to #50.
View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Allegations of State Sponsorship Angola Anonymous Argentina Australia Azerbaijan Bahamas Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box Belarus Belgium Bolivia Brazil Bulgaria Cambodia Canada Cayman Islands Chile China Colombia Cook Islands Corporate Cyberwar Cyprus Dominican Republic Ecuador El Salvador Environmental Estonia Ethiopia European Union Extractivist Leaks Fascist France Fuerzas Represivas Germany Guatemala Guinea Ecuatorial Hack Iceland India Indonesia Iran Iraq Italy Jordan Leak Leak Markets Limited Distribution Mexico MilicoLeaks View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Tendertech</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tendertech/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tendertech/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Tendertech 426,000 emails from Tendertech / Тендертех, a firm specializing in processing financial and banking documents on behalf of businesses and entrepreneurs. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 160 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
426,000 emails from Tendertech / Тендертех, a firm specializing in processing financial and banking documents on behalf of businesses and entrepreneurs.</description></item><item><title>Trust Capital Funding</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/trust_capital_funding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/trust_capital_funding/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Trust Capital Funding Over 230 gigabytes from the financing company Trust Capital Funding, which provides funding for commercial real estate, franchise startups and businesses as well as merchant processing and other banking products. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE BlackMatter FILE SIZE 233 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 230 gigabytes from the financing company Trust Capital Funding, which provides funding for commercial real estate, franchise startups and businesses as well as merchant processing and other banking products.</description></item><item><title>Worldwide Invest</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/worldwide_invest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/worldwide_invest/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Worldwide Invest Nearly 250,000 emails from Worldwide Invest / ВОРЛДВАЙД ИНВЕСТ АС, an investment firms with ties to Estonia and Russian railways. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 130 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 250,000 emails from Worldwide Invest / ВОРЛДВАЙД ИНВЕСТ АС, an investment firms with ties to Estonia and Russian railways.</description></item></channel></rss>