<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Leak on DDoSecrets Wiki</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/leak/</link><description>Recent content in Leak on DDoSecrets Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/leak/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Acpeds</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/acpeds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/acpeds/</guid><description>ACPeds From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
ACPeds Video of call discussing the Dobbs v. Jackson ruling overturning Roe v. Wade; archive of SBAlist private pre-Dobbs/post-Dobbs planning materials; ACPeds internal strategy documents, meeting minutes, emails and other communications. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Leak SOURCE FILE SIZE 20 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link EDITOR NOTES
A Google Drive published on the American College of Pediatricians' website including financial records, PII for its 700 members, and video of an internal planning session.</description></item><item><title>Assangeleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/assangeleaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/assangeleaks/</guid><description>AssangeLeaks From Distributed Denial of Secrets
AssangeLeaks AssangeLeaks The documents published today include chat logs, contracts, and financial information covering early years in the Assange organization. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY TYPE Leak SOURCE FILE SIZE 25 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
With the Justice Department&amp;rsquo;s superseding indictment against Assange, public access to the evidence becomes critical. The documents in this file illuminate that case and illustrate how WikiLeaks operates behind closed doors.</description></item></channel></rss>