<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>United States of
America on DDoSecrets Wiki</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/united-states-of-america/</link><description>Recent content in United States of
America on DDoSecrets Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/united-states-of-america/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Acpeds</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/acpeds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/acpeds/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
ACPeds Video of call discussing the Dobbs v. Jackson ruling overturning Roe v. Wade; archive of SBAlist private pre-Dobbs/post-Dobbs planning materials; ACPeds internal strategy documents, meeting minutes, emails and other communications. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Leak SOURCE FILE SIZE 20 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link EDITOR NOTES
A Google Drive published on the American College of Pediatricians' website including financial records, PII for its 700 members, and video of an internal planning session.</description></item><item><title>Aerial Surveillance Footage</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aerial_surveillance_footage/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aerial_surveillance_footage/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Aerial Surveillance Footage Over 600 hours of aerial surveillance footage taken by police helicopters in and around Dallas, TX and Atlanta, GA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 1.9 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link
Over 600 hours of aerial surveillance footage taken by police helicopters in and around Dallas, TX and Atlanta, GA.
The extensive footage reveals the capabilities of the &amp;ldquo;military-grade&amp;rdquo; technology behind police surveillance.</description></item><item><title>Airman Teixeira Leaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/airman_teixeira_leaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/airman_teixeira_leaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Airman Teixeira Leaks Photographs of classified documents leaked by Airman Jack Teixeira to a series of Discord channels. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Jack Teixeira FILE SIZE 53 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link REFERENCES Wikipedia EDITOR NOTES
Photographs of classified documents leaked by U.S. Airman Jack Teixeira from the 102nd Intelligence Wing of the Massachusetts Air National Guard.</description></item><item><title>Alliance Coal</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/alliance_coal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/alliance_coal/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Alliance Coal 42 GB of files hacked from the second largest coal producer in the Eastern U.S., including over 180,000 emails. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Vice FILE SIZE 42 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
42 GB of files hacked from the second largest coal producer in the Eastern U.S., including over 180,000 emails.</description></item><item><title>Apex Mobile</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/apex_mobile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/apex_mobile/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Apex Mobile 25 GB from Apex Mobile, a set of apps used by &amp;ldquo;over 150 civic, law enforcement and fire agencies across the US and Canada&amp;rdquo; for reporting and collecting information. The data includes over 36,000 reports, 18,000 images, and at least 15,000 messages. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 25 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Azusa Police Department</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/azusa_police_department/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/azusa_police_department/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Azusa Police Department Approximately 3.5 gigabytes (uncompressed) of data hacked from the police department in Azusa, CA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE DoppelPaymer FILE SIZE 2.85 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 3.5 gigabytes (uncompressed) of data hacked from the police department in Azusa, CA by DoppelPaymer. The dataset includes 3 gigabytes of case files, 100 megabytes of forms and training materials from their jail, payroll information for 2018-2021, shift assignments for 2016-2021 and 100 megabytes of miscellaneous information.</description></item><item><title>Bedford County, Pa Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bedford_county_pa_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bedford_county_pa_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Bedford County, PA Emails 5,000 emails leaked from a government server in Bedford County, Pennsylvania with material dated through February 5, 2021. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Hollidaysburg Community Watchdog FILE SIZE 2.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
5,000 emails leaked from a government server in Bedford County, Pennsylvania with material dated through February 5, 2021.</description></item><item><title>Blueleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/blueleaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/blueleaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
BlueLeaks BLUELEAKS Situational awareness bulletins, training materials and fusion center reports for more than 200 law enforcement agencies. dated August 1996 to June 2020. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 269 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link IPFS QmdUQ2d2PGA5q1L4pDhd9fek1ejzowbZKTMCnAYR2EgViA MORE REFERENCES Small Wars and Insurgencies EDITOR NOTES Type brief description here BlueLeaks, sometimes referred to by the hashtag #BlueLeaks, is 269 gigabytes of internal U.</description></item><item><title>Bob Otto Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bob_otto_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bob_otto_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Bob Otto emails Hacked emails from senior State Department official Robert Otto. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 635 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Hacked emails from senior State Department official Robert Otto.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Bob_Otto_emails&amp;amp;oldid=2127&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
United States of America Hack</description></item><item><title>Boy Scouts Of America</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/boy_scouts_of_america/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/boy_scouts_of_america/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Boy Scouts of America | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Records disclosed in litigation | | | detailing alleged or actual child | | | sexual abuse activities by BSA | | | employees or prospective | | | employees. | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | DATASET DETAILS | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | COUNTRIES | United States | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | TYPE | Research | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | SOURCE | Crew Janci LLP/Los Angeles Times | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | FILE SIZE | 1.</description></item><item><title>Bradley Foundation</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bradley_foundation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bradley_foundation/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Bradley Foundation Documents hacked by Russian state actors, including a forgery aimed at discrediting Hillary Clinton. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE RIS (alleged) FILE SIZE 29.9 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Vocativ EDITOR NOTES
Documents hacked by Russian state actors, including a forgery aimed at discrediting Hillary Clinton.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Bradley_Foundation&amp;amp;oldid=2129&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Organization Allegations of State Sponsorship United States of America</description></item><item><title>Cablegate</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cablegate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cablegate/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Cablegate 251,287 diplomatic cables released by Chelsea Manning through WikiLeaks. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Chelsea Manning FILE SIZE 557.6 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
251,287 diplomatic cables released by Chelsea Manning through WikiLeaks.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Cablegate&amp;amp;oldid=2130&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Leak United States of America</description></item><item><title>Casolaro Files</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/casolaro_files/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/casolaro_files/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
The Casolaro Files represent the surviving notebooks, files, clippings and draft writings by journalist Danny Casolaro, detailing his investigations into some of the most prominent American political controversies of the 1980s and early 90s; drawing connections in a cabal he referred to as &amp;ldquo;The Octopus&amp;rdquo;. These records are held by the State Historical Society of Missouri as part of their collection on the Arizona Project and were photographed by Christian Hansen.</description></item><item><title>Chinga La Migra</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chinga_la_migra/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chinga_la_migra/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Chinga La Migra A series of hacks against Arizona and Texas law enforcement by Anonymous-affiliated group LulzSec/AntiSec. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE LulzSec/AntiSec FILE SIZE DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link MAGNET (II) Link MAGNET (III) Link MAGNET (IV) Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A series of hacks against Arizona and Texas law enforcement by Anonymous-affiliated group LulzSec/AntiSec.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Chinga_La_Migra&amp;amp;oldid=2137&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Condie Construction Company</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/condie_construction_company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/condie_construction_company/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Condie Construction Company 57 gigabytes hacked from Condie Construction Company, which specializes in pipeline and infrastructure installation. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 57 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
57 gigabytes hacked from Condie Construction Company, a general engineering construction company specializing in pipeline and infrastructure installation. Their projects have budgets of up to $40 million and include culinary waterlines, sewer lines, pressurized irrigation pipelines, storm drainage, waster water treatment facilities, roadway reconstruction and new roadway construction.</description></item><item><title>Council For National Policy</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/council_for_national_policy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/council_for_national_policy/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Council for National Policy An unredacted copy of the highly restricted September 2020 membership directory for the Council for National Policy, an umbrella organization and networking group for conservative and Republican activists in the United States. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 3.9 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES New York Times, The Nation EDITOR NOTES A redacted version from 2014 was previously published by the Southern Poverty Law Center and a redacted version of the 2020 list is available here.</description></item><item><title>Denver Pd Crowd Management Manual</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/denver_pd_crowd_management_manual/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/denver_pd_crowd_management_manual/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Denver PD Crowd Management Manual The Denver Police Crowd Control Manual, obtained and published by Unicorn Riot. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Unicorn Riot FILE SIZE 16.6 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Unicorn Riot EDITOR NOTES
The Denver Police Crowd Control Manual, obtained and published by Unicorn Riot.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Denver_PD_Crowd_Management_Manual&amp;amp;oldid=2142&amp;rdquo;
Category:
United States of America</description></item><item><title>Dnc Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dnc_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dnc_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
DNC Emails Over 44,000 emails from the the US Democratic National Committee DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Guccifer 2.0 FILE SIZE DOWNLOADS MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES The archive was manually compiled by DDoSecrets due to WikiLeaks&amp;rsquo; decision to not make an archive available. Over 44,000 emails from the the US Democratic National Committee, hacked by Russian intelligence services and released under the pseudonym Guccifer 2.</description></item><item><title>Documents From Us Espionage Den</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/documents_from_us_espionage_den/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/documents_from_us_espionage_den/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Documents from US Espionage Den CIA documents seized by Iranian students during the 1979 Iranian revolution, when the embassy was overrun. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Iran/United States TYPE SOURCE Iran FILE SIZE 375.75 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Washington Post New York Times EDITOR NOTES
In November 1979, Iranian students seized an entire archive of CIA and State Department documents, which represented one of the most extensive losses of secret data in the history of any modern intelligence service.</description></item><item><title>Enron Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/enron_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/enron_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Enron Emails A complete selection of Enron&amp;rsquo;s emails (about 2x as previous releases) in .eml format. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Official SOURCE FILE SIZE 68.8 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link, Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A complete selection of Enron&amp;rsquo;s emails (about 2x as previous releases) in .eml format. Not to be confused with the Enron files.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.</description></item><item><title>Enron Files</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/enron_files/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/enron_files/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Enron files Documents, recordings and other records collected in the wake of the Enron scandal. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Official SOURCE FILE SIZE 2 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES MuckRock EDITOR NOTES
Documents, recordings and other records collected in the wake of the Enron scandal. Not to be confused with the Enron emails.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Enron_files&amp;amp;oldid=2150&amp;rdquo;
Categories:</description></item><item><title>Fbi Dhs Leak</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fbi-dhs_leak/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fbi-dhs_leak/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
FBI-DHS leak Hacked FBI and DHS personnel information released by @CthulhuSec. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 631.2 kB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Hacked FBI and DHS personnel information released by @CthulhuSec.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=FBI-DHS_leak&amp;amp;oldid=2154&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack United States of America</description></item><item><title>Fbiâ€™S Secret Rules</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fbis_secret_rules/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fbis_secret_rules/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
FBI&amp;rsquo;s Secret Rules Copies of the FBI&amp;rsquo;s secret investigative authorities and guidelines. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Leak SOURCE FILE SIZE 73.7 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES The Intercept EDITOR NOTES
Materials released by The Intercept on the FBI&amp;rsquo;s secret investigative authorities and guidelines.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=FBI&amp;rsquo;s_Secret_Rules&amp;amp;oldid=1154&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Leak United States of America</description></item><item><title>Fisher &amp; Paykel</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fisher__paykel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fisher__paykel/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fisher &amp;amp; Paykel Over 30 gigabytes hacked from Fisher &amp;amp; Paykel, a major appliance manufacturer which is a subsidiary of home appliance manufacturer Haier, based in East Tamaki, New Zealand. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES New Zealand, Italy, United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 31 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 30 gigabytes hacked from Fisher &amp;amp; Paykel, a major appliance manufacturer which is a subsidiary of home appliance manufacturer Haier, based in East Tamaki, New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Fraternal Order Of Police</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fraternal_order_of_police/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fraternal_order_of_police/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fraternal Order of Police Files from the Fraternal Order of Police. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 260 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Guardian EDITOR NOTES
Hacked files from the Fraternal Order of Police.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Fraternal_Order_of_Police&amp;amp;oldid=2157&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Organization United States of America</description></item><item><title>Fuck Fbi Friday</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fuck_fbi_friday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fuck_fbi_friday/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fuck FBI Friday A series of hacks against United States law enforcement agencies and contractors by Anonymous-affiliated group Lulzsec/Antisec. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Lulzsec/Antisec FILE SIZE 5.28 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link MAGNET (III) Link MAGNET (IV) Link MAGNET (V) Link MAGNET (VI) Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A series of hacks against the Federal Bureau of Investigation, law enforcement agencies, and contractors by Anonymous-affiliated group Lulzsec/Antisec.</description></item><item><title>Gop Election Theft</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gop_election_theft/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gop_election_theft/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from GOP Election Theft)]
RELEASE
Hofeller Files Files showing gerrymandering and other often questionable election tactics and strategies used by the Republicans. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Stephanie Hofeller FILE SIZE 19.21 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES NPR, New Yorker, New York Times EDITOR NOTES
Files showing gerrymandering and other often questionable election tactics and strategies used by the Republicans, taken from a leading GOP strategist.</description></item><item><title>Guccifer 2.0</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/guccifer_2.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/guccifer_2.0/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Guccifer 2.0 Records released directly by Guccifer 2.0, a persona operated by Russian intelligence. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Guccifer 2.0 FILE SIZE (WordPress) 119 MB FILE SIZE (CF) 820 MB FILE SIZE (NGP VAN) 678.4 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET (WordPress) Link MAGNET (CF) Link MAGNET (NGP VAN) Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Motherboard EmptyWheel ThreatConnect EmpyWheel Forbes EDITOR NOTES Guccifer 2.</description></item><item><title>Guccifer Archive</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/guccifer_archive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/guccifer_archive/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Guccifer Archive The files released by the original Guccifer. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Guccifer FILE SIZE 6.9 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
The files released by the original Guccifer, including files hacked Hillary Clinton emails and George W. Bush paintings.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Guccifer_Archive&amp;amp;oldid=2484&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack United States of America</description></item><item><title>Gulf Copper</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gulf_copper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gulf_copper/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Gulf Copper Over 9,000 files from Gulf Copper Energy Services, which serves major and independent offshore drilling rig contractors, offshore oil and gas operating and service companies, national oil companies, major commercial ship operators and the United States government and military. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Conti FILE SIZE 4.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Hofeller Files</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hofeller_files/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hofeller_files/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Hofeller Files Files showing gerrymandering and other often questionable election tactics and strategies used by the Republicans. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Stephanie Hofeller FILE SIZE 19.21 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES NPR, New Yorker, New York Times EDITOR NOTES
Files showing gerrymandering and other often questionable election tactics and strategies used by the Republicans, taken from a leading GOP strategist.</description></item><item><title>Hunter Biden Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hunter_biden_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hunter_biden_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Hunter Biden emails
Approximately 128,500 emails allegedly from the Hunter Biden laptop. The emails are dated between 2009 and 2019. There are anomalies with the dates and emails, in addition to concerns about the chain of custody. There are considerable issues with this dataset including signs of tampering.
DATASET DETAILS
COUNTRIES United States
TYPE Unknown
SOURCE See Editor Notes below
FILE SIZE 3.6 GB</description></item><item><title>Hunter Biden Iphone And Ipad Backups</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hunter_biden_iphone_and_ipad_backups/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hunter_biden_iphone_and_ipad_backups/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Hunter Biden iPhone and iPad | | | Backups | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Backups of an iPhone and iPad | | | allegedly used by Hunter Biden, | | | released onto 4chan by | | | &amp;ldquo;Kiwianon.&amp;rdquo; | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | DATASET DETAILS | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | COUNTRIES | United States | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | TYPE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | SOURCE | 4chan / Kiwianon | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | FILE SIZE | 28.</description></item><item><title>Hunter Biden Laptop</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hunter_biden_laptop/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hunter_biden_laptop/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Hunter Biden Laptop An alleged copy of the Hunter Biden laptop, released onto 4chan by someone apparently sometimes referred to as &amp;ldquo;Kiwianon.&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE SOURCE 4chan / KiwiAnon FILE SIZE 400 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES See the Hunter Biden emailsdataset for concerns and issues relating to data sourced from the same laptop that the backups appear to have been taken from.</description></item><item><title>Illinois Attorney General</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/illinois_attorney_general/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/illinois_attorney_general/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Illinois Attorney General A cache of files hacked from the Illinois Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s office. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE DoppelPaymer FILE SIZE About 200 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES ThreatPost EDITOR NOTES
A cache of files hacked from the Illinois Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s office by the ransomware crew DoppelPaymer. The total cache is allegedly &amp;ldquo;about 200 GB&amp;rdquo; that will be &amp;ldquo;progressively uploaded.</description></item><item><title>Innodata</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/innodata/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/innodata/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Innodata The first release of data from a surveillance company allegedly hacked by Anonymous. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Popov FILE SIZE (Part 1) 1.1 GB FILE SIZE (Part 2) 579 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET (Part 1) Link MAGNET (Part 2) Link MORE REFERENCES Emma Best EDITOR NOTES Igor Maksym Popov is a hacker, former FBI informant and a self-described contractor for Russia and Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>J.Irwin Company</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/j.irwin_company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/j.irwin_company/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
J. Irwin Company 300 megabytes from J. Irwin Company, which installs pipeline and constructs processing plants, compressor stations and other facilities for gas, oil and water transportation. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Xing FILE SIZE 309 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
300 megabytes from J. Irwin Company, which installs pipelines and constructs processing plants, compressor stations and other facilities for gas, oil and water transportation.</description></item><item><title>Jeb Bush Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jeb_bush_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jeb_bush_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Jeb Bush Emails Over 1.5 million emails released - and then removed - by the Jeb Bush campaign in 2015. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Leak SOURCE Jeb Bush FILE SIZE 32.6 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES CBS, The Verge Over 1.5 million emails released - and then removed - by the Jeb Bush campaign in 2015.</description></item><item><title>Jones Day</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jones_day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jones_day/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Jones Day Data hacked from the high profile Jones Day law firm, including data associated with the city of Chicago and Chicago PD, as well as data associated with the credit reporting agency Experian. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 85 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES VICE EDITOR NOTES
Data hacked from the high profile Jones Day lawfirm, including data associated with the city of Chicago and Chicago PD, as well as data associated with the credit reporting agency Experian.</description></item><item><title>Liberty Counsel</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/liberty_counsel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/liberty_counsel/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Liberty Counsel Databases from the far-right lobby and litigation group Liberty Counsel. Also: databases for Christian missionary groups using WMTEK software for customer management. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States, Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published by Enlace Hacktivista Liberty Counsel helped overturn Roe v. Wade, and claim to have prayed with Supreme Court justices.</description></item><item><title>Linestar</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/linestar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/linestar/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
LineStar 37 gigabytes hacked from the integrated pipeline compliance, technology and integrity maintenance company LineStar, along with 73,500 emails. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Xing FILE SIZE 37 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Wired EDITOR NOTES
37 gigabytes hacked from the integrated pipeline compliance, technology and integrity maintenance company LineStar.
Contents [1] [Redactions] [2] [Emails] Redactions For usability and to reduce the potential for abuse, approximately 19 gigabytes of .</description></item><item><title>Manafort Texts</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/manafort_texts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/manafort_texts/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Manafort texts Text messages obtained from the phone of Paul Manafort&amp;rsquo;s daughter. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 98.4 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES In a private communication, WikiLeaks stated that they thought the phone had been hacked by Ukrainian intelligence. Text messages obtained from the phone of Paul Manafort&amp;rsquo;s daughter. In a private communication, WikiLeaks stated that they thought the phone had been hacked by Ukrainian intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Mclanahan Russia</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mclanahan_russia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mclanahan_russia/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
McLanahan Russia 311,122 emails from McLanahan Russia, a mining equipment and services company with its origin and corporate headquarters in Hollidaysburg, Pennsylvania. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia, United States of America TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 302 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
311,122 emails from McLanahan Russia, a mining equipment and services company with its origin and corporate headquarters in Hollidaysburg, Pennsylvania.</description></item><item><title>Metropolitan Police Department D.C.</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/metropolitan_police_department_d.c./</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/metropolitan_police_department_d.c./</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Municipal Court Of Princeton</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/municipal_court_of_princeton/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/municipal_court_of_princeton/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Municipal Court of Princeton Nearly 30 GB of appeal letters, accounting and audit information, amendment documents, tax information and chats. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Marketo FILE SIZE 28 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 30 GB of appeal letters, accounting and audit information, amendment documents, tax information and chats.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Newbridge Securities</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/newbridge_securities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/newbridge_securities/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Newbridge Securities Corporation Approximately 90 gigabytes from Newbridge Securities, a securities brokerage, investment banking and wealth management services firm. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Marketo FILE SIZE 93 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 90 gigabytes from Newbridge Securities, a securities brokerage, investment banking and wealth management services firm.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>No Fly List</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/no_fly_list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/no_fly_list/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
No Fly List A copy of the United States&amp;rsquo; No Fly List from 2019, which CommuteAir left on an misconfigured (unsecured) development server. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE maia crimew FILE SIZE 90 MB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES maia.crimew, Daily Dot EDITOR NOTES
A copy of the United States&amp;rsquo; No Fly List from 2019, which CommuteAir left on an misconfigured (unsecured) development server.</description></item><item><title>North American Roofing</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/north_american_roofing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/north_american_roofing/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
North American Roofing 83 gigabytes hacked from the &amp;ldquo;most trusted and respected commercial roofing company in the U.S.&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 83 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
83 gigabytes hacked from the &amp;ldquo;most trusted and respected commercial roofing company in the U.S.&amp;rdquo; The company not only boasts about the quality of its work and its community involvement, but about its sustainability program and green initiative.</description></item><item><title>Nsa Report On Russia Spearphishing</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/nsa_report_on_russia_spearphishing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/nsa_report_on_russia_spearphishing/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
NSA Report on Russia Spearphishing An NSA report on Russian hacking efforts in the days before the 2016 U.S. Presidential election. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Reality Winner FILE SIZE 5.5 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Intercept EDITOR NOTES
An NSA report on Russian hacking efforts in the days before the 2016 U.S. Presidential election.</description></item><item><title>Oakland City Hall</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oakland_city_hall/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oakland_city_hall/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Oakland City Hall Internal documents from Oakland City Hall. The data includes policy documents, misconduct records and bank statements. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE PLAY FILE SIZE 11.7 GB and 600 GB How to Request Access MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Internal emails and files from Oakland City Hall, a mid-sized city in the San Francisco Bay area with a long history of human rights violations.</description></item><item><title>Oath Keepers</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oath_keepers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oath_keepers/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Oath Keepers Approximately 5 gigabytes of emails, chat logs, members and donor lists and other files from the servers of the Oath Keepers. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Southern Poverty Law Center EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 5 gigabytes of emails, chat logs, members and donor lists and other files from the servers of the Oath Keepers.</description></item><item><title>Odebrecht</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odebrecht/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odebrecht/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Odrebrecht 390,000 application (non-employee) emails ranging from 2008 to 2022 and 365 fserver emails ranging from April 2021 to early May 2022 from Novonor, previously Odebrecht S.A. The fserver emails contain details of SWIFT transfers, including payments to their employees and lawyers in the United States. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil, Dominican Republic, United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 12.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Odin Intelligence</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odin_intelligence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odin_intelligence/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
ODIN Intelligence 19 GB including thousands of photos, audio recordings, reports and user information from ODIN Intelligence and SweepWizard, a pair of apps geared towards law enforcement that primarily target houseless people. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE All Cyber-cops Are Bastards FILE SIZE 19 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES VICE, Wired, TechCrunch EDITOR NOTES
19 GB including thousands of photos, audio recordings, reports and user information from ODIN Intelligence and SweepWizard, a pair of apps geared towards law enforcement that primarily target houseless people.</description></item><item><title>Parler</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/parler/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/parler/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Parler Over a million videos and a million images uploaded to Parler, including ones from the January 6 Washington D.C. coup attempt. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Worldwide TYPE Scrape SOURCE donk_enby FILE SIZE 32.1 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES January 6 video metadata timelapse map; Kyle McDonald&amp;rsquo;s Parler map. Over a million videos and a million images uploaded to Parler, including ones from the January 6 Washington D.</description></item><item><title>Patriot Front</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/patriot_front/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/patriot_front/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Patriot Front Over 400 gigabytes of leaked records from Patriot Front, a U.S.-based neo-Nazi organization with chapters around the country. This leak includes videos, photos, documents, and chat messages. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Unicorn Riot FILE SIZE 440 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES A Guide To Patriot Front&amp;rsquo;s Leaked Media Files, Patriot Front Fascist Leak Exposes Nationwide Racist Campaigns, Unicorn Riot Far Right Investigations Desk, Rocket Chat archive EDITOR NOTES See also Patriot Front audio Over 400 gigabytes of leaked records from Patriot Front, a U.</description></item><item><title>Patriot Front Audio</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/patriot_front_audio/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/patriot_front_audio/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Patriot Front audio Audio files from Patriot Front&amp;rsquo;s discord server. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Unicorn Riot FILE SIZE 187.7 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Unicorn Riot EDITOR NOTES
Audio files from Patriot Front&amp;rsquo;s discord server, obtained and published by Unicorn Riot.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Patriot_Front_audio&amp;amp;oldid=2211&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
United States of America Fascist</description></item><item><title>Podesta Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/podesta_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/podesta_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Podesta emails A manual scrape of the Podesta emails, hacked by Russian state actors. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE DCLeaks FILE SIZE 3.3 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Includes WikiLeaks&amp;rsquo; duplicates. A manual scrape of the Podesta emails, hacked by Russian state actors.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Podesta_emails&amp;amp;oldid=2217&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Allegations of State Sponsorship Hack Organization United States of America</description></item><item><title>President Donald Trumpâ€™S Private Schedules</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/president_donald_trumps_private_schedules/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/president_donald_trumps_private_schedules/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s Private Schedules More than 90 pages of President Trump&amp;rsquo;s private schedules. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Axios FILE SIZE 296 KB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Axios EDITOR NOTES
More than 90 pages of President Trump&amp;rsquo;s private schedules, more detailed and more accurate than the officially released schedules.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=President_Donald_Trump&amp;rsquo;s_Private_Schedules&amp;amp;oldid=2220&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Leak United States of America</description></item><item><title>President Donald Trumpâ€™S Private Schedules</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/president_donald_trumps_private_schedules/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/president_donald_trumps_private_schedules/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s Private Schedules More than 90 pages of President Trump&amp;rsquo;s private schedules. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Axios FILE SIZE 296 KB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Axios EDITOR NOTES
More than 90 pages of President Trump&amp;rsquo;s private schedules, more detailed and more accurate than the officially released schedules.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=President_Donald_Trump&amp;rsquo;s_Private_Schedules&amp;amp;oldid=2220&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Leak United States of America</description></item><item><title>Presque Isle Police Department</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/presque_isle_police_department/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/presque_isle_police_department/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Presque Isle Police Department Nearly 200 gigabytes of data hacked from Presque Isle Police Department. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Avaddon FILE SIZE 195 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 200 gigabytes of data hacked from Presque Isle Police Department, including over 15,000 emails. About 10% of the cache is the department&amp;rsquo;s music collection.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Shell</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/shell/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/shell/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Shell Over 100 gigabytes hacked from the Shell global group of energy and petrochemical companies. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 104 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 100 gigabytes hacked from the Shell global group of energy and petrochemical companies.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Shell&amp;amp;oldid=2235&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Corporate Environmental Hack Ransomware United States of America</description></item><item><title>Shooting Sheriffs Saturday</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/shooting_sheriffs_saturday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/shooting_sheriffs_saturday/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Shooting Sheriffs Saturday An AntiSec hack of sheriffs&amp;rsquo; offices. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE AntiSec FILE SIZE 7.4 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES PasteBin EDITOR NOTES
An AntiSec hack of sheriffs&amp;rsquo; offices.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Shooting_Sheriffs_Saturday&amp;amp;oldid=2237&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Anonymous Hack United States of America</description></item><item><title>Snowden Archive</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/snowden_archive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/snowden_archive/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Snowden archive A collection of the Snowden documents. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Edward Snowden FILE SIZE 1.8 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A collection of the Snowden documents compiled by nsa-observer.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Snowden_archive&amp;amp;oldid=2238&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Leak United States of America</description></item><item><title>Sony</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sony/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sony/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Sony A collection of the Sony hack, which has been alleged to have been committed by North Korean hackers. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Guardians of Peace FILE SIZE 147 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES The password for the files is: diespe123 A collection of the original .rar files released as part of the Sony hack, which has been alleged to have been committed by North Korean hackers.</description></item><item><title>Special:Mostlinkedcategories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialmostlinkedcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialmostlinkedcategories/</guid><description>Showing below up to 50 results in range #1 to #50.
View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Hackâ€â€Ž (216 members) Corporateâ€â€Ž (136 members) Anonymousâ€â€Ž (86 members) Limited Distributionâ€â€Ž (84 members) United States of Americaâ€â€Ž (72 members) Russiaâ€â€Ž (65 members) Cyberwarâ€â€Ž (54 members) Ransomwareâ€â€Ž (53 members) Environmentalâ€â€Ž (41 members) Banker&amp;rsquo;s Boxâ€â€Ž (25 members) Leakâ€â€Ž (24 members) Organizationâ€â€Ž (24 members) Fascistâ€â€Ž (23 members) Allegations of State Sponsorshipâ€â€Ž (22 members) Brazilâ€â€Ž (11 members) Researchersâ€â€Ž (10 members) Ukraineâ€â€Ž (8 members) Extractivist Leaksâ€â€Ž (7 members) Fuerzas Represivasâ€â€Ž (7 members) Italyâ€â€Ž (6 members) Chileâ€â€Ž (6 members) Scrapeâ€â€Ž (6 members) Colombiaâ€â€Ž (6 members) Germanyâ€â€Ž (5 members) Australiaâ€â€Ž (4 members) Iranâ€â€Ž (4 members) Argentinaâ€â€Ž (4 members) United Kingdomâ€â€Ž (4 members) Myanmarâ€â€Ž (4 members) Indonesiaâ€â€Ž (4 members) Canadaâ€â€Ž (4 members) Thailandâ€â€Ž (3 members) Syriaâ€â€Ž (3 members) Turkeyâ€â€Ž (3 members) Franceâ€â€Ž (3 members) Paraguayâ€â€Ž (3 members) Peruâ€â€Ž (3 members) Leak Marketsâ€â€Ž (3 members) El Salvadorâ€â€Ž (3 members) Ecuadorâ€â€Ž (3 members) Chinaâ€â€Ž (2 members) European Unionâ€â€Ž (2 members) Azerbaijanâ€â€Ž (2 members) Panamaâ€â€Ž (2 members) Venezuelaâ€â€Ž (2 members) Belarusâ€â€Ž (2 members) Guatemalaâ€â€Ž (2 members) MilicoLeaksâ€â€Ž (2 members) Angolaâ€â€Ž (1 member) Bulgariaâ€â€Ž (1 member) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Tigerswan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tigerswan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tigerswan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
TigerSwan Internal TigerSwan materials documenting surveillance of and operations against Standing Rock and the Dakota Access Pipeline protestors. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Leak SOURCE The Intercept FILE SIZE 78.5 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES The Intercept EDITOR NOTES
Internal TigerSwan materials documenting surveillance of and operations against Standing Rock and the Dakota Access Pipeline protestors.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=TigerSwan&amp;amp;oldid=1174&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Trump Transition Leak</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/trump_transition_leak/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/trump_transition_leak/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Trump Transition leak Dozens of documents from the Trump administration transition, including backgrounds and opposition research on potential Trump appointees. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Axios FILE SIZE 60.2 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES Axios EDITOR NOTES
Dozens of documents from the Trump administration transition, including backgrounds and opposition research on potential Trump appointees.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Trump_Transition_leak&amp;amp;oldid=1175&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Trust Capital Funding</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/trust_capital_funding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/trust_capital_funding/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Trust Capital Funding Over 230 gigabytes from the financing company Trust Capital Funding, which provides funding for commercial real estate, franchise startups and businesses as well as merchant processing and other banking products. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE BlackMatter FILE SIZE 233 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 230 gigabytes from the financing company Trust Capital Funding, which provides funding for commercial real estate, franchise startups and businesses as well as merchant processing and other banking products.</description></item><item><title>United Northern And Southern Knights Of The Ku Klux Klan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/united_northern_and_southern_knights_of_the_ku_klux_klan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/united_northern_and_southern_knights_of_the_ku_klux_klan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
United Northern and Southern Knights of the Ku Klux Klan &amp;ldquo;Everything you wanted to know about the United Northern and Southern Knights of the Ku Klux Klan&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 424 KB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
&amp;ldquo;Everything you wanted to know about the United Northern and Southern Knights of the Ku Klux Klan&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Virginia Department Of Military Affairs</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/virginia_department_of_military_affairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/virginia_department_of_military_affairs/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Virginia Department of Military Affairs Two gigabytes of emails hacked from the Virginia Department of Military Affairs and released by the dark marketplace Marketo. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Marketo FILE SIZE 2 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Two gigabytes consisting of emails hacked from the Virginia Department of Military Affairs and released by the dark marketplace Marketo.</description></item><item><title>Vz Us Corruption</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/vz-us_corruption/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/vz-us_corruption/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
VZ-US Corruption 14,000 files allegedly documenting a Venezuela/U.S. energy sector scandal. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States / Venezuela TYPE Leak SOURCE Cryptome / Dan Rosenau FILE SIZE 9.4 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Source statement on Cryptome EDITOR NOTES
14,000 files allegedly documenting a Venezuela/U.S. energy sector scandal involving J.P. Morgan, ProEnergy Services, Derwick Associates.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=VZ-US_Corruption&amp;amp;oldid=2262&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>W.L. Contractors</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/w.l._contractors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/w.l._contractors/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
W.L. Contractors 15 gigabytes hacked from a Colorado based traffic signal, Intelligent Transportation Systems, and CCTV contractor. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 15 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
15 gigabytes hacked from a based traffic signal, ITS (Intelligent Transportation Systems), and CCTV contractor operating throughout Colorado and Wyoming.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>W&amp;T Offshore</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/wt_offshore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/wt_offshore/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
W&amp;amp;T Offshore 19 gigabytes hacked from W&amp;amp;T Offshore, an independent oil and natural gas producer, exploring, developing, and acquiring oil and natural gas in the Gulf of Mexico. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 19 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
19 gigabytes hacked from W&amp;amp;T Offshore, an independent oil and natural gas producer, exploring, developing, and acquiring oil and natural gas in the Gulf of Mexico.</description></item><item><title>Washington County Sheriff</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_county_sheriff/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_county_sheriff/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Washington County Sheriff 1,311 files hacked from the Washington County Sheriff by ransomware operator Conti. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Conti FILE SIZE 419 MB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
1,311 files hacked from the Washington County Sheriff by ransomware operator Conti.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Washington D.C. Metropolitan Pd</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Washington D.C. Metropolitan PD)]
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Washington D.C. Metropolitan Pd</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Washington D.C. Metropolitan PD)]
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item></channel></rss>