<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ransomware on DDoSecrets Wiki</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/ransomware/</link><description>Recent content in ransomware on DDoSecrets Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/ransomware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aban Offshore</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aban_offshore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aban_offshore/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Aban Offshore Approximately 14 gigabytes of files hacked by Nefilim from Aban Offshore drilling, India&amp;rsquo;s largest offshore drilling services provider to oil companies. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES India TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 14 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 14 gigabytes of files hacked by Nefilim from Aban Offshore drilling, India&amp;rsquo;s largest offshore drilling services provider to oil companies, mainly for ONGC.</description></item><item><title>Aliansce Sonae</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aliansce_sonae/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aliansce_sonae/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Aliansce Sonae 31 GB hacked of hacked files from Aliansce Sonae Shopping Centers SA, a Brazil-based company principally engaged in the development and operating of shopping centers in Brazil. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 31 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
31 GB hacked of hacked files from Aliansce Sonae Shopping Centers SA, formerly known as Sonae Sierra Brasil SA, a Brazil-based company principally engaged in the development and operating of shopping centers in Brazil.</description></item><item><title>Alliance Coal</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/alliance_coal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/alliance_coal/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Alliance Coal 42 GB of files hacked from the second largest coal producer in the Eastern U.S., including over 180,000 emails. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Vice FILE SIZE 42 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
42 GB of files hacked from the second largest coal producer in the Eastern U.S., including over 180,000 emails.</description></item><item><title>Arteris</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/arteris/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/arteris/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Arteris Over 60 gigabytes hacked from Arteris, which is responsible for the restoration, modernization, monitoring, maintenance, and operation of more than 3,250 km of Brazilian highways. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 61 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 60 gigabytes hacked from Arteris, which is responsible for the restoration, modernization, monitoring, maintenance, and operation of more than 3,250 km of Brazilian highways.</description></item><item><title>Azusa Police Department</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/azusa_police_department/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/azusa_police_department/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Azusa Police Department Approximately 3.5 gigabytes (uncompressed) of data hacked from the police department in Azusa, CA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE DoppelPaymer FILE SIZE 2.85 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 3.5 gigabytes (uncompressed) of data hacked from the police department in Azusa, CA by DoppelPaymer. The dataset includes 3 gigabytes of case files, 100 megabytes of forms and training materials from their jail, payroll information for 2018-2021, shift assignments for 2016-2021 and 100 megabytes of miscellaneous information.</description></item><item><title>Banco De PoupançA E CréDito</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/banco_de_poupan%C3%A7a_e_cr%C3%A9dito/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/banco_de_poupan%C3%A7a_e_cr%C3%A9dito/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Banco de Poupança e Crédito Several megabytes from Banco de Poupança e Crédito, a government-owned, full service bank in Angola. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Angola TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBit FILE SIZE 17 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Several megabytes from Banco de Poupança e Crédito, a government-owned, full service bank in Angola. The data was first released by LockBit under the bank&amp;rsquo;s old name, Banco Comercial de Angola.</description></item><item><title>Bangkok Airways</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bangkok_airways/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bangkok_airways/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Bangkok Airways 140 gigabytes hacked from Bangkok Airways, including airport, employment, and contract information. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Thailand TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBit FILE SIZE 106.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
140 gigabytes hacked from Bangkok Airways, including airport, employment, and contract information.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Bangkok_Airways&amp;amp;oldid=2125&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Corporate Hack Thailand Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Bmk</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bmk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bmk/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
BMK A Saudi financial company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Saudi Arabia TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 30.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A Saudi financial company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Bouygues Construction</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bouygues_construction/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bouygues_construction/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Bouygues Construction 57 gigabytes hacked from Bouygues Construction, which operates in over sixty countries in the sectors of building, civil works and energies and services. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES France TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 57 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
57 gigabytes hacked from Bouygues Construction, which operates in over sixty countries in the sectors of building, civil works and energies and services.</description></item><item><title>Casagrande Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/casagrande_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/casagrande_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Casagrande Group Files hacked from a drilling and foundation equipment manufacturer. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Italy TYPE Hack SOURCE BlackMatter FILE SIZE 10.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Files hacked from a drilling and foundation equipment manufacturer.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)</description></item><item><title>Category:Hack</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/categoryhack/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/categoryhack/</guid><description>Help
From Distributed Denial of Secrets
Releases of hacked datasets.
Subcategories This category has only the following subcategory.
R Ransomware Pages in category &amp;ldquo;Hack&amp;rdquo; The following 200 pages are in this category, out of 215 total.
(previous page) (next page)
A Accent Capital Achinsk City Government Adopt A Trucker founder emails Aerial Surveillance Footage Aerogas Agencia Nacional de Hidrocarburos ALET Aliansce Sonae Alliance Coal AnibalLeaks Apex Mobile Aqaba Company for Ports Operation &amp;amp; Management, Jordan ArianTel Arron Banks Arteris Australia Queensland Azusa Police Department B Banco de Poupança e Crédito Bangkok Airways Blagoveshchensk City Administration BMK Bob Otto emails Bouygues Construction C Capital Legal Services Casagrande Group Cellebrite Mobilogy Cellebrite Team Foundation Server Central Bank of Russia Chamber of Mines of South Africa Chinese Ministry of Commerce Chinga La Migra CitizenGo CitizenGo &amp;amp; HatzeOir databases CityComp Comando Conjunto de las Fuerzas Armadas Comando General de las Fuerzas Militares de Colombia Condie Construction Company Continent Express Convex CorpMSP Cosan Council for National Policy CyberAnakin D Dark Side of the Kremlin Dept of Education of the Strezhevoy City District Administration Dept.</description></item><item><title>Category:Leak Markets</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/categoryleak_markets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/categoryleak_markets/</guid><description>Help
From Distributed Denial of Secrets
Files leaked onto dark web marketplaces as part of attempted or failed sales of data, or which attempted to coerce companies and organizations into paying to prevent the leaking of the data, similar to someransomware leaking models.
Pages in category &amp;ldquo;Leak Markets&amp;rdquo; The following 3 pages are in this category, out of 3 total.
M Municipal Court of Princeton N Newbridge Securities V Virginia Department of Military Affairs Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.</description></item><item><title>Citycomp</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/citycomp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/citycomp/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
CityComp A Dutch IT company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Germany TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 39.4 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES A full copy of the data was not able to be retrieved before the Team Snatch server went down. A Dutch IT company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.</description></item><item><title>Comet Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/comet_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/comet_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Comet Group)]
RELEASE
Groupe Comet 6.9 gigabytes hacked from an industrial recycling firm based in Belgium and operating throughout Europe, Asia and South America. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Belgium TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBIt FILE SIZE 5.4 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
6.9 gigabytes hacked from an industrial recycling firm based in Belgium and operating throughout Europe, Asia and South America.</description></item><item><title>Condie Construction Company</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/condie_construction_company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/condie_construction_company/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Condie Construction Company 57 gigabytes hacked from Condie Construction Company, which specializes in pipeline and infrastructure installation. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 57 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
57 gigabytes hacked from Condie Construction Company, a general engineering construction company specializing in pipeline and infrastructure installation. Their projects have budgets of up to $40 million and include culinary waterlines, sewer lines, pressurized irrigation pipelines, storm drainage, waster water treatment facilities, roadway reconstruction and new roadway construction.</description></item><item><title>Cosan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cosan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cosan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Cosan Over 100 gigabytes of hacked files from Cosan, a Brazilian conglomerate producer of bioethanol, sugar and energy. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil, Argentina, Bolivia, Paraguay, Uruguay TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 105 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 100 gigabytes of hacked files from Cosan, a Brazilian conglomerate producer of bioethanol, sugar and energy. The company operates in Brazil, Argentina, Bolivia, Paraguay, Uruguay.</description></item><item><title>Durham</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/durham/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/durham/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Durham 14 gigabytes (uncompressed) hacked from the Durham region of Canada. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Canada TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 6.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
14 gigabytes (uncompressed) hacked from the Durham region of Canada.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)</description></item><item><title>Dussmann Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dussmann_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dussmann_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Dussmann Group 222 gigabytes hacked from German multi-service provider with subsidiaries focusing on facility management, corporate childcare, nursing and care for the elderly, and business systems solutions, including HVAC, electrical work, and elevators. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES 222 gigabytes hacked from German multi-service provider with subsidiaries focusing on facility management, corporate childcare, nursing and care for the elderly, and business systems solutions, including HVAC, electrical work, and elevators.</description></item><item><title>Ernst &amp; Young</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ernst__young/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ernst__young/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ernst &amp;amp; Young Internal files from the accounting firm Ernst &amp;amp; Young (EY). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 2 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Two terabytes of internal files from the accounting firm Ernst &amp;amp; Young (EY). Ernst &amp;amp; Young primarily provides accounting, tax, consulting and advisory services.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Execupharm</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/execupharm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/execupharm/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
ExecuPharm 200,000 emails and other files from ExecuPharm, a pharmaceutical company that performs outsourced medical trials. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 108.87 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
200,000 emails and other files from ExecuPharm, a pharmaceutical company that performs outsourced medical trials.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=ExecuPharm&amp;amp;oldid=588&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Corporate Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Fisher &amp; Paykel</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fisher__paykel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fisher__paykel/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fisher &amp;amp; Paykel Over 30 gigabytes hacked from Fisher &amp;amp; Paykel, a major appliance manufacturer which is a subsidiary of home appliance manufacturer Haier, based in East Tamaki, New Zealand. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES New Zealand, Italy, United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 31 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 30 gigabytes hacked from Fisher &amp;amp; Paykel, a major appliance manufacturer which is a subsidiary of home appliance manufacturer Haier, based in East Tamaki, New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Groupe Comet</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/groupe_comet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/groupe_comet/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Groupe Comet 6.9 gigabytes hacked from an industrial recycling firm based in Belgium and operating throughout Europe, Asia and South America. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Belgium TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBIt FILE SIZE 5.4 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
6.9 gigabytes hacked from an industrial recycling firm based in Belgium and operating throughout Europe, Asia and South America.</description></item><item><title>Gulf Copper</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gulf_copper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gulf_copper/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Gulf Copper Over 9,000 files from Gulf Copper Energy Services, which serves major and independent offshore drilling rig contractors, offshore oil and gas operating and service companies, national oil companies, major commercial ship operators and the United States government and military. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Conti FILE SIZE 4.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Harita Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/harita_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/harita_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Harita Group Emails from Harita Group, which primarily deals with nickel mining, bauxite mining, coal, ferronickel smelters, alumina refineries, logging, and palm oil plantations. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Indonesia TYPE Hack SOURCE Somos malas&amp;hellip; podemos ser peores FILE SIZE 510 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link REFERENCES Wikipedia EDITOR NOTES
Emails from the Harita Group, which primarily deals with nickel mining, bauxite mining, coal, ferronickel smelters, alumina refineries, logging, and palm oil plantations.</description></item><item><title>Henning Harders</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/henning_harders/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/henning_harders/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Henning Harders 303 gigabytes hacked from Henning Harders, an Australian freight forwarding agent, trade consultancy and licensed customs broker. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Australia TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 303 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
303 gigabytes hacked from Henning Harders, an Australian freight forwarding agent, trade consultancy and licensed customs broker.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Illinois Attorney General</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/illinois_attorney_general/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/illinois_attorney_general/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Illinois Attorney General A cache of files hacked from the Illinois Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s office. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE DoppelPaymer FILE SIZE About 200 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES ThreatPost EDITOR NOTES
A cache of files hacked from the Illinois Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s office by the ransomware crew DoppelPaymer. The total cache is allegedly &amp;ldquo;about 200 GB&amp;rdquo; that will be &amp;ldquo;progressively uploaded.</description></item><item><title>India Bulls</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/india_bulls/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/india_bulls/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
India Bulls Over 130,000 emails and other files from India Bulls, which operates in the financial, real estate, and pharmaceutical sectors along with other industries. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES India TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 39.35 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 130,000 emails and other files from India Bulls, which operates in the financial, real estate, and pharmaceutical sectors along with other industries.</description></item><item><title>J.Irwin Company</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/j.irwin_company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/j.irwin_company/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
J. Irwin Company 300 megabytes from J. Irwin Company, which installs pipeline and constructs processing plants, compressor stations and other facilities for gas, oil and water transportation. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Xing FILE SIZE 309 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
300 megabytes from J. Irwin Company, which installs pipelines and constructs processing plants, compressor stations and other facilities for gas, oil and water transportation.</description></item><item><title>Jones Day</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jones_day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jones_day/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Jones Day Data hacked from the high profile Jones Day law firm, including data associated with the city of Chicago and Chicago PD, as well as data associated with the credit reporting agency Experian. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 85 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES VICE EDITOR NOTES
Data hacked from the high profile Jones Day lawfirm, including data associated with the city of Chicago and Chicago PD, as well as data associated with the credit reporting agency Experian.</description></item><item><title>Kcsa Strategic Communications</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/kcsa_strategic_communications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/kcsa_strategic_communications/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
KCSA Strategic Communications A public relations firm based in Boston, MA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 152.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A public relations firm based in Boston, MA breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Linestar</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/linestar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/linestar/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
LineStar 37 gigabytes hacked from the integrated pipeline compliance, technology and integrity maintenance company LineStar, along with 73,500 emails. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Xing FILE SIZE 37 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Wired EDITOR NOTES
37 gigabytes hacked from the integrated pipeline compliance, technology and integrity maintenance company LineStar.
Contents [1] [Redactions] [2] [Emails] Redactions For usability and to reduce the potential for abuse, approximately 19 gigabytes of .</description></item><item><title>Mas Holdings</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mas_holdings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mas_holdings/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MAS Holdings 29 gigabytes of hacked files from MAS Holdings, South Asia&amp;rsquo;s largest manufacturer of lingerie and one of Sri Lanka&amp;rsquo;s largest apparel manufacturers. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Sri Lanka TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 29 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
29 gigabytes of hacked files from MAS Holdings, South Asia&amp;rsquo;s largest manufacturer of lingerie and one of Sri Lanka&amp;rsquo;s largest apparel manufacturers.</description></item><item><title>Medical Diagnostics Laboratories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/medical_diagnostics_laboratories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/medical_diagnostics_laboratories/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Medical Diagnostics Laboratories 83 gigabytes of data hacked from Medical Diagnostics Laboratories, which performs outsourced medical testing in addition to Research and Development (R&amp;amp;D). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 83 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
83 gigabytes of data hacked from Medical Diagnostics Laboratories, which performs outsourced medical testing in addition to Research and Development (R&amp;amp;D).</description></item><item><title>Metropolitan Police Department D.C.</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/metropolitan_police_department_d.c./</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/metropolitan_police_department_d.c./</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Mk Brokers</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mk_brokers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mk_brokers/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MK Brokers 23 gigabytes hacked from the Bulgarian investment firm MK Brokers, including nearly 150,000 files. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Bulgaria TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBit FILE SIZE 8.15 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
23 gigabytes hacked from the Bulgarian investment firm MK Brokers, including nearly 150,000 files.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=MK_Brokers&amp;amp;oldid=2194&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box Bulgaria Corporate Hack Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Mvtec</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mvtec/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mvtec/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MVTEC Source code for Artificial Intelligence and Deep Learning software. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 339.89 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Source code for Artificial Intelligence and Deep Learning software used in robotics, medical imaging, inspection, manufacturing and production, surveillance, research and more.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=MVTEC&amp;amp;oldid=2196&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Corporate Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Myatt Blume &amp; Osburn</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myatt_blume__osburn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myatt_blume__osburn/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Myatt Blume &amp;amp; Osburn A Texas accounting firm with corporate and government clients. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 27.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A Texas accounting firm with corporate and government clients breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Myattcpa</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myattcpa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myattcpa/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Myattcpa)]
RELEASE
Myatt Blume &amp;amp; Osburn A Texas accounting firm with corporate and government clients. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 27.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A Texas accounting firm with corporate and government clients breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Netzsch</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/netzsch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/netzsch/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Netzsch Over 375,000 files from machinery manufacturer Netzsch. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 411.31 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 375,000 files from machinery manufacturer Netzsch, which earns approximately $1 billion (USD) annually according to some sources, and half a billion (USD) according to others.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Netzsch&amp;amp;oldid=589&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Corporate Ransomware</description></item><item><title>North American Roofing</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/north_american_roofing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/north_american_roofing/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
North American Roofing 83 gigabytes hacked from the &amp;ldquo;most trusted and respected commercial roofing company in the U.S.&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 83 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
83 gigabytes hacked from the &amp;ldquo;most trusted and respected commercial roofing company in the U.S.&amp;rdquo; The company not only boasts about the quality of its work and its community involvement, but about its sustainability program and green initiative.</description></item><item><title>Nusantara Regas</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/nusantara_regas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/nusantara_regas/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Nusantara Regas A gigabyte of files hacked from the natural gas company Nusantara Regas. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Indonesia TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBit FILE SIZE 724 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A gigabyte of files hacked from the natural gas company Nusantara Regas.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Nusantara_Regas&amp;amp;oldid=2205&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Corporate Environmental Hack Indonesia Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Oakland City Hall</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oakland_city_hall/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oakland_city_hall/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Oakland City Hall Internal documents from Oakland City Hall. The data includes policy documents, misconduct records and bank statements. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE PLAY FILE SIZE 11.7 GB and 600 GB How to Request Access MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Internal emails and files from Oakland City Hall, a mid-sized city in the San Francisco Bay area with a long history of human rights violations.</description></item><item><title>Parkland</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/parkland/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/parkland/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Parkland Nearly 750 gigabytes (uncompressed) hacked from one of Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest gas station and convenience store chains. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Canada TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 499 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 750 gigabytes (uncompressed) hacked from one of Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest gas station and convenience store chains.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Perceptics</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/perceptics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/perceptics/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Perceptics Hacked data from the Automated License Plate Reader (surveillance) company. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 449 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Intercept EDITOR NOTES
Hacked data from the Automated License Plate Reader (surveillance) company. The data was breached by Boris The Blade AKA Team Snatch, and includes emails and data the company downloaded from U.</description></item><item><title>Petrolimex</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/petrolimex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/petrolimex/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Petrolimex 52 gigabytes from the Vietnam National Petroleum Group, which makes up 50% of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s petroleum market and is active in the fields of engineering, installation, mechanical and oil equipment DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Vietnam TYPE Hack SOURCE BlackByte FILE SIZE 52 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
52 gigabytes from the Vietnam National Petroleum Group, which makes up 50% of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s petroleum market and is active in the fields of engineering, installation, mechanical and oil equipment.</description></item><item><title>Planatol</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/planatol/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/planatol/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Planatol Emails, documents and databases from industrial manufacturer Planatol. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 47.24 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Emails, documents and databases from industrial manufacturer Planatol.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Planatol&amp;amp;oldid=2216&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Corporate Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Presque Isle Police Department</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/presque_isle_police_department/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/presque_isle_police_department/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Presque Isle Police Department Nearly 200 gigabytes of data hacked from Presque Isle Police Department. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Avaddon FILE SIZE 195 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 200 gigabytes of data hacked from Presque Isle Police Department, including over 15,000 emails. About 10% of the cache is the department&amp;rsquo;s music collection.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Pricewaterhousecoopers</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pricewaterhousecoopers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pricewaterhousecoopers/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from PricewaterhouseCoopers)]
RELEASE
PWC Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Procuradoria Geral Da Fazenda Nacional</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/procuradoria-geral_da_fazenda_nacional/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/procuradoria-geral_da_fazenda_nacional/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Henning Harders 3.1 gigabytes hacked from Brazil&amp;rsquo;s Procuradoria Geral da Fazenda Nacional. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Everest FILE SIZE 3.1 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
3.1 gigabytes hacked from Brazil&amp;rsquo;s Procuradoria Geral da Fazenda Nacional.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Procuradoria-Geral_da_Fazenda_Nacional&amp;amp;oldid=2222&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Brazil Hack Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Pwc</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pwc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pwc/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
PWC Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Saltos Del Francoli</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/saltos_del_francoli/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/saltos_del_francoli/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Saltos del Francoli 3.8 gigabytes hacked from the Panamanian hydroelectric company Saltos del Francolí, S.A. (SDF Energy Group), involved in the Los Planetas project. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Panama TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBit FILE SIZE 2.48 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
3.8 gigabytes hacked from the Panamanian hydroelectric company Saltos del Francolí, S.A. (SDF Energy Group), involved in the Los Planetas project.</description></item><item><title>Shell</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/shell/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/shell/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Shell Over 100 gigabytes hacked from the Shell global group of energy and petrochemical companies. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 104 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 100 gigabytes hacked from the Shell global group of energy and petrochemical companies.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Shell&amp;amp;oldid=2235&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Corporate Environmental Hack Ransomware United States of America</description></item><item><title>Special:Mostlinkedcategories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialmostlinkedcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialmostlinkedcategories/</guid><description>Showing below up to 50 results in range #1 to #50.
View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Hack‏‎ (216 members) Corporate‏‎ (136 members) Anonymous‏‎ (86 members) Limited Distribution‏‎ (84 members) United States of America‏‎ (72 members) Russia‏‎ (65 members) Cyberwar‏‎ (54 members) Ransomware‏‎ (53 members) Environmental‏‎ (41 members) Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box‏‎ (25 members) Leak‏‎ (24 members) Organization‏‎ (24 members) Fascist‏‎ (23 members) Allegations of State Sponsorship‏‎ (22 members) Brazil‏‎ (11 members) Researchers‏‎ (10 members) Ukraine‏‎ (8 members) Extractivist Leaks‏‎ (7 members) Fuerzas Represivas‏‎ (7 members) Italy‏‎ (6 members) Chile‏‎ (6 members) Scrape‏‎ (6 members) Colombia‏‎ (6 members) Germany‏‎ (5 members) Australia‏‎ (4 members) Iran‏‎ (4 members) Argentina‏‎ (4 members) United Kingdom‏‎ (4 members) Myanmar‏‎ (4 members) Indonesia‏‎ (4 members) Canada‏‎ (4 members) Thailand‏‎ (3 members) Syria‏‎ (3 members) Turkey‏‎ (3 members) France‏‎ (3 members) Paraguay‏‎ (3 members) Peru‏‎ (3 members) Leak Markets‏‎ (3 members) El Salvador‏‎ (3 members) Ecuador‏‎ (3 members) China‏‎ (2 members) European Union‏‎ (2 members) Azerbaijan‏‎ (2 members) Panama‏‎ (2 members) Venezuela‏‎ (2 members) Belarus‏‎ (2 members) Guatemala‏‎ (2 members) MilicoLeaks‏‎ (2 members) Angola‏‎ (1 member) Bulgaria‏‎ (1 member) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Thsa</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thsa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thsa/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
THSA TH Company (THSA), an industrial solutions company. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 37.2 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
TH Company (THSA), an industrial solutions company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)</description></item><item><title>Toll Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/toll_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/toll_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Toll Group 84 gigabytes hacked from an Australian transportation and logistics company with operations in road, rail, sea, air and warehousing. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 150 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
150 gigabytes hacked from an Australian transportation and logistics company with operations in road, rail, sea, air and warehousing. A subsidiary of Japan Post Holdings, the company has three divisions; Global Express, Global Forwarding, and Global Logistics.</description></item><item><title>Trust Capital Funding</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/trust_capital_funding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/trust_capital_funding/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Trust Capital Funding Over 230 gigabytes from the financing company Trust Capital Funding, which provides funding for commercial real estate, franchise startups and businesses as well as merchant processing and other banking products. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE BlackMatter FILE SIZE 233 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 230 gigabytes from the financing company Trust Capital Funding, which provides funding for commercial real estate, franchise startups and businesses as well as merchant processing and other banking products.</description></item><item><title>W.L. Contractors</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/w.l._contractors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/w.l._contractors/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
W.L. Contractors 15 gigabytes hacked from a Colorado based traffic signal, Intelligent Transportation Systems, and CCTV contractor. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 15 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
15 gigabytes hacked from a based traffic signal, ITS (Intelligent Transportation Systems), and CCTV contractor operating throughout Colorado and Wyoming.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>W&amp;T Offshore</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/wt_offshore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/wt_offshore/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
W&amp;amp;T Offshore 19 gigabytes hacked from W&amp;amp;T Offshore, an independent oil and natural gas producer, exploring, developing, and acquiring oil and natural gas in the Gulf of Mexico. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 19 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
19 gigabytes hacked from W&amp;amp;T Offshore, an independent oil and natural gas producer, exploring, developing, and acquiring oil and natural gas in the Gulf of Mexico.</description></item><item><title>Washington County Sheriff</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_county_sheriff/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_county_sheriff/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Washington County Sheriff 1,311 files hacked from the Washington County Sheriff by ransomware operator Conti. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Conti FILE SIZE 419 MB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
1,311 files hacked from the Washington County Sheriff by ransomware operator Conti.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Washington D.C. Metropolitan Pd</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Washington D.C. Metropolitan PD)]
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Washington D.C. Metropolitan Pd</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Washington D.C. Metropolitan PD)]
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>29 Leaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/29-leaks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/29-leaks/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.
Background Formations House, now The London Office, facilitates international money laundering by taking advantage of the lax regulatory framework of the United Kingdom and many of its former colonies.
Journalist Oliver Bullough first wrote about Formations House in the Guardian in 2016, then in his book Moneyland: The Inside Story of the Crooks and Kleptocrats Who Rule the World.</description></item><item><title>Blueleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/blueleaks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/blueleaks/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.</description></item><item><title>Prime Minister of Iraq's Office</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pm-of-iraq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pm-of-iraq/</guid><description>2,500 emails from the Prime Minister of Iraq&amp;rsquo;s office sent between March 2021 and April 2022. The emails document the daily business of the office while Mustafa Al-Kadhimi (مصطفى عبد اللطيف مشتت) held it.</description></item><item><title>Aqaba Company for Ports Operation &amp; Management, Jordan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/aqaba-company/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/aqaba-company/</guid><description>Over 50,000 emails from Jordan Aqaba Company for Ports Operation &amp;amp; Management, sent mostly between November 2019 and April 2022.
In 2004, the state-run Aqaba Development Corporation (ADC) acquired and took over the management and operation of the port on behalf of the Aqaba Special Economic Zone Authority (ASEZA). Management of the port is handled by the ADC&amp;rsquo;s Aqaba Company for Ports Operation and Management.</description></item><item><title>LetMeSpy</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/letmespy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/letmespy/</guid><description>Tens of thousands of database entries containing customer information, messages, call, GPS and other logs from devices compromised by the LetMeSpy stalkerware.
Research LetMeSpy, a phone tracking app spying on thousands, says it was hacked (TechCrunch)
Miscreants leak texts and info siphoned by Android stalkerware app LetMeSpy (The Register)
LetMeSpy data leak reveals users of digital stalking software (The Daily Dot)
#FuckStalkerware pt. 1 - the LetMeSpy hack (maia arson crimew)</description></item><item><title>PWC</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pwc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pwc/</guid><description>Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Sherwood</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/sherwood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/sherwood/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.</description></item></channel></rss>