<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hack on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://example.org/categories/hack/</link><description>Recent content in hack on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.org/categories/hack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>29 Leaks</title><link>https://example.org/releases/29-leaks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/releases/29-leaks/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.</description></item><item><title>Blueleaks</title><link>https://example.org/releases/blueleaks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/releases/blueleaks/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.</description></item><item><title>National Police of Paraguay</title><link>https://example.org/releases/national-police-of-paraguay/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/releases/national-police-of-paraguay/</guid><description>Over 500,000 internal documents and images from the National Police of Paraguay (Policía Nacional del Paraguay), and 175 gigabytes of SQL databases.
The data includes documents from the Internal Affairs Directorate (Dirección de Asuntos Internos), the Identification Department (Departamento de Identificaciones) and the Foreigners Registry Department (Departamento Registro de Extranjeros), Technology and Development Division (Division de Tecnologia y Desarrollo), as well as other documents including orders from command, photographs of evidence and documents about wanted individuals.</description></item><item><title>Prime Minister of Iraq's Office</title><link>https://example.org/releases/pm-of-iraq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/releases/pm-of-iraq/</guid><description>2,500 emails from the Prime Minister of Iraq&amp;rsquo;s office sent between March 2021 and April 2022. The emails document the daily business of the office while Mustafa Al-Kadhimi (مصطفى عبد اللطيف مشتت) held it.</description></item><item><title>Aqaba Company for Ports Operation &amp; Management, Jordan</title><link>https://example.org/releases/aqaba-company/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/releases/aqaba-company/</guid><description>Over 50,000 emails from Jordan Aqaba Company for Ports Operation &amp;amp; Management, sent mostly between November 2019 and April 2022.
In 2004, the state-run Aqaba Development Corporation (ADC) acquired and took over the management and operation of the port on behalf of the Aqaba Special Economic Zone Authority (ASEZA). Management of the port is handled by the ADC&amp;rsquo;s Aqaba Company for Ports Operation and Management.</description></item><item><title>LetMeSpy</title><link>https://example.org/releases/letmespy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/releases/letmespy/</guid><description>Tens of thousands of database entries containing customer information, messages, call, GPS and other logs from devices compromised by the LetMeSpy stalkerware.
Research LetMeSpy, a phone tracking app spying on thousands, says it was hacked (TechCrunch)
Miscreants leak texts and info siphoned by Android stalkerware app LetMeSpy (The Register)
LetMeSpy data leak reveals users of digital stalking software (The Daily Dot)
#FuckStalkerware pt. 1 - the LetMeSpy hack (maia arson crimew)</description></item><item><title>PWC</title><link>https://example.org/releases/pwc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/releases/pwc/</guid><description>Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Sherwood</title><link>https://example.org/releases/sherwood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.org/releases/sherwood/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.</description></item></channel></rss>