<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hack on DDoSecrets Wiki</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/hack/</link><description>Recent content in hack on DDoSecrets Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/hack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accent Capital</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/accent_capital/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/accent_capital/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Accent Capital 365,000 emails from Accent Capital, a commercial real-estate investment firm. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 211 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
365,000 emails from Accent Capital, a commercial real-estate investment firm. In contrast with many other real-estate investment firms, Accent Capital owns or is directly involved with the management of many of the properties its clients invest in.</description></item><item><title>Achinsk City Government</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/achinsk_city_government/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/achinsk_city_government/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Achinsk City Government Over 7,000 emails from the Achinsk city government. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 8.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 7,000 emails from the Achinsk city government.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Adopt A Trucker Founder Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/adopt_a_trucker_founder_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/adopt_a_trucker_founder_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE 250 MB of emails and attachments from the Adopt A Trucker campaign founder, Chris Garrah. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Canada TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 250 MB MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
250 MB of emails and attachments from the Protonmail account of Adopt A Trucker campaign founder, Chris Garrah. The emails run from February 7th through the morning of February 21st.
The source noted that while they were able to remove some malware from the original inbox, it is possible that some was missed.</description></item><item><title>Aerial Surveillance Footage</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aerial_surveillance_footage/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aerial_surveillance_footage/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Aerial Surveillance Footage Over 600 hours of aerial surveillance footage taken by police helicopters in and around Dallas, TX and Atlanta, GA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 1.9 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link
Over 600 hours of aerial surveillance footage taken by police helicopters in and around Dallas, TX and Atlanta, GA.
The extensive footage reveals the capabilities of the &amp;ldquo;military-grade&amp;rdquo; technology behind police surveillance.</description></item><item><title>Aerogas</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aerogas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aerogas/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Aerogas Approximately 100,000 emails from Aerogas, an engineering company which specializes in the oil and gas industry. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 145 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 100,000 emails from Aerogas, an engineering company which specializes in the oil and gas industry. Aerogas&amp;rsquo; clients include Rosneft, NOVATEK, Volgagaz, Purneft and others.</description></item><item><title>Agencia Nacional De Hidrocarburos</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/agencia_nacional_de_hidrocarburos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/agencia_nacional_de_hidrocarburos/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Agencia Nacional de Hidrocarburos (ANH) Hacked emails from the Agencia Nacional de Hidrocarburos, which is responsible for administering the country&amp;rsquo;s hydrocarbon resources, including issuing drilling and mining permits. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Colombia TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 62 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Hacked emails from the Agencia Nacional de Hidrocarburos (ANH), which is responsible for administering the country&amp;rsquo;s hydrocarbon resources, including issuing drilling and mining permits.</description></item><item><title>Aliansce Sonae</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aliansce_sonae/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aliansce_sonae/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Aliansce Sonae 31 GB hacked of hacked files from Aliansce Sonae Shopping Centers SA, a Brazil-based company principally engaged in the development and operating of shopping centers in Brazil. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 31 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
31 GB hacked of hacked files from Aliansce Sonae Shopping Centers SA, formerly known as Sonae Sierra Brasil SA, a Brazil-based company principally engaged in the development and operating of shopping centers in Brazil.</description></item><item><title>Alliance Coal</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/alliance_coal/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/alliance_coal/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Alliance Coal 42 GB of files hacked from the second largest coal producer in the Eastern U.S., including over 180,000 emails. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Vice FILE SIZE 42 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
42 GB of files hacked from the second largest coal producer in the Eastern U.S., including over 180,000 emails.</description></item><item><title>Aniballeaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aniballeaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aniballeaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
AnibalLeaks A hacked database of Argentine military personnel. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Argentina TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 40 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A hacked database of Argentine military personnel.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.</description></item><item><title>Apex Mobile</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/apex_mobile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/apex_mobile/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Apex Mobile 25 GB from Apex Mobile, a set of apps used by &amp;ldquo;over 150 civic, law enforcement and fire agencies across the US and Canada&amp;rdquo; for reporting and collecting information. The data includes over 36,000 reports, 18,000 images, and at least 15,000 messages. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 25 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Aqaba Company For Ports Operation &amp; Management, Jordan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aqaba_company_for_ports_operation__management_jordan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aqaba_company_for_ports_operation__management_jordan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Aqaba Company for Ports Operation &amp;amp; Management, Jordan Over 50,000 emails from Jordan&amp;rsquo;s ports management company DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Jordan TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 27.8 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link
EDITOR NOTES
Over 50,000 emails from Jordan Aqaba Company for Ports Operation &amp;amp; Management, sent mostly between November 2019 and April 2022.
In 2004, the state-run Aqaba Development Corporation (ADC) acquired and took over the management and operation of the port on behalf of the Aqaba Special Economic Zone Authority (ASEZA).</description></item><item><title>Ariantel</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ariantel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ariantel/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
ArianTel 320,000 emails from ArianTel, an Iranian telecom company documenting Iranian surveillance systems and the SIAM system. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Iran TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 44 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [[[Link]]] TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Intercept EDITOR NOTES
320,000 emails from ArianTel, an Iranian telecom company documenting Iranian surveillance systems and the SIAM system.
Research How Iran can track and control protestor&amp;rsquo;s phones (The Intercept)</description></item><item><title>Arron Banks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/arron_banks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/arron_banks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Arron Banks Hacked messages from a leading proponent for Brexit. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Britain TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 2.45 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Hacked messages from a leading proponent for Brexit.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Arron_Banks&amp;amp;oldid=2122&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Fascist United Kingdom</description></item><item><title>Arteris</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/arteris/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/arteris/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Arteris Over 60 gigabytes hacked from Arteris, which is responsible for the restoration, modernization, monitoring, maintenance, and operation of more than 3,250 km of Brazilian highways. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 61 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 60 gigabytes hacked from Arteris, which is responsible for the restoration, modernization, monitoring, maintenance, and operation of more than 3,250 km of Brazilian highways.</description></item><item><title>Australia Queensland</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/australia_queensland/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/australia_queensland/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Australia Queensland Miscellaneous Australia materials hacked and released by Anonymous. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Australia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 82 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Miscellaneous Australia materials hacked and released by Anonymous.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Australia_Queensland&amp;amp;oldid=1133&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Australia Hack Anonymous</description></item><item><title>Azusa Police Department</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/azusa_police_department/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/azusa_police_department/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Azusa Police Department Approximately 3.5 gigabytes (uncompressed) of data hacked from the police department in Azusa, CA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE DoppelPaymer FILE SIZE 2.85 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 3.5 gigabytes (uncompressed) of data hacked from the police department in Azusa, CA by DoppelPaymer. The dataset includes 3 gigabytes of case files, 100 megabytes of forms and training materials from their jail, payroll information for 2018-2021, shift assignments for 2016-2021 and 100 megabytes of miscellaneous information.</description></item><item><title>Banco De PoupançA E CréDito</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/banco_de_poupan%C3%A7a_e_cr%C3%A9dito/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/banco_de_poupan%C3%A7a_e_cr%C3%A9dito/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Banco de Poupança e Crédito Several megabytes from Banco de Poupança e Crédito, a government-owned, full service bank in Angola. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Angola TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBit FILE SIZE 17 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Several megabytes from Banco de Poupança e Crédito, a government-owned, full service bank in Angola. The data was first released by LockBit under the bank&amp;rsquo;s old name, Banco Comercial de Angola.</description></item><item><title>Bangkok Airways</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bangkok_airways/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bangkok_airways/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Bangkok Airways 140 gigabytes hacked from Bangkok Airways, including airport, employment, and contract information. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Thailand TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBit FILE SIZE 106.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
140 gigabytes hacked from Bangkok Airways, including airport, employment, and contract information.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Bangkok_Airways&amp;amp;oldid=2125&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Corporate Hack Thailand Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Blagoveshchensk City Administration</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/blagoveshchensk_city_administration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/blagoveshchensk_city_administration/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Blagoveshchensk City Administration / Благове́щенск 230,000 emails from the Blagoveshchensk City Administration / Благове́щенск from 2019 through 2022. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 150 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
230,000 emails from the Blagoveshchensk City Administration / Благове́щенск from 2019 through 2022.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Bmk</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bmk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bmk/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
BMK A Saudi financial company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Saudi Arabia TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 30.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A Saudi financial company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Bob Otto Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bob_otto_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bob_otto_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Bob Otto emails Hacked emails from senior State Department official Robert Otto. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 635 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Hacked emails from senior State Department official Robert Otto.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Bob_Otto_emails&amp;amp;oldid=2127&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
United States of America Hack</description></item><item><title>Bouygues Construction</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bouygues_construction/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bouygues_construction/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Bouygues Construction 57 gigabytes hacked from Bouygues Construction, which operates in over sixty countries in the sectors of building, civil works and energies and services. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES France TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 57 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
57 gigabytes hacked from Bouygues Construction, which operates in over sixty countries in the sectors of building, civil works and energies and services.</description></item><item><title>Capital Legal Services</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/capital_legal_services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/capital_legal_services/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Capital Legal Services Approximately 200,000 emails hacked from the Russian law firm Capital Legal Services, which practices law in a variety of areas. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 65 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 200,000 emails hacked from the Russian law firm Capital Legal Services, which practices law in a variety of areas.</description></item><item><title>Casagrande Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/casagrande_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/casagrande_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Casagrande Group Files hacked from a drilling and foundation equipment manufacturer. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Italy TYPE Hack SOURCE BlackMatter FILE SIZE 10.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Files hacked from a drilling and foundation equipment manufacturer.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)</description></item><item><title>Category:Ransomware</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/categoryransomware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/categoryransomware/</guid><description>Help
From Distributed Denial of Secrets
Ransomware is a new category of data leak that we can&amp;rsquo;t ignore. Several ransomware crews have begun releasing data which they hacked and published on their own leak sites. Early in our lifecycle, we published Perceptics in our index, and are aware of the public interest of that data set, which came from a ransomware origin. Since then, we have seen other public interest datasets in the ransomware category, and want to be upfront about the nature of the sources in republishing this data.</description></item><item><title>Cayman National Bank And Trust</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cayman_national_bank_and_trust/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cayman_national_bank_and_trust/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Cayman National Bank and Trust)]
RELEASE
Sherwood Copies of the servers of the Cayman National Bank and Trust (Isle of Man). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Cayman Islands TYPE Hack SOURCE Phineas Fisher FILE SIZE 2.26 TB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Unicorn Riot EDITOR NOTES
Copies of the servers of the Cayman National Bank and Trust (Isle of Man) via the hacktivist sometimes known as Phineas Fisher.</description></item><item><title>Cellebrite Mobilogy</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cellebrite_mobilogy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cellebrite_mobilogy/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Cellebrite Mobilogy 3.6 TB of backend data from Cellebrite Mobilogy, previously Cellebrite&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Lifecycle Division. Mobilogy software can be used for device diagnostics, content transfer, backup and restorations. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 3.6 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
3.6 TB of backend data from Cellebrite Mobilogy, previously Cellebrite&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Lifecycle Division. Mobilogy software can be used for device diagnostics, content transfer, backup and restorations.</description></item><item><title>Cellebrite Team Foundation Server</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cellebrite_team_foundation_server/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cellebrite_team_foundation_server/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Cellebrite Team Foundation Server Backup files for Cellebrite&amp;rsquo;s Team Foundation Server, a collaboration environment that&amp;rsquo;s since been replaced by the Azure DevOps Server. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 430 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Backup files for Cellebrite&amp;rsquo;s Team Foundation Server, a collaboration environment that&amp;rsquo;s since been replaced by the Azure DevOps Server.
Limited Distribution Due to the potential for abuse, this data is only being made available to journalists and researchers at this time.</description></item><item><title>Central Bank Of Russia</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/central_bank_of_russia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/central_bank_of_russia/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Central Bank of Russia Thousands of files allegedly hacked from the Central Bank of Russia by Thblckrbbtworld, who claims affiliation with Anonymous. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 22.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of files allegedly hacked from the Central Bank of Russia by Thblckrbbtworld, who claims affiliation with Anonymous.</description></item><item><title>Chamber Of Mines (South Africa)</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chamber_of_mines_south_africa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chamber_of_mines_south_africa/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Chamber of Mines (South Africa))]
A small hack of files from the Chamber of Mines of South Africa, previously released by Anonymous and Par:AnoIA.
RELEASE
Chamber of Mines of South Africa A small hack of files from the Chamber of Mines of South Africa, previously released by Anonymous and Par:AnoIA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY South Africa TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 16.7 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Chamber Of Mines Of South Africa</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chamber_of_mines_of_south_africa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chamber_of_mines_of_south_africa/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
A small hack of files from the Chamber of Mines of South Africa, previously released by Anonymous and Par:AnoIA.
RELEASE
Chamber of Mines of South Africa A small hack of files from the Chamber of Mines of South Africa, previously released by Anonymous and Par:AnoIA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY South Africa TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 16.7 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Chinese Ministry Of Commerce</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chinese_ministry_of_commerce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chinese_ministry_of_commerce/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
Documents released through Par:AnoIA, allegedly containing details about deals with Russia, Ukraine and Belarus. The documents are partly in English, Russian and Chinese. One document, obtained from the Chinese foreign office in Minsk indicates relations between the notorious Russian mob boss Marat Balagula and high ranking Ukrainian politicians.
RELEASE
Chinese Ministry of Commerce Documents released through Par:AnoIA, allegedly containing details about deals with Russia, Ukraine and Belarus.</description></item><item><title>Chinga La Migra</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chinga_la_migra/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/chinga_la_migra/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Chinga La Migra A series of hacks against Arizona and Texas law enforcement by Anonymous-affiliated group LulzSec/AntiSec. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE LulzSec/AntiSec FILE SIZE DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link MAGNET (II) Link MAGNET (III) Link MAGNET (IV) Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A series of hacks against Arizona and Texas law enforcement by Anonymous-affiliated group LulzSec/AntiSec.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Chinga_La_Migra&amp;amp;oldid=2137&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Citizengo</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/citizengo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/citizengo/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
CitizenGo Over 17,000 documents hacked from right wing campaigning organizations Grupo CitizenGO &amp;amp; HazteOir hacked by ACABGang. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE ACABGang FILE SIZE 24 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES These files are the unredacted version of WikiLeaks&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Intolerance Network&amp;rdquo;. See also CitizenGo &amp;amp; HatzeOir databases Over 17,000 documents from right wing campaigning organizations Grupo CitizenGO &amp;amp; HazteOir hacked by ACABGang.</description></item><item><title>Citizengo &amp; Hatzeoir Databases</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/citizengo__hatzeoir_databases/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/citizengo__hatzeoir_databases/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
CitizenGo &amp;amp; HatzeOir databases Database and site dumps from right wing campaigning organizations Grupo CitizenGO &amp;amp; HazteOir hacked by ACABGang in 2017. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE ACABGang FILE SIZE 22 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES These files are the lost portion of the CitizenGo release and WikiLeaks&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Intolerance Network&amp;rdquo;. Database and site dumps from right wing campaigning organizations Grupo CitizenGO &amp;amp; HazteOir hacked by ACABGang in 2017.</description></item><item><title>Citycomp</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/citycomp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/citycomp/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
CityComp A Dutch IT company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Germany TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 39.4 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES A full copy of the data was not able to be retrieved before the Team Snatch server went down. A Dutch IT company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.</description></item><item><title>Comando Conjunto De Las Fuerzas Armadas</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/comando_conjunto_de_las_fuerzas_armadas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/comando_conjunto_de_las_fuerzas_armadas/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Comando Conjunto de las Fuerzas Armadas Over 100,000 emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Comando Conjunto de las Fuerzas Armadas del Perú (Joint Command of the Armed Forces of Peru). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Peru TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 63 GB DOWNLOAD: Request Access REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Over 100,000 emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Comando Conjunto de las Fuerzas Armadas del Perú (Joint Command of the Armed Forces of Peru).</description></item><item><title>Comando General De Las Fuerzas Militares De Colombia</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/comando_general_de_las_fuerzas_militares_de_colombia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/comando_general_de_las_fuerzas_militares_de_colombia/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Comando General de las Fuerzas Militares de Colombia Over 300,000 emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Comando General de las Fuerzas Militares de Colombia (General Command of the Military Forces of Colombia). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Colombia TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 420 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Over 300,000 emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Comando General de las Fuerzas Militares de Colombia (General Command of the Military Forces of Colombia).</description></item><item><title>Comet Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/comet_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/comet_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Comet Group)]
RELEASE
Groupe Comet 6.9 gigabytes hacked from an industrial recycling firm based in Belgium and operating throughout Europe, Asia and South America. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Belgium TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBIt FILE SIZE 5.4 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
6.9 gigabytes hacked from an industrial recycling firm based in Belgium and operating throughout Europe, Asia and South America.</description></item><item><title>Condie Construction Company</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/condie_construction_company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/condie_construction_company/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Condie Construction Company 57 gigabytes hacked from Condie Construction Company, which specializes in pipeline and infrastructure installation. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 57 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
57 gigabytes hacked from Condie Construction Company, a general engineering construction company specializing in pipeline and infrastructure installation. Their projects have budgets of up to $40 million and include culinary waterlines, sewer lines, pressurized irrigation pipelines, storm drainage, waster water treatment facilities, roadway reconstruction and new roadway construction.</description></item><item><title>Continent Express</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/continent_express/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/continent_express/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Continent Express Nearly 400 GB of files and databases from Continent Express, a Russian travel agency. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE NB65 FILE SIZE 399 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 400 GB of files and databases from Continent Express, a Russian travel agency.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Convex</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/convex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/convex/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Convex 120 gigabytes from the Russian internet provider Convex, revealing pervasive Russian surveillance of internet and phone activities, including the previously unknown Green Atom surveillance program. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE CAXXII FILE SIZE 128 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [Link] TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES KyivPost, Library of Congress EDITOR NOTES The data was originally released by the hackers independently.</description></item><item><title>Corpmsp</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/corpmsp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/corpmsp/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | CorpMSP | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Over 480 GB and 75,000 files, | | | emails and disk images from | | | CorpMSP, a federal institution | | | providing support to small and | | | medium-sized businesses. The | | | controlling shareholder of | | | CorpMSP is the Russian | | | Federation.</description></item><item><title>Cosan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cosan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cosan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Cosan Over 100 gigabytes of hacked files from Cosan, a Brazilian conglomerate producer of bioethanol, sugar and energy. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil, Argentina, Bolivia, Paraguay, Uruguay TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 105 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 100 gigabytes of hacked files from Cosan, a Brazilian conglomerate producer of bioethanol, sugar and energy. The company operates in Brazil, Argentina, Bolivia, Paraguay, Uruguay.</description></item><item><title>Council For National Policy</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/council_for_national_policy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/council_for_national_policy/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Council for National Policy An unredacted copy of the highly restricted September 2020 membership directory for the Council for National Policy, an umbrella organization and networking group for conservative and Republican activists in the United States. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 3.9 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES New York Times, The Nation EDITOR NOTES A redacted version from 2014 was previously published by the Southern Poverty Law Center and a redacted version of the 2020 list is available here.</description></item><item><title>Cyberanakin</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cyberanakin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cyberanakin/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
Files from a revenge hacking spree against Russian entities allegedly in response to the MH17 downing.
RELEASE
CyberAnakin Files from a revenge hacking spree against Russian entities allegedly in response to the MH17 downing. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE CyberAnakin FILE SIZE 2.1 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES VICE EDITOR NOTES Limited Distribution Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=CyberAnakin&amp;amp;oldid=1139&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Limited Distribution Russia</description></item><item><title>Dark Side Of The Kremlin</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dark_side_of_the_kremlin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dark_side_of_the_kremlin/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
Hundreds of thousands of documents and emails from Russian journalists, bankers, oligarchs, nationalists and terrorists.
RELEASE
Dark Side of the Kremlin Hundreds of thousands of documents and emails from Russian journalists, bankers, oligarchs, nationalists and terrorists. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Various (including Ukrainian Cyber Alliance and CyberHunta) FILE SIZE 108 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link IPFS CID QmbHFPMqykf4ArUrSdMTUAimqqKkPqajdaRDdpdVDTuk78 MORE REFERENCES The Daily Beast, New York Times EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Dept Of Education Of The Strezhevoy City District Administration</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dept_of_education_of_the_strezhevoy_city_district_administration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dept_of_education_of_the_strezhevoy_city_district_administration/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Dept of Education of the Strezhevoy City District Administration 250,000 emails from the Deptartment of Education of the Strezhevoy (Стрежево́й) City District Administration. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 221 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
250,000 emails from the Deptartment of Education of the Strezhevoy (Стрежево́й) City District Administration.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Dept. For Church Charity And Social Service Of The Russian Orthodox Church</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dept._for_church_charity_and_social_service_of_the_russian_orthodox_church/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dept._for_church_charity_and_social_service_of_the_russian_orthodox_church/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Dept. for Church Charity and Social Service of the Russian Orthodox Church Roughly 57,500 emails from the Russian Orthodox Church&amp;rsquo;s charitable wing. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 15 GB MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Roughly 57,500 emails from the Russian Orthodox Church&amp;rsquo;s charitable wing.
Due to the nature of the data, at this time it is only being offered to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Donetsk People'S Republic Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/donetsk_peoples_republic_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/donetsk_peoples_republic_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Donetsk People&amp;rsquo;s Republic emails Over 1 million emails and documents from the Donetsk People&amp;rsquo;s Republic, an unrecognized republic of Russia in the occupied parts of eastern Ukraine. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Kiborg News FILE SIZE 1.4 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 1 million emails and documents from the Donetsk People&amp;rsquo;s Republic in the occupied parts of eastern Ukraine, created by Russian-backed paramilitaries in 2014 and illegally annexed by Russia in 2022.</description></item><item><title>Doxxing Adventskalender</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/doxxing-adventskalender/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/doxxing-adventskalender/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Doxxing-Adventskalender The mass &amp;ldquo;doxxing&amp;rdquo; of German celebrities and politicians. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Germany TYPE Hack SOURCE 0rbit FILE SIZE 6.7 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES ZDNet EDITOR NOTES Limited Distribution The mass &amp;ldquo;doxxing&amp;rdquo; of German celebrities and politicians. Also known as 0rbit leaks.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Doxxing-Adventskalender&amp;amp;oldid=1182&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Germany Hack Limited Distribution</description></item><item><title>Durham</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/durham/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/durham/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Durham 14 gigabytes (uncompressed) hacked from the Durham region of Canada. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Canada TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 6.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
14 gigabytes (uncompressed) hacked from the Durham region of Canada.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)</description></item><item><title>Dussmann Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dussmann_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dussmann_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Dussmann Group 222 gigabytes hacked from German multi-service provider with subsidiaries focusing on facility management, corporate childcare, nursing and care for the elderly, and business systems solutions, including HVAC, electrical work, and elevators. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES 222 gigabytes hacked from German multi-service provider with subsidiaries focusing on facility management, corporate childcare, nursing and care for the elderly, and business systems solutions, including HVAC, electrical work, and elevators.</description></item><item><title>Ecm</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ecm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ecm/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from ECM)]
RELEASE
Elektrocentromontazh 1.23 million emails from Elektrocentromontazh (ECM) / Электроцентромонтаж, the chief power organization of Russia since 1940. ECM designs, builds, installs and maintains electrical equipment in power generation and transmission facilities in over 25 regions of Russia. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 1.7 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>EjéRcito Del Perú</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ej%C3%A9rcito_del_per%C3%BA/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ej%C3%A9rcito_del_per%C3%BA/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ejército del Perú Over 175,000 emails from Ejército del Perú (Peruvian Army). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Peru TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 112 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Over 175,000 emails from Ejército del Perú (Peruvian Army).
Contents [1] [Research] [2] [Aftermath] [3] [Guacamaya statement] [4] [Guacamaya Release Art and Statement] Research Hackean al Ejército Peruano y filtran sus reglajes a políticos (La Encerrona)</description></item><item><title>El Salvador Police Database</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/el_salvador_police_database/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/el_salvador_police_database/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
El Salvador Police Database A pair of databases of approximately 37,000 police in El Salvador, containing identification numbers, names, telephone numbers, office assignment information, email addresses, etc. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES El Salvador TYPE Hack SOURCE FocaLeaks FILE SIZE 4.5 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES DataBreaches.net EDITOR NOTES
A pair of databases of approximately 37,000 police in El Salvador, containing identification numbers, names, telephone numbers, office assignment information, email addresses, etc.</description></item><item><title>Elektrocentromontazh</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/elektrocentromontazh/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/elektrocentromontazh/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Elektrocentromontazh 1.23 million emails from Elektrocentromontazh (ECM) / Электроцентромонтаж, the chief power organization of Russia since 1940. ECM designs, builds, installs and maintains electrical equipment in power generation and transmission facilities in over 25 regions of Russia. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 1.7 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Elvees</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/elvees/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/elvees/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Elvees 70,000 files hacked from Elvees, a Russian producer of integrated circuits and security solutions, including anti-drone technology. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 749 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [Link] TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
70,000 files hacked from Elvees, a Russian producer of integrated circuits and security solutions, including anti-drone technology. Elvees also provides security technology for oil fields, refineries, and pipelines along with other energy industry needs.</description></item><item><title>Embassy Of Ecuador, Moscow</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/embassy_of_ecuador_moscow/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/embassy_of_ecuador_moscow/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Embassy of Ecuador, Moscow Over 30,000 emails ranging from 2018 to March, 2022 and 40,000 files from the Embassy of Ecuador, Moscow. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 53.3 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES The Daily Dot EDITOR NOTES
Over 30,000 emails ranging from 2018 to March, 2022 and 40,000 files from the Embassy of Ecuador, Moscow.</description></item><item><title>Enami Ep</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/enami_ep/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/enami_ep/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
ENAMI EP Hacked emails from the state mining company of Ecuador, founded under Rafael Correa&amp;rsquo;s administration and responsible for the over-development and destruction of indigenous lands. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Ecuador TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 63 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Hacked emails from the state mining company of Ecuador, founded under Rafael Correa&amp;rsquo;s administration and responsible for the over-development and destruction of indigenous lands.</description></item><item><title>Enerpred</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/enerpred/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/enerpred/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Enerpred 645,000 emails from Enerpred / Энерпред, the largest producer of hydraulic tools in Russia and the CIS, specializing in the energy, petrochemical, coal, gas and construction industries. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 432 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
645,000 emails from Enerpred / Энерпред, the largest producer of hydraulic tools in Russia and the CIS, specializing in the energy, petrochemical, coal, gas and construction industries.</description></item><item><title>Epik</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/epik/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/epik/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Epik User, registration, forwarding and other information behind the &amp;ldquo;privacy&amp;rdquo; web hosting and registrar service Epik, known for hosting fascist, white supremacist and other right-wing content as well as harassment and doxing websites. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 180 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Part 1, Part 2 TORRENT Part 1, Part 2, Part 3 DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Daily Dot, HuffPost, The Record EDITOR NOTES The files were initially released by the hackers independent of DDoSecrets and are presented as-is.</description></item><item><title>Ernst &amp; Young</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ernst__young/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ernst__young/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ernst &amp;amp; Young Internal files from the accounting firm Ernst &amp;amp; Young (EY). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 2 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Two terabytes of internal files from the accounting firm Ernst &amp;amp; Young (EY). Ernst &amp;amp; Young primarily provides accounting, tax, consulting and advisory services.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Estado Mayor Conjunto De La Defensa De Chile</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/estado_mayor_conjunto_de_la_defensa_de_chile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/estado_mayor_conjunto_de_la_defensa_de_chile/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Estado Mayor Conjunto de la Defensa de Chile)]
RELEASE
Estado Mayor Conjunto de las Fuerza Armadas de Chile Nearly 400,000 emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Estado Mayor Conjunto de las Fuerza Armadas de Chile (Joint Chiefs of Staff of the Chilean Armed Forces), who advise the Ministro de Defensa de Chile (Minister of Defense). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Chile TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 366 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [Link] TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Estado Mayor Conjunto De Las Fuerza Armadas De Chile</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/estado_mayor_conjunto_de_las_fuerza_armadas_de_chile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/estado_mayor_conjunto_de_las_fuerza_armadas_de_chile/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Estado Mayor Conjunto de las Fuerza Armadas de Chile Nearly 400,000 emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Estado Mayor Conjunto de las Fuerza Armadas de Chile (Joint Chiefs of Staff of the Chilean Armed Forces), who advise the Ministro de Defensa de Chile (Minister of Defense). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Chile TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 366 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [Link] TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Ethiopia Financial Intelligence Service</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ethiopia_financial_intelligence_service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ethiopia_financial_intelligence_service/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ethiopia Financial Intelligence Service Approximately 19,000 emails from Ethiopia&amp;rsquo;s Financial Intelligence Service DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Ethiopia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 45 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 19,000 emails from Ethiopia&amp;rsquo;s Financial Intelligence Service, previously known as the Financial Intelligence Center, the government agency responsible for monitoring suspicious financial transactions in the country.
Embargo During an initial embargo, the data was shared with the Platform to Protect Whistleblowers in Africa (PPLAAF), which shared its findings with various media partners: Bloomberg in the United States; Süddeutsche Zeitung in Germany; Tamedia in Switzerland; and The Continent in South Africa.</description></item><item><title>Execupharm</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/execupharm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/execupharm/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
ExecuPharm 200,000 emails and other files from ExecuPharm, a pharmaceutical company that performs outsourced medical trials. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 108.87 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
200,000 emails and other files from ExecuPharm, a pharmaceutical company that performs outsourced medical trials.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=ExecuPharm&amp;amp;oldid=588&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Corporate Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Fbi Dhs Leak</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fbi-dhs_leak/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fbi-dhs_leak/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
FBI-DHS leak Hacked FBI and DHS personnel information released by @CthulhuSec. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 631.2 kB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Hacked FBI and DHS personnel information released by @CthulhuSec.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=FBI-DHS_leak&amp;amp;oldid=2154&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack United States of America</description></item><item><title>Filippobaloo Tiscali.It.Zip</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/filippobaloo_tiscali.it.zip/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/filippobaloo_tiscali.it.zip/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
filippobaloo_tiscali.it.zip An email archived hacked from Italian political figure Filippo Gallina. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Italy TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 93 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
An email archived hacked from Italian political figure Filippo Gallina.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Filippobaloo_tiscali.it.zip&amp;amp;oldid=1184&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Italy</description></item><item><title>Fisher &amp; Paykel</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fisher__paykel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fisher__paykel/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fisher &amp;amp; Paykel Over 30 gigabytes hacked from Fisher &amp;amp; Paykel, a major appliance manufacturer which is a subsidiary of home appliance manufacturer Haier, based in East Tamaki, New Zealand. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES New Zealand, Italy, United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 31 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 30 gigabytes hacked from Fisher &amp;amp; Paykel, a major appliance manufacturer which is a subsidiary of home appliance manufacturer Haier, based in East Tamaki, New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Forest</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/forest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/forest/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Forest 37,500 emails from Forest / Форест, a Russian logging and wood manufacturing firm and associated companies. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 35.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
37,500 emails from Forest / Форест, a Russian logging and wood manufacturing firm and associated companies.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Fraternal Order Of Police</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fraternal_order_of_police/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fraternal_order_of_police/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fraternal Order of Police Files from the Fraternal Order of Police. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 260 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Guardian EDITOR NOTES
Hacked files from the Fraternal Order of Police.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Fraternal_Order_of_Police&amp;amp;oldid=2157&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Organization United States of America</description></item><item><title>Fuck Fbi Friday</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fuck_fbi_friday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fuck_fbi_friday/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fuck FBI Friday A series of hacks against United States law enforcement agencies and contractors by Anonymous-affiliated group Lulzsec/Antisec. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Lulzsec/Antisec FILE SIZE 5.28 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link MAGNET (III) Link MAGNET (IV) Link MAGNET (V) Link MAGNET (VI) Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A series of hacks against the Federal Bureau of Investigation, law enforcement agencies, and contractors by Anonymous-affiliated group Lulzsec/Antisec.</description></item><item><title>Fuerza Armada De El Salvador</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fuerza_armada_de_el_salvador/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fuerza_armada_de_el_salvador/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fuerza Armada de El Salvador Nearly 250,000 emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Fuerza Armada de El Salvador (Armed Forces of El Salvador). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES El Salvador TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 73 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Nearly 250,000 emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Fuerza Armada de El Salvador (Armed Forces of El Salvador).</description></item><item><title>FundaçÃO Nacional De Artes</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/funda%C3%A7%C3%A3o_nacional_de_artes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/funda%C3%A7%C3%A3o_nacional_de_artes/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fundação Nacional de Artes Over 1 million emails from Fundação Nacional de Artes (Funarte), the Brazilian government&amp;rsquo;s National Arts Foundation. Funarte develops policies to promote the arts, including music, dance, theater and the circus. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 302 GB How to Request Access MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 1 million emails from Fundação Nacional de Artes (Funarte), the Brazilian government&amp;rsquo;s National Arts Foundation.</description></item><item><title>Gableaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gableaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gableaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GabLeaks 70 GB of Gab public posts, private posts, user profiles, hashed passwords for users, DMs, and plaintext passwords for groups. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES International TYPE Hack SOURCE JaXpArO (they/them) &amp;amp; My Little Anonymous Revival Project FILE SIZE 70 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES Wired EDITOR NOTES Gab response to query from Wired The Gab data is an important but complicated dataset.</description></item><item><title>Gazprom Linde Engineering</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gazprom_linde_engineering/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gazprom_linde_engineering/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Gazprom Linde Engineering 768,000 emails from Gazprom Linde Engineering, which specializes in designing gas and petrochemical processing facilities and oil refineries. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 728 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
768,000 emails from Gazprom Linde Engineering, which specializes in designing gas and petrochemical processing facilities and oil refineries.</description></item><item><title>Gazregion</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gazregion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gazregion/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Gazregion Emails and files from Gazregion, a construction company specializing in gas pipelines and facilities. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous, NB65, Porteur FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES This release consists of three submissions from three sources about the same company. Emails, files and decryption keys from Gazregion, a construction company specializing in gas pipelines and facilities.</description></item><item><title>German Chambers Of Commerce</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/german_chambers_of_commerce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/german_chambers_of_commerce/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
DATASET NAME Documents allegedly acquired from the delegate of German economy in Ukraine, Alexander Marcus and his wife, a Russian citizen and FSB operative DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Germany TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 2.7 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
According to the source, the 2.7 Gigabyte of internal documents have been acquired through their offices in Ukraine and Azerbaijan, from the delegate of German economy in Ukraine, Alexander Marcus and his wife, a Russian citizen and FSB operative.</description></item><item><title>Givesendgo</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GiveSendGo Donor information for every GiveSendGo campaign as of February 2021. Note that this is unrelated to the February 2022 leaks. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES N/A TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 15 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES Fox Business, The Guardian, Medium, VICE EDITOR NOTES See also GiveSendGo 2.0, GiveSendGo 3.0, GiveSendGo 4.0 and GiveSendGo 5.0 Donor information for every campaign on the &amp;lsquo;Christian fundraising platform&amp;rsquo; GiveSendGo, best known for being used by far-right extremists like the Proud Boys.</description></item><item><title>Givesendgo 3.0</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_3.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_3.0/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GiveSendGo 3.0 Donor information for the Freedom Convoy campaign from the GiveSendGo platform as of February 13, 2022 DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES N/A TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 33.6 MB MORE REFERENCES Vice EDITOR NOTES See also GiveSendGo, GiveSendGo 2.0, GiveSendGo 4.0 and GiveSendGo 5.0 Donor information for the Freedom Convoy campaign from the GiveSendGo platform ending on February 13, 2022, including names (self-reported), email addresses and zip codes.</description></item><item><title>Givesendgo 4.0</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_4.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_4.0/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GiveSendGo 4.0 5 GB of files including donor info for the Adopt A Trucker campaign, a full MySQL dump, sourcecode for their Bitbucket repo, their customer service systems, verification documents, and Stripe data for the Freedom Convoy and the Adopt A Trucker campaigns. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES N/A TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 5 GB MORE REFERENCES Daily Dot EDITOR NOTES See also GiveSendGo, GiveSendGo 2.</description></item><item><title>Givesendgo 5.0</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_5.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_5.0/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GiveSendGo 5.0 Updated Stripe and donor information for the Freedom Convoy campaign from the GiveSendGo platform as of February 23, 2022 DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES N/A TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 863.3 MB MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES See also GiveSendGo, GiveSendGo 2.0, GiveSendGo 3.0 and GiveSendGo 4.0 Updated Stripe and donor information for the Freedom Convoy campaign from the GiveSendGo platform as of February 23, 2022.</description></item><item><title>Givesendgo Freedom Convoy Donor Info</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_freedom_convoy_donor_info/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_freedom_convoy_donor_info/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from GiveSendGo Freedom Convoy donor info)]
RELEASE
GiveSendGo 3.0 Donor information for the Freedom Convoy campaign from the GiveSendGo platform as of February 13, 2022 DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES N/A TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 33.6 MB MORE REFERENCES Vice EDITOR NOTES See also GiveSendGo, GiveSendGo 2.0, GiveSendGo 4.0 and GiveSendGo 5.0 Donor information for the Freedom Convoy campaign from the GiveSendGo platform ending on February 13, 2022, including names (self-reported), email addresses and zip codes.</description></item><item><title>Gorraleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gorraleaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gorraleaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GorraLeaks 2.0 Hundreds of gigabytes of hacked Argentinian police data, including emails, documents, wiretap recordings, and more. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Argentina TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 187 GB / 259 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES infobae EDITOR NOTES
Hundreds of gigabytes of hacked Argentinian police data, including emails, documents, wiretap recordings, and more. Initial reports put estimated 700 GB of data, however examinations of the data and discussions with the source establish it is slightly less than half of that once duplications have been removed.</description></item><item><title>Gqleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gqleaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gqleaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GQLeaks 120 GB of emails hacked from the Centro Nacional de la Informatización de la Administración Pública de Guinea Ecuatorial (CNIAPGE) or Equatorial Guinea&amp;rsquo;s National Center for the Computerization of Public Administration. The emails are dated between 2017 and early 2022. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Equatorial Guinea TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 120 GB DOWNLOADS (How to request access) MORE REFERENCES Diario Rombe EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Green Atom</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/green_atom/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/green_atom/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Green Atom)]
RELEASE
Convex 120 gigabytes from the Russian internet provider Convex, revealing pervasive Russian surveillance of internet and phone activities, including the previously unknown Green Atom surveillance program. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE CAXXII FILE SIZE 128 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [Link] TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES KyivPost, Library of Congress EDITOR NOTES The data was originally released by the hackers independently.</description></item><item><title>Groupe Comet</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/groupe_comet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/groupe_comet/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Groupe Comet 6.9 gigabytes hacked from an industrial recycling firm based in Belgium and operating throughout Europe, Asia and South America. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Belgium TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBIt FILE SIZE 5.4 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
6.9 gigabytes hacked from an industrial recycling firm based in Belgium and operating throughout Europe, Asia and South America.</description></item><item><title>Guccifer Archive</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/guccifer_archive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/guccifer_archive/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Guccifer Archive The files released by the original Guccifer. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Guccifer FILE SIZE 6.9 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
The files released by the original Guccifer, including files hacked Hillary Clinton emails and George W. Bush paintings.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Guccifer_Archive&amp;amp;oldid=2484&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack United States of America</description></item><item><title>Gulf Copper</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gulf_copper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gulf_copper/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Gulf Copper Over 9,000 files from Gulf Copper Energy Services, which serves major and independent offshore drilling rig contractors, offshore oil and gas operating and service companies, national oil companies, major commercial ship operators and the United States government and military. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Conti FILE SIZE 4.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Guov I Gs General Dept. Of Troops And Civil Construction</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/guov_i_gs_-_general_dept._of_troops_and_civil_construction/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/guov_i_gs_-_general_dept._of_troops_and_civil_construction/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GUOV i GS - General Dept. of Troops and Civil Construction 15,600 emails from GUOV I GS - the General Dept. of Troops and Civil Construction, a construction company that works on projects in the interests of the Russian Ministry of Defense. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Porteur FILE SIZE 9.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Harita Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/harita_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/harita_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Harita Group Emails from Harita Group, which primarily deals with nickel mining, bauxite mining, coal, ferronickel smelters, alumina refineries, logging, and palm oil plantations. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Indonesia TYPE Hack SOURCE Somos malas&amp;hellip; podemos ser peores FILE SIZE 510 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link REFERENCES Wikipedia EDITOR NOTES
Emails from the Harita Group, which primarily deals with nickel mining, bauxite mining, coal, ferronickel smelters, alumina refineries, logging, and palm oil plantations.</description></item><item><title>Hart</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hart/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hart/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
HART Over 10 gigabytes of internal chats, documents and other files from the COVID misinformation group HART (Health Advisory &amp;amp; Recovery Team). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United Kingdom TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 10.2 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 10 gigabytes of internal chats, documents and other files from the COVID misinformation group HART (Health Advisory &amp;amp; Recovery Team), documenting non-public members and participants, &amp;ldquo;psych ops&amp;rdquo; and efforts to build influence campaigns targeting policy makers and the public with anti-masking and anti-vaccination propaganda.</description></item><item><title>Hbgary</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hbgary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hbgary/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
HBGary Over 70,000 emails from key people at the private intelligence firm HBGary. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 7 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES KrebsOnSecurity EDITOR NOTES
Over 70,000 emails from key people at the private intelligence firm HBGary. The emails show, among other things, plots to discredit their enemies.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=HBGary&amp;amp;oldid=2170&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Anonymous Corporate Hack</description></item><item><title>Henning Harders</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/henning_harders/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/henning_harders/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Henning Harders 303 gigabytes hacked from Henning Harders, an Australian freight forwarding agent, trade consultancy and licensed customs broker. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Australia TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 303 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
303 gigabytes hacked from Henning Harders, an Australian freight forwarding agent, trade consultancy and licensed customs broker.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Igor.Piliaiev@Gmail.Com</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/igor.piliaiev@gmail.com/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/igor.piliaiev@gmail.com/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
[email protected] Emails from Igor Pilyaeva, tied to Russian operations in Ukraine. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE MadUkrop$_Crew FILE SIZE 75.5 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES CyberGuerilla EDITOR NOTES
Emails from Igor Pilyaeva, tied to Russian operations in Ukraine, hacked by MadUkrop$_Crew.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/[[email protected]]&amp;amp;oldid=1141&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Russia Ukraine</description></item><item><title>Illinois Attorney General</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/illinois_attorney_general/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/illinois_attorney_general/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Illinois Attorney General A cache of files hacked from the Illinois Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s office. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE DoppelPaymer FILE SIZE About 200 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES ThreatPost EDITOR NOTES
A cache of files hacked from the Illinois Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s office by the ransomware crew DoppelPaymer. The total cache is allegedly &amp;ldquo;about 200 GB&amp;rdquo; that will be &amp;ldquo;progressively uploaded.</description></item><item><title>Inafor</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/inafor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/inafor/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
INAFOR Hacked emails and files from the Nicaraguan forestry service. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Nicaragua TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 17.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Emails and files hacked from the Nicaraguan forestry service by members of Anonymous.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=INAFOR&amp;amp;oldid=2174&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Nicaragua</description></item><item><title>India Bulls</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/india_bulls/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/india_bulls/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
India Bulls Over 130,000 emails and other files from India Bulls, which operates in the financial, real estate, and pharmaceutical sectors along with other industries. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES India TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 39.35 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 130,000 emails and other files from India Bulls, which operates in the financial, real estate, and pharmaceutical sectors along with other industries.</description></item><item><title>Ingerop</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ingerop/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ingerop/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE Image Here DATASET NAME Hacked files from the French contractor firm Ingerop responsible for projects including nuclear power plants. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY France TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 65 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES Cyware EDITOR NOTES
Hacked files from the French contractor firm Ingerop responsible for projects including nuclear power plants.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Ingerop&amp;amp;oldid=1165&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Corporate France Hack</description></item><item><title>Innwa Bank</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/innwa_bank/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/innwa_bank/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Innwa Bank
Nearly 20,000 files from Innwa Bank, which is owned by the Myanmar Economic Corporation (MEC) and is used to pay salaries and transfer funds for military officers and units, and military controlled businesses.
DATASET DETAILS
COUNTRIES Myanmar
TYPE Hack
SOURCE Sugondese Electronic Army
FILE SIZE 49 MB
DOWNLOADS (How to Download)
MAGNET [[[[Link]]]]
TORRENT Link
MORE
REFERENCES
Justice For Myanmar
EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Integrity Initiative</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/integrity_initiative/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/integrity_initiative/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Integrity Initiative Integrity Initiative is a non-profit that counters Russian propaganda. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United Kingdom TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE (Parts 1-6) 91.5 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET (Parts 1-6) Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Integrity Initiative EDITOR NOTES
Integrity Initiative was a non-profit that counters Russian propaganda. It appeared to have confirmed the hack, but has not reviewed the individual documents.</description></item><item><title>Intolerance Network</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/intolerance_network/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/intolerance_network/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Intolerance Network)]
RELEASE
CitizenGo Over 17,000 documents hacked from right wing campaigning organizations Grupo CitizenGO &amp;amp; HazteOir hacked by ACABGang. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE ACABGang FILE SIZE 24 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES These files are the unredacted version of WikiLeaks&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Intolerance Network&amp;rdquo;. See also CitizenGo &amp;amp; HatzeOir databases Over 17,000 documents from right wing campaigning organizations Grupo CitizenGO &amp;amp; HazteOir hacked by ACABGang.</description></item><item><title>Italian State Police</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/italian_state_police/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/italian_state_police/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Italian State Police 1.35 Gigabyte of hacked from the Italian State Police, including details about wiretaps. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Italy TYPE Hack SOURCE Unknown FILE SIZE 1.1 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
1.35 Gigabyte of hacked from the Italian State Police, including details about wiretaps from Telcom Italia and confidential technical information about interception devices. The materials were ostensibly hacked by Anonymous.</description></item><item><title>J.Irwin Company</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/j.irwin_company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/j.irwin_company/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
J. Irwin Company 300 megabytes from J. Irwin Company, which installs pipeline and constructs processing plants, compressor stations and other facilities for gas, oil and water transportation. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Xing FILE SIZE 309 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
300 megabytes from J. Irwin Company, which installs pipelines and constructs processing plants, compressor stations and other facilities for gas, oil and water transportation.</description></item><item><title>Jhonlin Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jhonlin_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jhonlin_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Jhonlin Group Over 600,000 hacked emails from the Jhonlin Group, a mining and palm oil plantation conglomerate. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Indonesia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 513 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [Link] TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 600,000 hacked emails from the Jhonlin Group, a mining and palm oil plantation conglomerate.
The conglomerate is known for using police to intimidate journalists and activists.</description></item><item><title>Jones Day</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jones_day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jones_day/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Jones Day Data hacked from the high profile Jones Day law firm, including data associated with the city of Chicago and Chicago PD, as well as data associated with the credit reporting agency Experian. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 85 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES VICE EDITOR NOTES
Data hacked from the high profile Jones Day lawfirm, including data associated with the city of Chicago and Chicago PD, as well as data associated with the credit reporting agency Experian.</description></item><item><title>Kcsa Strategic Communications</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/kcsa_strategic_communications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/kcsa_strategic_communications/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
KCSA Strategic Communications A public relations firm based in Boston, MA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 152.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A public relations firm based in Boston, MA breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Khava D@Mail.Ru</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/khava-d@mail.ru/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/khava-d@mail.ru/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
[email protected] Emails from Dmitry V. Khavchenko, a militant allegedly connected to pro-Russian terrorists. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Myrotvorets Center FILE SIZE 1.7 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES Euromaidan Press EDITOR NOTES
Emails from Dmitry V. Khavchenko, a militant allegedly connected to pro-Russian terrorists in the Donbas accused of ties to Russian security services and influence operations targeting Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Latam Air</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/latam_air/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/latam_air/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from LATAM Air)]
RELEASE
LATAM Airlines 53 gigabytes of cargo manifests from LATAM Airlines, focusing on Colombia and Peru. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Colombia, Peru TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 53 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES 53 gigabytes of cargo manifests hacked from LATAM Airlines, focusing on Colombia and Peru.
Due to the presence of PII including copies of passports, the data is being offered only on a Limited Distribution basis.</description></item><item><title>Latam Airlines</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/latam_airlines/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/latam_airlines/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
LATAM Airlines 53 gigabytes of cargo manifests from LATAM Airlines, focusing on Colombia and Peru. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Colombia, Peru TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 53 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES 53 gigabytes of cargo manifests hacked from LATAM Airlines, focusing on Colombia and Peru.
Due to the presence of PII including copies of passports, the data is being offered only on a Limited Distribution basis.</description></item><item><title>Leakymails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/leakymails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/leakymails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
LeakyMails A collection of emails and dossiers released by LeakyMails, focusing on personnel affiliated with intelligence services. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Argentina TYPE Hack SOURCE LeakyMails FILE SIZE (Dossiers) 27.1 FILE SIZE (Emails) 243 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET (Dossiers) Link MAGNET (Emails) Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A collection of emails and dossiers released by LeakyMails, focusing on personnel affiliated with intelligence services.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=LeakyMails&amp;amp;oldid=1167&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Letmespy</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/letmespy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/letmespy/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
LetMeSpy Tens of thousands of database entries containing customer information, messages, call, GPS and other logs from devices compromised by the LetMeSpy stalkerware. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 68 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES LetMeSpy statement EDITOR NOTES
Tens of thousands of database entries containing customer information, messages, call, GPS and other logs from devices compromised by the LetMeSpy stalkerware.</description></item><item><title>Liberty Counsel</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/liberty_counsel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/liberty_counsel/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Liberty Counsel Databases from the far-right lobby and litigation group Liberty Counsel. Also: databases for Christian missionary groups using WMTEK software for customer management. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States, Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published by Enlace Hacktivista Liberty Counsel helped overturn Roe v. Wade, and claim to have prayed with Supreme Court justices.</description></item><item><title>Linestar</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/linestar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/linestar/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
LineStar 37 gigabytes hacked from the integrated pipeline compliance, technology and integrity maintenance company LineStar, along with 73,500 emails. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Xing FILE SIZE 37 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Wired EDITOR NOTES
37 gigabytes hacked from the integrated pipeline compliance, technology and integrity maintenance company LineStar.
Contents [1] [Redactions] [2] [Emails] Redactions For usability and to reduce the potential for abuse, approximately 19 gigabytes of .</description></item><item><title>Llc Capital</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/llc_capital/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/llc_capital/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
LLC Capital 31,990 emails from LLC Capital / ООО Капитал, a specialized accounting firm which works with SAFMAR Group and its assets, including PJSC RussNeft. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 20.4 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
31,990 emails from LLC Capital / ООО Капитал, a specialized accounting firm which works with Mikhail Gutseriev&amp;rsquo;s SAFMAR Group and its assets, including PJSC RussNeft.</description></item><item><title>Macron Leaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/macron_leaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/macron_leaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Macron Leaks Macron emails hacked by Russian state actors, first released directly before the French election. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY France TYPE Hack SOURCE 4chan FILE SIZE 6.8 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Macron emails hacked by Russian state actors, first released directly before the French election.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Macron_leaks&amp;amp;oldid=2183&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Allegations of State Sponsorship France Hack</description></item><item><title>Manafort Texts</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/manafort_texts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/manafort_texts/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Manafort texts Text messages obtained from the phone of Paul Manafort&amp;rsquo;s daughter. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 98.4 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES In a private communication, WikiLeaks stated that they thought the phone had been hacked by Ukrainian intelligence. Text messages obtained from the phone of Paul Manafort&amp;rsquo;s daughter. In a private communication, WikiLeaks stated that they thought the phone had been hacked by Ukrainian intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Marathon Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/marathon_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/marathon_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Marathon Group 62,000 emails from the Marathon Group, an investment firm owned by Alexander Vinokurov, who is under EU sanctions for &amp;ldquo;providing a substantial source of revenue to the Government of Russia.&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 51.9 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
62,000 emails from the Marathon Group, an investment firm owned by Alexander Vinokurov, who is under EU sanctions for &amp;ldquo;providing a substantial source of revenue to the Government of Russia.</description></item><item><title>Mas Holdings</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mas_holdings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mas_holdings/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MAS Holdings 29 gigabytes of hacked files from MAS Holdings, South Asia&amp;rsquo;s largest manufacturer of lingerie and one of Sri Lanka&amp;rsquo;s largest apparel manufacturers. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Sri Lanka TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 29 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
29 gigabytes of hacked files from MAS Holdings, South Asia&amp;rsquo;s largest manufacturer of lingerie and one of Sri Lanka&amp;rsquo;s largest apparel manufacturers.</description></item><item><title>Mashoil</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mashoil/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mashoil/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MashOil Nearly 140,000 emails from MashOil, which designs, manufactures and maintains equipment used in the drilling, mining and fracking industries. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 110 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 140,000 emails from MashOil, which designs, manufactures and maintains equipment used in the drilling, mining and fracking industries.</description></item><item><title>Mclanahan Russia</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mclanahan_russia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mclanahan_russia/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
McLanahan Russia 311,122 emails from McLanahan Russia, a mining equipment and services company with its origin and corporate headquarters in Hollidaysburg, Pennsylvania. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia, United States of America TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 302 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
311,122 emails from McLanahan Russia, a mining equipment and services company with its origin and corporate headquarters in Hollidaysburg, Pennsylvania.</description></item><item><title>Medical Diagnostics Laboratories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/medical_diagnostics_laboratories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/medical_diagnostics_laboratories/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Medical Diagnostics Laboratories 83 gigabytes of data hacked from Medical Diagnostics Laboratories, which performs outsourced medical testing in addition to Research and Development (R&amp;amp;D). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 83 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
83 gigabytes of data hacked from Medical Diagnostics Laboratories, which performs outsourced medical testing in addition to Research and Development (R&amp;amp;D).</description></item><item><title>Meritservus And Meritkapital</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/meritservus_and_meritkapital/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/meritservus_and_meritkapital/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MeritServus and MeritKapital Over 400,000 files and 72,000 emails from MeritServus and MeritKapital, which provide corporate registration and administration, asset management and holding company services along with golden passport services. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Cyprus TYPE Hack SOURCE F R E A K Y FILE SIZE 500 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 400,000 files and 72,000 emails from MeritServus and MeritKapital, which provide corporate registration, administration, asset management and holding company services along with golden passport services.</description></item><item><title>Metprom Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/metprom_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/metprom_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Metprom Group Emails from a metallurgic engineering and investment group involved in dozens of projects with ArcelorMittal, PAO NLMK, EVRAZ group enterprises, PAO Mechel plants, PAO Severstal, Isfahan metallurgical plant, Helwan metallurgical plant and others. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE B00da, Porteur, Wh1t3 Sh4d0w FILE SIZE 184 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Part One, Part Two TORRENT Part One, Part Two DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Metropolitan Police Department D.C.</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/metropolitan_police_department_d.c./</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/metropolitan_police_department_d.c./</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Milicoleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/milicoleaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/milicoleaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MilicoLeaks Emails from senior officials and offices in the Chilean Army. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Chile TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 2.35 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Verdad Ahora EDITOR NOTES
~3,500 emails from senior officials and offices in the Chilean Army, including the Directors of Intelligence, Operations, Finance, and International Relations. Journalists reporting on the cache discovered evidence of fraud, corruption and secret bilateral intelligence sharing agreements with the Pentagon.</description></item><item><title>Mining Secrets</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mining_secrets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mining_secrets/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Mining Secrets Over 4 terabytes of files and emails from the Swiss-registered mining and investment consortium Solway and its Guatemalan subsidiaries Pronico and CGN. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Guatemala, Russia, Switzerland TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 4.2 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Mail, Files TORRENT Mail, Files DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Forbidden Stories (en) Forbidden Stories (es) Forbidden Stories (fr),Guacamaya statement EDITOR NOTES A video of the hack was sent to Enlace Hacktivista and can be seen here Over 4 terabytes of files and emails from the Swiss-registered mining and investment consortium Solway and its Guatemalan subsidiaries Pronico and CGN.</description></item><item><title>Ministerio De Ambiente Y Recursos Naturales</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministerio_de_ambiente_y_recursos_naturales/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministerio_de_ambiente_y_recursos_naturales/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ministerio de Ambiente y Recursos Naturales (MARN) Hacked emails from Ministerio de Ambiente y Recursos Naturales (MARN), which controls natural resources in Guatemala. MARN&amp;rsquo;s corruption has resulted in the destruction of natural resources. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Guatemala TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Hacked emails from Ministerio de Ambiente y Recursos Naturales (MARN), which controls natural resources in Guatemala.</description></item><item><title>Ministerio De Justicia Of Chile</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministerio_de_justicia_of_chile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministerio_de_justicia_of_chile/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ministerio de Justicia of Chile Over 384,000 emails from the Ministerio de Justicia (Ministry of Justice) of Chile. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Chile TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 67 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES Ciper EDITOR NOTES
Over 384,000 emails from the Ministerio de Justicia (Ministry of Justice) of Chile.
Limited Distribution Due to the sensitivity of the data, the data is only being provided to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Ministry Of Communications And It Of Azerbaijan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministry_of_communications_and_it_of_azerbaijan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministry_of_communications_and_it_of_azerbaijan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ministry of Communications and IT of Azerbaijan The documents contain a variety of information showing interesting ties between various corporations, government agencies and officials. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Azerbaijan TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 1.4 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
The documents contain a variety of information showing interesting ties between various corporations, government agencies and officials.</description></item><item><title>Ministry Of Culture Of The Russian Federation</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministry_of_culture_of_the_russian_federation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministry_of_culture_of_the_russian_federation/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ministry of Culture of the Russian Federation / Минкультуры России 230,000 emails from the Ministry of Culture of the Russian Federation / Министерство культуры Российской Федерации, which is responsible for state policy regarding art, cinematography, archives, copyright, cultural heritage, and censorship. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 446 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Mk Brokers</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mk_brokers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mk_brokers/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MK Brokers 23 gigabytes hacked from the Bulgarian investment firm MK Brokers, including nearly 150,000 files. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Bulgaria TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBit FILE SIZE 8.15 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
23 gigabytes hacked from the Bulgarian investment firm MK Brokers, including nearly 150,000 files.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=MK_Brokers&amp;amp;oldid=2194&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box Bulgaria Corporate Hack Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Mosekspertiza</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mosekspertiza/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mosekspertiza/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Mosekspertiza Over 150,000 emails, 8,200 files and several hundred gigabytes of databases from Mosekspertiza, a state-owned company created by the Moscow Chamber of Commerce to provide expert services and consultations to Russian businesses. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE NB65 FILE SIZE 483.3 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Email, File, Database TORRENT Email, File, Database DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Municipal Court Of Princeton</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/municipal_court_of_princeton/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/municipal_court_of_princeton/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Municipal Court of Princeton Nearly 30 GB of appeal letters, accounting and audit information, amendment documents, tax information and chats. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Marketo FILE SIZE 28 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 30 GB of appeal letters, accounting and audit information, amendment documents, tax information and chats.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Mvtec</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mvtec/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mvtec/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MVTEC Source code for Artificial Intelligence and Deep Learning software. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 339.89 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Source code for Artificial Intelligence and Deep Learning software used in robotics, medical imaging, inspection, manufacturing and production, surveillance, research and more.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=MVTEC&amp;amp;oldid=2196&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Corporate Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Myanmar Internal Revenue Department</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myanmar_internal_revenue_department/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myanmar_internal_revenue_department/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Myanmar Internal Revenue Department Tax filings from Myanmar&amp;rsquo;s Internal Revenue Department (IRD). The data includes all tax filings and supporting documents from 2021. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Myanmar TYPE Hack SOURCE Sugondese Electronic Army FILE SIZE 446 GB How to Request Access MORE REFERENCES ICIJ investigation EDITOR NOTES ReadMe.txt from the source Tax filings from the Myanmar&amp;rsquo;s Internal Revenue Department (IRD), a state agency that has been illegally controlled by the Myanmar military since the coup on February 1, 2021.</description></item><item><title>Myanmar Investments</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myanmar_investments/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myanmar_investments/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Myanmar Investments Thousands of confidential documents and investment proposals and approvals hacked from the Myanmar Investment Commission. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Myanmar TYPE Hack SOURCE Sugondese separatist Bofa FILE SIZE 156 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Justice for Myanmar EDITOR NOTES Source statement Contents [1] [Description] [2] [Burmese Translation] [3] [Research] [4] [Aftermath] [5] [Source Information] [6] [See Also] Description Thousands of confidential documents and investment proposals and approvals hacked from the Myanmar Investment Commission.</description></item><item><title>Myatt Blume &amp; Osburn</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myatt_blume__osburn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myatt_blume__osburn/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Myatt Blume &amp;amp; Osburn A Texas accounting firm with corporate and government clients. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 27.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A Texas accounting firm with corporate and government clients breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Myattcpa</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myattcpa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myattcpa/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Myattcpa)]
RELEASE
Myatt Blume &amp;amp; Osburn A Texas accounting firm with corporate and government clients. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 27.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A Texas accounting firm with corporate and government clients breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>National Police Of Paraguay</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/national_police_of_paraguay/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/national_police_of_paraguay/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
National Police of Paraguay Over 500,000 internal documents, images and SQL databases from the National Police of Paraguay (Policía Nacional del Paraguay). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Paraguay TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 400 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 500,000 internal documents and images from the National Police of Paraguay (Policía Nacional del Paraguay), and 175 gigabytes of SQL databases.
The data includes documents from the Internal Affairs Directorate (Dirección de Asuntos Internos), the Identification Department (Departamento de Identificaciones) and the Foreigners Registry Department (Departamento Registro de Extranjeros), Technology and Development Division (Division de Tecnologia y Desarrollo), as well as other documents including orders from command, photographs of evidence and documents about wanted individuals.</description></item><item><title>Nauru Police Force</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/nauru_police_force/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/nauru_police_force/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Nauru Police Force 285,635 emails from the Nauru Police Force, documenting conditions of the island and abuses endured by asylum-seekers and refugees, the majority of whom are from Iran, while many others hail from Afghanistan, Iraq, Myanmar, Pakistan and Sri Lanka or are stateless. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Australia, Nauru TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 82 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Neocom Geoservice</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/neocom_geoservice/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/neocom_geoservice/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Neocom Geoservice 87,500 emails from Neocom Geoservice, an engineering firm specializing in exploring oil and gas fields and providing drilling support. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 107 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
87,500 emails from Neocom Geoservice, an engineering firm specializing in exploring oil and gas fields and providing drilling support.</description></item><item><title>Netzsch</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/netzsch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/netzsch/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Netzsch Over 375,000 files from machinery manufacturer Netzsch. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 411.31 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 375,000 files from machinery manufacturer Netzsch, which earns approximately $1 billion (USD) annually according to some sources, and half a billion (USD) according to others.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Netzsch&amp;amp;oldid=589&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Corporate Ransomware</description></item><item><title>New Granada Energy Corporation</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/new_granada_energy_corporation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/new_granada_energy_corporation/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
New Granada Energy Corporation Hacked emails from a Colombian oil subsidiary of Sinopec. &amp;ldquo;Environmental Statistics&amp;rdquo; emails show that &amp;ldquo;small&amp;rdquo; spills occur weekly. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Colombia TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 252 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Hacked emails from a Colombian oil subsidiary of Sinopec. &amp;ldquo;Environmental Statistics&amp;rdquo; emails show that &amp;ldquo;small&amp;rdquo; spills occur weekly.</description></item><item><title>Newbridge Securities</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/newbridge_securities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/newbridge_securities/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Newbridge Securities Corporation Approximately 90 gigabytes from Newbridge Securities, a securities brokerage, investment banking and wealth management services firm. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Marketo FILE SIZE 93 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 90 gigabytes from Newbridge Securities, a securities brokerage, investment banking and wealth management services firm.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>No Fly List</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/no_fly_list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/no_fly_list/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
No Fly List A copy of the United States&amp;rsquo; No Fly List from 2019, which CommuteAir left on an misconfigured (unsecured) development server. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE maia crimew FILE SIZE 90 MB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES maia.crimew, Daily Dot EDITOR NOTES
A copy of the United States&amp;rsquo; No Fly List from 2019, which CommuteAir left on an misconfigured (unsecured) development server.</description></item><item><title>North American Roofing</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/north_american_roofing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/north_american_roofing/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
North American Roofing 83 gigabytes hacked from the &amp;ldquo;most trusted and respected commercial roofing company in the U.S.&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 83 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
83 gigabytes hacked from the &amp;ldquo;most trusted and respected commercial roofing company in the U.S.&amp;rdquo; The company not only boasts about the quality of its work and its community involvement, but about its sustainability program and green initiative.</description></item><item><title>Npo Vs</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/npo_vs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/npo_vs/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
NPO VS Over one million emails from NPO VS / НПО ВС, a Russian IT company that specializes in data automation and security, including the processing and protection of state secrets. NPO VS&amp;rsquo; clients include the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs and the Ministry of Defence. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 759 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Nuclear Power Production And Development Company Of Iran</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/nuclear_power_production_and_development_company_of_iran/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/nuclear_power_production_and_development_company_of_iran/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Nuclear Power Production and Development Company of Iran Over 100,000 emails from the Nuclear Power Production and Development Company of Iran, which runs Iranian research and development in the nuclear fuel cycle, including uranium exploration, mining and conversion. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Iran TYPE Hack SOURCE Black Reward FILE SIZE 75 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [[Link]] TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Nusantara Regas</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/nusantara_regas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/nusantara_regas/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Nusantara Regas A gigabyte of files hacked from the natural gas company Nusantara Regas. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Indonesia TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBit FILE SIZE 724 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A gigabyte of files hacked from the natural gas company Nusantara Regas.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Nusantara_Regas&amp;amp;oldid=2205&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Corporate Environmental Hack Indonesia Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Nzf Dnr Feb2017.Tgz</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/nzf_dnr_feb2017.tgz/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/nzf_dnr_feb2017.tgz/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
NZF_DNR_feb2017.tgz Files relating to &amp;ldquo;illegal armed groups of terrorist organization Donetsk People&amp;rsquo;s Republic.&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE madUkrop$_Crew FILE SIZE 1.5 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES CyberGuerilla EDITOR NOTES
Hacked files from madUkrop$_Crew relating to &amp;ldquo;illegal armed groups of terrorist organization Donetsk People&amp;rsquo;s Republic.&amp;rdquo;
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=NZF_DNR_feb2017.tgz&amp;amp;oldid=1143&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Russia Ukraine</description></item><item><title>Oakland City Hall</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oakland_city_hall/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oakland_city_hall/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Oakland City Hall Internal documents from Oakland City Hall. The data includes policy documents, misconduct records and bank statements. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE PLAY FILE SIZE 11.7 GB and 600 GB How to Request Access MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Internal emails and files from Oakland City Hall, a mid-sized city in the San Francisco Bay area with a long history of human rights violations.</description></item><item><title>Oath Keepers</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oath_keepers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oath_keepers/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Oath Keepers Approximately 5 gigabytes of emails, chat logs, members and donor lists and other files from the servers of the Oath Keepers. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Southern Poverty Law Center EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 5 gigabytes of emails, chat logs, members and donor lists and other files from the servers of the Oath Keepers.</description></item><item><title>Oculus</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oculus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oculus/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Oculus The source code of the neural network (AI) scanner used by Russia&amp;rsquo;s censorship office to detect &amp;ldquo;objectionable&amp;rdquo; material online. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Belarusian Cyberpartisans FILE SIZE 7.85 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link
EDITOR NOTES See also Russian Censor Files The source code of the neural network (AI) scanner used by Russia&amp;rsquo;s censorship office to detect &amp;ldquo;objectionable&amp;rdquo; material online, such as &amp;ldquo;propaganda&amp;rdquo; relating to gender and sexuality, instructions on weapons or drugs, signs of extremism and terrorism and &amp;ldquo;misinformation&amp;rdquo; or disrespect that discredits official state sources.</description></item><item><title>Odebrecht</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odebrecht/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odebrecht/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Odrebrecht 390,000 application (non-employee) emails ranging from 2008 to 2022 and 365 fserver emails ranging from April 2021 to early May 2022 from Novonor, previously Odebrecht S.A. The fserver emails contain details of SWIFT transfers, including payments to their employees and lawyers in the United States. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil, Dominican Republic, United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 12.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Odin Intelligence</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odin_intelligence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odin_intelligence/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
ODIN Intelligence 19 GB including thousands of photos, audio recordings, reports and user information from ODIN Intelligence and SweepWizard, a pair of apps geared towards law enforcement that primarily target houseless people. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE All Cyber-cops Are Bastards FILE SIZE 19 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES VICE, Wired, TechCrunch EDITOR NOTES
19 GB including thousands of photos, audio recordings, reports and user information from ODIN Intelligence and SweepWizard, a pair of apps geared towards law enforcement that primarily target houseless people.</description></item><item><title>Office Of Industrial Economics, Thailand</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/office_of_industrial_economics_thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/office_of_industrial_economics_thailand/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Office of Industrial Economics, Thailand 831,722 emails from Thailand&amp;rsquo;s Office of Industrial, a department of the Ministry of Industry responsible for guidance on industry growth, economics and IT systems. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Thailand TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 197 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
831,722 emails from Thailand&amp;rsquo;s Office of Industrial, a department of the Ministry of Industry responsible for guidance on industry growth, economics and IT systems.</description></item><item><title>Optimeyes</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/optimeyes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/optimeyes/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
OptimEyes S3 buckets, git and database backups, and credentials from the risk assessment company OptimEyes. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE 4chan FILE SIZE 67.8 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
S3 buckets, git and database backups, and credentials from the risk assessment company OptimEyes.
Research Leaked data from tobacco giant Phillip Morris posted to 4chan (The Daily Dot)
Limited Distribution Due to the presence of critical AWS keys and other credentials, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Oryx Resources</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oryx_resources/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oryx_resources/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Oryx Resources Hacked emails from the Venezuelan oil company owned by Samark Lopez, a company linked to several corruption cases. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Venezuela TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 133 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Hacked emails from the Venezuelan oil company owned by Samark Lopez, a company linked to several corruption cases.</description></item><item><title>Parkland</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/parkland/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/parkland/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Parkland Nearly 750 gigabytes (uncompressed) hacked from one of Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest gas station and convenience store chains. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Canada TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 499 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 750 gigabytes (uncompressed) hacked from one of Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest gas station and convenience store chains.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Petrofort</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/petrofort/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/petrofort/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Petrofort Approximately 300,000 emails from Petrofort, one of the largest office spaces and business centers in Saint Petersburg. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 244 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 300,000 emails from Petrofort, one of the largest office spaces and business centers in Saint Petersburg.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Petrolimex</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/petrolimex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/petrolimex/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Petrolimex 52 gigabytes from the Vietnam National Petroleum Group, which makes up 50% of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s petroleum market and is active in the fields of engineering, installation, mechanical and oil equipment DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Vietnam TYPE Hack SOURCE BlackByte FILE SIZE 52 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
52 gigabytes from the Vietnam National Petroleum Group, which makes up 50% of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s petroleum market and is active in the fields of engineering, installation, mechanical and oil equipment.</description></item><item><title>Petroworks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/petroworks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/petroworks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Petroworks 450 gigabytes of files and emails from Petroworks, which provides well drilling services and drilling equipment to Oil, Gas and Energy industries. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Colombia, Ecuador TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 447 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
450 gigabytes of files and emails from Petroworks, which provides well drilling services and drilling equipment to Oil, Gas and Energy industries.</description></item><item><title>Planatol</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/planatol/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/planatol/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Planatol Emails, documents and databases from industrial manufacturer Planatol. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 47.24 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Emails, documents and databases from industrial manufacturer Planatol.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Planatol&amp;amp;oldid=2216&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Corporate Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Podesta Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/podesta_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/podesta_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Podesta emails A manual scrape of the Podesta emails, hacked by Russian state actors. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE DCLeaks FILE SIZE 3.3 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Includes WikiLeaks&amp;rsquo; duplicates. A manual scrape of the Podesta emails, hacked by Russian state actors.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Podesta_emails&amp;amp;oldid=2217&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Allegations of State Sponsorship Hack Organization United States of America</description></item><item><title>Polar Branch Of The Russian Federal Research Institute Of Fisheries And Oceanography</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/polar_branch_of_the_russian_federal_research_institute_of_fisheries_and_oceanography/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/polar_branch_of_the_russian_federal_research_institute_of_fisheries_and_oceanography/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Polar Branch of the Russian Federal Research Institute of Fisheries and Oceanography 466 GB of emails from the Polar Branch of the Russian Federal Research Institute of Fisheries and Oceanography, whose studies determine the total allowable catch of different forms of commercial sea life. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE B00da, Porteur FILE SIZE 466 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Part One, Part Two, Part Three, Part Four TORRENT Part One, Part Two, Part Three, Part Four DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>PolicíA Nacional Civil De El Salvador</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/polic%C3%ADa_nacional_civil_de_el_salvador/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/polic%C3%ADa_nacional_civil_de_el_salvador/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Policía Nacional Civil de El Salvador Over 10 million emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Policía Nacional Civil de El Salvador (National Civil Police of El Salvador). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES El Salvador TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 6.8 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Over 10 million emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Policía Nacional Civil de El Salvador (National Civil Police of El Salvador).</description></item><item><title>Port And Railway Projects Service Of Jsc Ummc</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/port_and_railway_projects_service_of_jsc_ummc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/port_and_railway_projects_service_of_jsc_ummc/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Port and Railway Projects Service of JSC UMMC 77,500 emails from Port and Railway Projects Service of JSC UMMC / Служба по портовым и железнодорожным проектам (ОАО УГМК), which operates the two largest ports in Russia specializing in coal shipments. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 106 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Prav.Cmr@Gmail.Com</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/prav.cmr@gmail.com/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/prav.cmr@gmail.com/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
[email protected] Emails from Jana Salmin, tied to Russian operations in Ukraine. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE MadUkrop$_Crew FILE SIZE 209 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES CyberGuerilla EDITOR NOTES
Emails from Jana Salmin, tied to Russian operations in Ukraine, hacked by MadUkrop$_Crew.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/[[email protected]]&amp;amp;oldid=1144&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Russia Ukraine</description></item><item><title>Presque Isle Police Department</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/presque_isle_police_department/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/presque_isle_police_department/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Presque Isle Police Department Nearly 200 gigabytes of data hacked from Presque Isle Police Department. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Avaddon FILE SIZE 195 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 200 gigabytes of data hacked from Presque Isle Police Department, including over 15,000 emails. About 10% of the cache is the department&amp;rsquo;s music collection.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Pricewaterhousecoopers</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pricewaterhousecoopers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pricewaterhousecoopers/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from PricewaterhouseCoopers)]
RELEASE
PWC Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Prime Minister Of Iraq'S Office</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/prime_minister_of_iraqs_office/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/prime_minister_of_iraqs_office/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Prime Minister of Iraq&amp;rsquo;s office 2,500 emails from the Prime Minister of Iraq&amp;rsquo;s office DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Iraq TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 1.2 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link
EDITOR NOTES
2,500 emails from the Prime Minister of Iraq&amp;rsquo;s office sent between March 2021 and April 2022. The emails document the daily business of the office while Mustafa Al-Kadhimi (مصطفى عبد اللطيف مشتت) held it.</description></item><item><title>Private Office Of Sheikh Hazza Bin Zayed Al Nahyan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/private_office_of_sheikh_hazza_bin_zayed_al_nahyan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/private_office_of_sheikh_hazza_bin_zayed_al_nahyan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Private Office of Sheikh Hazza bin Zayed Al Nahyan 153,584 emails from the Private Office of Sheikh Hazza bin Zayed Al Nahyan, the former National Security Advisor of the United Arab Emirates (UAE) and the brother of the UAE&amp;rsquo;s newly appointed President. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United Arab Emirates TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 280.9 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Procuradoria Geral Da Fazenda Nacional</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/procuradoria-geral_da_fazenda_nacional/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/procuradoria-geral_da_fazenda_nacional/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Henning Harders 3.1 gigabytes hacked from Brazil&amp;rsquo;s Procuradoria Geral da Fazenda Nacional. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Everest FILE SIZE 3.1 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
3.1 gigabytes hacked from Brazil&amp;rsquo;s Procuradoria Geral da Fazenda Nacional.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Procuradoria-Geral_da_Fazenda_Nacional&amp;amp;oldid=2222&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Brazil Hack Ransomware</description></item><item><title>Pscb</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pscb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pscb/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
PSCB 229,000 emails and 630,000 files from the Petersburg Social Commercial Bank / Петербургский социальный коммерческий банк, one of the top 100 Russian banks in terms of net assets. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE NB65 FILE SIZE 542 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
229,000 emails and 630,000 files from the Petersburg Social Commercial Bank / Петербургский социальный коммерческий банк, one of the top 100 Russian banks in terms of net assets.</description></item><item><title>Pt Rea Kaltim Plantations And Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pt_rea_kaltim_plantations_and_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pt_rea_kaltim_plantations_and_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
PT Rea Kaltim Plantations and Group 314,055 hacked emails from PT Rea Kaltim Plantations and Group, which has been the subject of a number of protests, conflicts and allegations of human rights violations. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Indonesia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 277 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Enlace Hacktivista simultaneously published the data 314,055 hacked emails from PT Rea Kaltim Plantations and Group, a palm oil company in Indonesia which has been the subject of a number of protests, conflicts and allegations of human rights violations.</description></item><item><title>Public Chamber Of The Krasnoyarsk</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/public_chamber_of_the_krasnoyarsk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/public_chamber_of_the_krasnoyarsk/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Public Chamber of the Krasnoyarsk 69,000 emails from the Public Chamber of the Krasnoyarsk, the largest city in Krasnoyarsk Krai, Russia. Krasnoyarsk is an important junction of the Trans-Siberian Railway, and is one of the largest producers of aluminium in the country. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Porteur, B00da FILE SIZE 41.1 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [Link] TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Pwc</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pwc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pwc/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
PWC Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Quiborax</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/quiborax/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/quiborax/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Quiborax Hacked emails from a Chilean mining company whose activities threaten protected areas. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Chile TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 522 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Hacked emails from a Chilean mining company whose activities threaten protected areas.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Quiborax&amp;amp;oldid=2226&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Chile Corporate Environmental Extractivist Leaks Hack</description></item><item><title>Rosatom</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/rosatom/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/rosatom/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Rosatom / Росатом 15 gigabytes of files allegedly hacked from the Rosatom State Nuclear Energy Corporation, including information on Techsnabexport / Техснабэкспорт, commonly known as TENEX. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 15.3 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
15 gigabytes of files allegedly hacked from the Rosatom State Nuclear Energy Corporation, including information on Techsnabexport / Техснабэкспорт, commonly known as TENEX, which exports uranium and provides uranium enrichment services for foreign reactors.</description></item><item><title>Roskomnadzor</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/roskomnadzor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/roskomnadzor/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Roskomnadzor / Роскомнадзор | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Over 360,000 files from | | | Roskomnadzor, the Russian agency | | | responsible for monitoring, | | | controlling and censoring Russian | | | mass media. | | | | | | | | | Более 360,000 файлов | | | Роскомнадзора, Российского | | | агентства, отвечающего за | | | наблюдение, контроль и цензуру | | | СМИ России.</description></item><item><title>Roskomnadzor 2.0 (Grfc)</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/roskomnadzor_2.0_grfc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/roskomnadzor_2.0_grfc/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Roskomnadzor 2.0 (GRFC))]
RELEASE
[RussianCensorFiles] Documents and correspondence from the internal network of the General Radio Frequency Center (GRFC) subdivision of Roskomnadzor. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Belarusian Cyberpartisans FILE SIZE 335 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES See also Roskomnadzor Documents and correspondence from the internal network of the General Radio Frequency Center (GRFC) subdivision of Roskomnadzor.</description></item><item><title>Roskomnadzor Moscow</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/roskomnadzor_moscow/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/roskomnadzor_moscow/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Roskomnadzor Moscow / Роскомнадзор Nearly 500 GB of files from the Moscow office of censorship, including meeting notes, audio recordings, written exchanges, and e-mails. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Kiborg News FILE SIZE 489 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES See also Roskomnadzor and Russian Censor Files Nearly 500 GB of files from the Moscow office of Federal Service for Supervision of Communications, Information Technology and Mass Media, which is responsible for monitoring and censorship of the internet and other mass communications.</description></item><item><title>Rostproekt</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/rostproekt/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/rostproekt/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
RostProekt 2.4 gigabytes of emails allegedly hacked from the Russian construction company RostProekt / РостПроект. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 2.4 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
2.4 gigabytes of emails allegedly hacked from the Russian construction company RostProekt / РостПроект.
Disclaimer This dataset was released in the buildup to, in the midst of, or in the aftermath of a cyberwar or hybrid war.</description></item><item><title>Russian Interior Ministry</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/russian_interior_ministry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/russian_interior_ministry/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Russian Interior Ministry The complete hack of the Russian Interior Ministry. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Ukrainian Cyber Troops FILE SIZE 67.6 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES BBC News, InformNapalm, Foreign Policy EDITOR NOTES
The complete hack of the Russian Interior Ministry, including documentation of Russian aggression against Ukraine.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Russian_Interior_Ministry&amp;amp;oldid=2485&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Russia Ukraine</description></item><item><title>Russiancensorfiles</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/russiancensorfiles/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/russiancensorfiles/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
[RussianCensorFiles] Documents and correspondence from the internal network of the General Radio Frequency Center (GRFC) subdivision of Roskomnadzor. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Belarusian Cyberpartisans FILE SIZE 335 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES See also Roskomnadzor Documents and correspondence from the internal network of the General Radio Frequency Center (GRFC) subdivision of Roskomnadzor. GRFC monitors social media and other open sources in order to implement the Kremlin censorship and provide data for decision makers.</description></item><item><title>Saltos Del Francoli</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/saltos_del_francoli/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/saltos_del_francoli/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Saltos del Francoli 3.8 gigabytes hacked from the Panamanian hydroelectric company Saltos del Francolí, S.A. (SDF Energy Group), involved in the Los Planetas project. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Panama TYPE Hack SOURCE LockBit FILE SIZE 2.48 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
3.8 gigabytes hacked from the Panamanian hydroelectric company Saltos del Francolí, S.A. (SDF Energy Group), involved in the Los Planetas project.</description></item><item><title>Salvini Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/salvini_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/salvini_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Salvini emails Thousands of emails from Italy&amp;rsquo;s fascist Deputy Prime Minister, Matteo Salvini and the Noi con Salvini political party. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Italy TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 5 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Motherboard, CyberGuerilla EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of emails from Italy&amp;rsquo;s fascist Deputy Prime Minister, Matteo Salvini and the Noi con Salvini political party.</description></item><item><title>Sawatzky</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sawatzky/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sawatzky/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Sawatzky 575,000 emails from a property management company. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 432 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
575,000 emails from a property management company.
Sawatzky&amp;rsquo;s clients include Du Pont, Lenovo, Whirlpool, Aveva, Wella, Johnson + Johnson, Cisco, Google, Swatch, Avito, Samsung, Microsoft, Western Union, Saint-gobain, Turkish Airlines, and British American Tobacco.</description></item><item><title>Sberbank Of Russia</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sberbank_of_russia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sberbank_of_russia/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Sberbank of Russia Over 13,500 files hacked from Sberbank of Russia&amp;rsquo;s translation bureau. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States, Russia, Ukraine TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 2.1 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Over 13,500 files hacked from Sberbank of Russia&amp;rsquo;s translation bureau, providing a unique insight into the interests of the bank and its clients. Translations include political analysis, military sales, and open source reporting.</description></item><item><title>SecretaríA De La Defensa Nacional De MéXico</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/secretar%C3%ADa_de_la_defensa_nacional_de_m%C3%A9xico/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/secretar%C3%ADa_de_la_defensa_nacional_de_m%C3%A9xico/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Secretaría de la Defensa Nacional de México 6 TB of emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Secretaría de la Defensa Nacional de México (SEDENA), the Secretariat of National Defense of Mexico. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Mexico TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 6 TB DOWNLOADS: Request Access MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista 6 TB of emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Secretaría de la Defensa Nacional de México (SEDENA) (Secretariat of National Defense of Mexico).</description></item><item><title>Shell</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/shell/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/shell/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Shell Over 100 gigabytes hacked from the Shell global group of energy and petrochemical companies. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 104 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 100 gigabytes hacked from the Shell global group of energy and petrochemical companies.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Shell&amp;amp;oldid=2235&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Corporate Environmental Hack Ransomware United States of America</description></item><item><title>Sherwood</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sherwood/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sherwood/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Sherwood Copies of the servers of the Cayman National Bank and Trust (Isle of Man). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Cayman Islands TYPE Hack SOURCE Phineas Fisher FILE SIZE 2.26 TB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Unicorn Riot EDITOR NOTES
Copies of the servers of the Cayman National Bank and Trust (Isle of Man) via the hacktivist sometimes known as Phineas Fisher.</description></item><item><title>Sholtai Boltai</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sholtai_boltai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/sholtai_boltai/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
The majority of the b0ltai files, which through a series of hacks expose Russian oligarchs and decision makers. Some have alleged that sholtai boltai&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the Russian government began before the associated arrests, though this remains unconfirmed.
RELEASE
Sholtai Boltai The majority of the b0ltai files, which through a series of hacks expose Russian oligarchs and decision makers. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE b0ltai FILE SIZE 8.</description></item><item><title>Shooting Sheriffs Saturday</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/shooting_sheriffs_saturday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/shooting_sheriffs_saturday/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Shooting Sheriffs Saturday An AntiSec hack of sheriffs&amp;rsquo; offices. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE AntiSec FILE SIZE 7.4 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES PasteBin EDITOR NOTES
An AntiSec hack of sheriffs&amp;rsquo; offices.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Shooting_Sheriffs_Saturday&amp;amp;oldid=2237&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Anonymous Hack United States of America</description></item><item><title>Socar Energoresource</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/socar_energoresource/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/socar_energoresource/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
SOCAR Energoresource 116,500 emails SOCAR Energoresource / ООО Сокар энергоресурс, which operates the Antipinsky Refinery and several oilfields. SOCAR Energoresource works directly with Gazprom, Rosneft and Lukoil and is partially owned by the State Oil Company of Azerbaijan Republic (SOCAR). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 130 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Special State Protection Service Of Azerbaijan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/special_state_protection_service_of_azerbaijan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/special_state_protection_service_of_azerbaijan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Special State Protection Service of Azerbaijan Passport scans, reports, confidential shareholder documents, account statements, letters of credit, and details of oil drilling technologies. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Azerbaijan TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 1 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Files hacked by Anonymous and originally posted to the now-defunct Par:AnoIA leak platform. The cache contains passport scans, reports, confidential shareholder documents, account statements, letters of credit, and details of oil drilling technologies.</description></item><item><title>Special:Categories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialcategories/</guid><description>Help
The following categories exist on the wiki, and may or may not be unused. Also see wanted categories.
[Categories]
[Display categories starting at:]
[Show]
(first | last) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Allegations of State Sponsorship‏‎ (22 members) Angola‏‎ (1 member) Anonymous‏‎ (86 members) Argentina‏‎ (4 members) Australia‏‎ (4 members) Azerbaijan‏‎ (2 members) Bahamas‏‎ (0 members) Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box‏‎ (25 members) Belarus‏‎ (2 members) Belgium‏‎ (1 member) Bolivia‏‎ (1 member) Brazil‏‎ (11 members) Bulgaria‏‎ (1 member) Cambodia‏‎ (1 member) Canada‏‎ (4 members) Cayman Islands‏‎ (1 member) Chile‏‎ (6 members) China‏‎ (2 members) Colombia‏‎ (6 members) Cook Islands‏‎ (1 member) Corporate‏‎ (136 members) Cyberwar‏‎ (54 members) Cyprus‏‎ (1 member) Dominican Republic‏‎ (1 member) Ecuador‏‎ (3 members) El Salvador‏‎ (3 members) Environmental‏‎ (41 members) Estonia‏‎ (1 member) Ethiopia‏‎ (1 member) European Union‏‎ (2 members) Extractivist Leaks‏‎ (7 members) Fascist‏‎ (23 members) France‏‎ (3 members) Fuerzas Represivas‏‎ (7 members) Germany‏‎ (5 members) Guatemala‏‎ (2 members) Guinea Ecuatorial‏‎ (1 member) Hack‏‎ (216 members) Iceland‏‎ (1 member) India‏‎ (1 member) Indonesia‏‎ (4 members) Iran‏‎ (4 members) Iraq‏‎ (1 member) Italy‏‎ (6 members) Jordan‏‎ (1 member) Leak‏‎ (24 members) Leak Markets‏‎ (3 members) Limited Distribution‏‎ (84 members) Mexico‏‎ (1 member) MilicoLeaks‏‎ (2 members) (first | last) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Special:Mostlinkedcategories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialmostlinkedcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialmostlinkedcategories/</guid><description>Showing below up to 50 results in range #1 to #50.
View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Hack‏‎ (216 members) Corporate‏‎ (136 members) Anonymous‏‎ (86 members) Limited Distribution‏‎ (84 members) United States of America‏‎ (72 members) Russia‏‎ (65 members) Cyberwar‏‎ (54 members) Ransomware‏‎ (53 members) Environmental‏‎ (41 members) Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box‏‎ (25 members) Leak‏‎ (24 members) Organization‏‎ (24 members) Fascist‏‎ (23 members) Allegations of State Sponsorship‏‎ (22 members) Brazil‏‎ (11 members) Researchers‏‎ (10 members) Ukraine‏‎ (8 members) Extractivist Leaks‏‎ (7 members) Fuerzas Represivas‏‎ (7 members) Italy‏‎ (6 members) Chile‏‎ (6 members) Scrape‏‎ (6 members) Colombia‏‎ (6 members) Germany‏‎ (5 members) Australia‏‎ (4 members) Iran‏‎ (4 members) Argentina‏‎ (4 members) United Kingdom‏‎ (4 members) Myanmar‏‎ (4 members) Indonesia‏‎ (4 members) Canada‏‎ (4 members) Thailand‏‎ (3 members) Syria‏‎ (3 members) Turkey‏‎ (3 members) France‏‎ (3 members) Paraguay‏‎ (3 members) Peru‏‎ (3 members) Leak Markets‏‎ (3 members) El Salvador‏‎ (3 members) Ecuador‏‎ (3 members) China‏‎ (2 members) European Union‏‎ (2 members) Azerbaijan‏‎ (2 members) Panama‏‎ (2 members) Venezuela‏‎ (2 members) Belarus‏‎ (2 members) Guatemala‏‎ (2 members) MilicoLeaks‏‎ (2 members) Angola‏‎ (1 member) Bulgaria‏‎ (1 member) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Special:Randomrootpage</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialrandomrootpage/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialrandomrootpage/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
OSCE Vienna Hacked materials from the Organization for Security and Cooperation in Europe, released to help bring attention to attempts to influence Ukrainian elections. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Ukraine TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 250 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Hacked materials from the Organization for Security and Cooperation in Europe, released to help bring attention to attempts to influence Ukrainian elections.</description></item><item><title>Special:Uncategorizedcategories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialuncategorizedcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialuncategorizedcategories/</guid><description>Help
Showing below up to 50 results in range #1 to #50.
View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Allegations of State Sponsorship Angola Anonymous Argentina Australia Azerbaijan Bahamas Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box Belarus Belgium Bolivia Brazil Bulgaria Cambodia Canada Cayman Islands Chile China Colombia Cook Islands Corporate Cyberwar Cyprus Dominican Republic Ecuador El Salvador Environmental Estonia Ethiopia European Union Extractivist Leaks Fascist France Fuerzas Represivas Germany Guatemala Guinea Ecuatorial Hack Iceland India Indonesia Iran Iraq Italy Jordan Leak Leak Markets Limited Distribution Mexico MilicoLeaks View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Spyhide</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/spyhide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/spyhide/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
SpyHide Source code and user data for the Android spyware software SpyHide. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Germany, Iran TYPE Hack SOURCE maia arson crimew FILE SIZE 100 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES maia arson crimew EDITOR NOTES
Source code and user data for the Android spyware software SpyHide dating from 2016 through mid-July 2023.
Although SpyHide&amp;rsquo;s software was made in Iran and the servers were hosted in Germany, TechCrunch&amp;rsquo;s analysis identified at least 750,000 users and about 60,000 compromised devices in a surveillance network that spans every continent.</description></item><item><title>Staminus</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/staminus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/staminus/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Staminus Hacked data from Staminus Communications and their clients, including the Ku Klux Klan. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 47.9 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Gizmodo, Ars Technica EDITOR NOTES
Hacked data from Staminus Communications, a hosting provider that specializes in DDoS protection and whose clients included the Ku Klux Klan.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Staminus&amp;amp;oldid=2242&amp;rdquo;
Categories:</description></item><item><title>Stratfor Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/stratfor_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/stratfor_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Stratfor emails 5 million emails hacked from Stratfor by Anonymous and provided to WikiLeaks. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 23.6 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Archive produced by WikiLeaks and presented as-is. 5 million emails hacked from Stratfor by Anonymous and provided to WikiLeaks.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Stratfor_emails&amp;amp;oldid=2243&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Allegations of State Sponsorship Anonymous Hack Organization</description></item><item><title>Syrian Ministry Of Foreign Affairs</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/syrian_ministry_of_foreign_affairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/syrian_ministry_of_foreign_affairs/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Syrian Ministry of Foreign Affairs Internal government emails from the Syrian Ministry of Foreign Affair, including details about cargo flights from Russia, each containing 30 tons of Syrian cash. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Syria TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 685 MB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hacker News EDITOR NOTES
Internal government emails from the Syrian Ministry of Foreign Affair, including details about cargo flights from Russia, each containing 30 tons of Syrian cash.</description></item><item><title>Technoserv</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/technoserv/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/technoserv/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Technoserv Approximately 1.2 TB of files from Technoserv, a group of IT companies specializing in system integration, networking and cloud services, information security, and datamining. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Национальная республиканская армия / National Republican Army (of Russia) FILE SIZE 1.2 TB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES KyivPost EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 1.2 TB of files from Technoserv (now T1 Integration), a group of IT companies specializing in system integration, networking and cloud services, information security, and datamining.</description></item><item><title>Technotec</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/technotec/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/technotec/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Technotec 495,000 emails from the Russian firm Technotec, which provides oil and gas field services to companies including Rosneft and Gazprom Neft. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 440 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
495,000 emails from the Russian firm Technotec, which has provided oil and gas field services along with chemical reagents used in oil production and transportation to companies including Rosneft and Gazprom Neft since 1995.</description></item><item><title>Tejucana</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tejucana/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tejucana/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Tejucana Hacked emails from the Brazilian mining company, Tejucana. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 96 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET [[Link]] TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Hacked emails from the Brazilian mining company, Tejucana.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Tejucana&amp;amp;oldid=2249&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Brazil Corporate Environmental Extractivist Leaks Hack</description></item><item><title>Tendertech</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tendertech/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tendertech/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Tendertech 426,000 emails from Tendertech / Тендертех, a firm specializing in processing financial and banking documents on behalf of businesses and entrepreneurs. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 160 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
426,000 emails from Tendertech / Тендертех, a firm specializing in processing financial and banking documents on behalf of businesses and entrepreneurs.</description></item><item><title>Tetraedr</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tetraedr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tetraedr/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Tetraedr | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | .thumbinner style=&amp;ldquo;width:302px;&amp;rdquo;} | | | [![Anonymous Liberland and the | | | Pwn-Bär Hack Team Pom-Bear Mascot | | | About us Greetings citizens of | | | the world. Let us introduce | | | ourselves&amp;hellip; We are the Pwn-Bär | | | international hack team. We stand | | | for equal opportunity pwnage and | | | unrestricted access to | | | information.</description></item><item><title>Thailand Judicial Management Database</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thailand_judicial_management_database/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thailand_judicial_management_database/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Thailand Judicial Management Database A database of Thai judicial employees. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Thailand TYPE Hack SOURCE Blink Hacker Group FILE SIZE 106 MB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES DataBreaches.net EDITOR NOTES Limited Distribution A database of Thai judicial employees.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)</description></item><item><title>Thozis Corp</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thozis_corp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thozis_corp/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Thozis Corp. 5,500 emails from Thozis Corp., a Russian investment firm owned by Zakhar Smushkin, which is involved in the project to build a satellite city in Saint Petersburg. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 5.9 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
5,500 emails from Thozis Corp., a Russian investment firm owned by Zakhar Smushkin (number 2,674 on Forbes&amp;rsquo; billionaire list), which is involved in the project to build the Yuzhny satellite city in Saint Petersburg.</description></item><item><title>Thsa</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thsa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thsa/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
THSA TH Company (THSA), an industrial solutions company. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 37.2 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
TH Company (THSA), an industrial solutions company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)</description></item><item><title>Toll Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/toll_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/toll_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Toll Group 84 gigabytes hacked from an Australian transportation and logistics company with operations in road, rail, sea, air and warehousing. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 150 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
150 gigabytes hacked from an Australian transportation and logistics company with operations in road, rail, sea, air and warehousing. A subsidiary of Japan Post Holdings, the company has three divisions; Global Express, Global Forwarding, and Global Logistics.</description></item><item><title>Transneft</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/transneft/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/transneft/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Transneft / Транснефть 79,000 emails from the OMEGA Company, the R&amp;amp;D department of Russia&amp;rsquo;s state-controlled pipeline company, Transneft. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 79 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link MORE REFERENCES American Sanctions EDITOR NOTES Dedicated by the source to Hillary Clinton 79,000 emails from the OMEGA Company, the R&amp;amp;D department of Russia&amp;rsquo;s state-controlled pipeline company, Transneft / Транснефть.</description></item><item><title>Trust Capital Funding</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/trust_capital_funding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/trust_capital_funding/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Trust Capital Funding Over 230 gigabytes from the financing company Trust Capital Funding, which provides funding for commercial real estate, franchise startups and businesses as well as merchant processing and other banking products. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE BlackMatter FILE SIZE 233 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 230 gigabytes from the financing company Trust Capital Funding, which provides funding for commercial real estate, franchise startups and businesses as well as merchant processing and other banking products.</description></item><item><title>Truth Will Out Films Customer Database</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/truth_will_out_films_customer_database/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/truth_will_out_films_customer_database/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Truth Will Out Films Customer Database A 2019 database containing full customer information for the neo-Nazi film shop, Truth Will Out Films. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 89 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A 2019 database containing full customer information for the neo-Nazi film shop, Truth Will Out Films.
Due to the PII in the dataset, it is only being offered to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Twitch</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/twitch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/twitch/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Twitch 125 gigabytes of source code, internal tools and user payout information from the streaming platform Twitch. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE 4chan FILE SIZE 125 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES The files were initially released by the hackers independent of DDoSecrets and are presented as-is. 125 gigabytes of source code, internal tools and user payout information from the streaming platform Twitch.</description></item><item><title>United Northern And Southern Knights Of The Ku Klux Klan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/united_northern_and_southern_knights_of_the_ku_klux_klan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/united_northern_and_southern_knights_of_the_ku_klux_klan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
United Northern and Southern Knights of the Ku Klux Klan &amp;ldquo;Everything you wanted to know about the United Northern and Southern Knights of the Ku Klux Klan&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 424 KB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
&amp;ldquo;Everything you wanted to know about the United Northern and Southern Knights of the Ku Klux Klan&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Varela Leaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/varela_leaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/varela_leaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Varela Leaks Hacked messages from the President of Panama, Juan Carlos Varela. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Panama TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 24.9 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Prensa Latina CNN The Panama News EDITOR NOTES
Hacked messages from the President of Panama, Juan Carlos Varela implicating him in several scandals and apparent coups.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Varela_Leaks&amp;amp;oldid=2257&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Panama</description></item><item><title>Very English Coop D'Etat</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/very_english_coop_detat/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/very_english_coop_detat/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Very English Coop d&amp;rsquo;Etat Thousands of emails allegedly from Brexist supporters including former British spymaster Richard Dearlove, campaigner Gisela Stuart, historian Robert Tombs, and others. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United Kingdom TYPE Hack SOURCE Suspected to be Russian FILE SIZE 25.4 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Reuters EDITOR NOTES According to Google&amp;rsquo;s Threat Analysis Group, the leak is linked to a group they knew as &amp;ldquo;Cold River,&amp;rdquo; a Russia-based hacking group.</description></item><item><title>Vgtrk</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/vgtrk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/vgtrk/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
VGTRK Over 20 years and 900,000 emails from VGTRK / ВГТРК (All-Russia State Television and Radio Broadcasting Company / Всероссийская государственная телевизионная и радиовещательная компания), a Russian state-owned broadcaster which operates five national TV stations, two international networks, five radio stations, and over 80 regional TV and radio networks. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE NB65 FILE SIZE 786.2 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Mail, Files TORRENT Mail, Files DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES</description></item><item><title>Virginia Department Of Military Affairs</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/virginia_department_of_military_affairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/virginia_department_of_military_affairs/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Virginia Department of Military Affairs Two gigabytes of emails hacked from the Virginia Department of Military Affairs and released by the dark marketplace Marketo. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Marketo FILE SIZE 2 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Two gigabytes consisting of emails hacked from the Virginia Department of Military Affairs and released by the dark marketplace Marketo.</description></item><item><title>Vyberi Radio</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/vyberi_radio/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/vyberi_radio/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Vyberi Radio 1.5 million emails from the Vyberi Radio / Выбери Радио group, which operates around 100 radio stations in 18 cities throughout Russia, with over 8 million listeners. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 823 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
1.5 million emails from the Vyberi Radio / Выбери Радио group of companies, which operates around 100 radio stations in 18 cities throughout Russia, with over 8 million listeners.</description></item><item><title>W.L. Contractors</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/w.l._contractors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/w.l._contractors/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
W.L. Contractors 15 gigabytes hacked from a Colorado based traffic signal, Intelligent Transportation Systems, and CCTV contractor. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 15 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
15 gigabytes hacked from a based traffic signal, ITS (Intelligent Transportation Systems), and CCTV contractor operating throughout Colorado and Wyoming.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>W&amp;T Offshore</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/wt_offshore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/wt_offshore/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
W&amp;amp;T Offshore 19 gigabytes hacked from W&amp;amp;T Offshore, an independent oil and natural gas producer, exploring, developing, and acquiring oil and natural gas in the Gulf of Mexico. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 19 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
19 gigabytes hacked from W&amp;amp;T Offshore, an independent oil and natural gas producer, exploring, developing, and acquiring oil and natural gas in the Gulf of Mexico.</description></item><item><title>Washington County Sheriff</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_county_sheriff/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_county_sheriff/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Washington County Sheriff 1,311 files hacked from the Washington County Sheriff by ransomware operator Conti. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Conti FILE SIZE 419 MB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
1,311 files hacked from the Washington County Sheriff by ransomware operator Conti.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Washington D.C. Metropolitan Pd</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Washington D.C. Metropolitan PD)]
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Washington D.C. Metropolitan Pd</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Washington D.C. Metropolitan PD)]
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Webdetetive</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/webdetetive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/webdetetive/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
WebDetetive 150,000 files from the spyware reseller WebDetetive DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 1.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
150,000 files from the spyware reseller WebDetetive, a phone monitoring app typically installed on phones without the user&amp;rsquo;s consent (or even knowledge). The software uploads the contents of the user&amp;rsquo;s phone to its servers, messages, call logs, phone call recordings, photos, ambient recordings from the phone&amp;rsquo;s microphone and GPS data.</description></item><item><title>Worldwide Invest</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/worldwide_invest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/worldwide_invest/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Worldwide Invest Nearly 250,000 emails from Worldwide Invest / ВОРЛДВАЙД ИНВЕСТ АС, an investment firms with ties to Estonia and Russian railways. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 130 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Link TORRENT Link DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 250,000 emails from Worldwide Invest / ВОРЛДВАЙД ИНВЕСТ АС, an investment firms with ties to Estonia and Russian railways.</description></item><item><title>Роскомнадзор</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BC%D0%BD%D0%B0%D0%B4%D0%B7%D0%BE%D1%80/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BC%D0%BD%D0%B0%D0%B4%D0%B7%D0%BE%D1%80/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Роскомнадзор)]
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Roskomnadzor / Роскомнадзор | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Over 360,000 files from | | | Roskomnadzor, the Russian agency | | | responsible for monitoring, | | | controlling and censoring Russian | | | mass media. | | | | | | | | | Более 360,000 файлов | | | Роскомнадзора, Российского | | | агентства, отвечающего за | | | наблюдение, контроль и цензуру | | | СМИ России.</description></item><item><title>29 Leaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/29-leaks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/29-leaks/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.
Background Formations House, now The London Office, facilitates international money laundering by taking advantage of the lax regulatory framework of the United Kingdom and many of its former colonies.
Journalist Oliver Bullough first wrote about Formations House in the Guardian in 2016, then in his book Moneyland: The Inside Story of the Crooks and Kleptocrats Who Rule the World.</description></item><item><title>Blueleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/blueleaks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/blueleaks/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.</description></item><item><title>National Police of Paraguay</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/national-police-of-paraguay/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/national-police-of-paraguay/</guid><description>Over 500,000 internal documents and images from the National Police of Paraguay (Policía Nacional del Paraguay), and 175 gigabytes of SQL databases.
The data includes documents from the Internal Affairs Directorate (Dirección de Asuntos Internos), the Identification Department (Departamento de Identificaciones) and the Foreigners Registry Department (Departamento Registro de Extranjeros), Technology and Development Division (Division de Tecnologia y Desarrollo), as well as other documents including orders from command, photographs of evidence and documents about wanted individuals.</description></item><item><title>Prime Minister of Iraq's Office</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pm-of-iraq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pm-of-iraq/</guid><description>2,500 emails from the Prime Minister of Iraq&amp;rsquo;s office sent between March 2021 and April 2022. The emails document the daily business of the office while Mustafa Al-Kadhimi (مصطفى عبد اللطيف مشتت) held it.</description></item><item><title>Aqaba Company for Ports Operation &amp; Management, Jordan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/aqaba-company/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/aqaba-company/</guid><description>Over 50,000 emails from Jordan Aqaba Company for Ports Operation &amp;amp; Management, sent mostly between November 2019 and April 2022.
In 2004, the state-run Aqaba Development Corporation (ADC) acquired and took over the management and operation of the port on behalf of the Aqaba Special Economic Zone Authority (ASEZA). Management of the port is handled by the ADC&amp;rsquo;s Aqaba Company for Ports Operation and Management.</description></item><item><title>LetMeSpy</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/letmespy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/letmespy/</guid><description>Tens of thousands of database entries containing customer information, messages, call, GPS and other logs from devices compromised by the LetMeSpy stalkerware.
Research LetMeSpy, a phone tracking app spying on thousands, says it was hacked (TechCrunch)
Miscreants leak texts and info siphoned by Android stalkerware app LetMeSpy (The Register)
LetMeSpy data leak reveals users of digital stalking software (The Daily Dot)
#FuckStalkerware pt. 1 - the LetMeSpy hack (maia arson crimew)</description></item><item><title>PWC</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pwc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pwc/</guid><description>Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Sherwood</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/sherwood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/sherwood/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.</description></item></channel></rss>