<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>limited-distribution on DDoSecrets Wiki</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/limited-distribution/</link><description>Recent content in limited-distribution on DDoSecrets Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/limited-distribution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Washington D.C. Metropolitan Pd</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Washington D.C. Metropolitan PD)]
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>29 Leaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/29-leaks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/29-leaks/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.
Background Formations House, now The London Office, facilitates international money laundering by taking advantage of the lax regulatory framework of the United Kingdom and many of its former colonies.
Journalist Oliver Bullough first wrote about Formations House in the Guardian in 2016, then in his book Moneyland: The Inside Story of the Crooks and Kleptocrats Who Rule the World.</description></item><item><title>Blueleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/blueleaks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/blueleaks/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.</description></item><item><title>National Police of Paraguay</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/national-police-of-paraguay/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/national-police-of-paraguay/</guid><description>Over 500,000 internal documents and images from the National Police of Paraguay (Policía Nacional del Paraguay), and 175 gigabytes of SQL databases.
The data includes documents from the Internal Affairs Directorate (Dirección de Asuntos Internos), the Identification Department (Departamento de Identificaciones) and the Foreigners Registry Department (Departamento Registro de Extranjeros), Technology and Development Division (Division de Tecnologia y Desarrollo), as well as other documents including orders from command, photographs of evidence and documents about wanted individuals.</description></item><item><title>Prime Minister of Iraq's Office</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pm-of-iraq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pm-of-iraq/</guid><description>2,500 emails from the Prime Minister of Iraq&amp;rsquo;s office sent between March 2021 and April 2022. The emails document the daily business of the office while Mustafa Al-Kadhimi (مصطفى عبد اللطيف مشتت) held it.</description></item><item><title>LetMeSpy</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/letmespy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/letmespy/</guid><description>Tens of thousands of database entries containing customer information, messages, call, GPS and other logs from devices compromised by the LetMeSpy stalkerware.
Research LetMeSpy, a phone tracking app spying on thousands, says it was hacked (TechCrunch)
Miscreants leak texts and info siphoned by Android stalkerware app LetMeSpy (The Register)
LetMeSpy data leak reveals users of digital stalking software (The Daily Dot)
#FuckStalkerware pt. 1 - the LetMeSpy hack (maia arson crimew)</description></item><item><title>PWC</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pwc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pwc/</guid><description>Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item></channel></rss>