<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>limited-distribution on DDoSecrets Wiki</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/limited-distribution/</link><description>Recent content in limited-distribution on DDoSecrets Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/categories/limited-distribution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aban Offshore</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aban_offshore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aban_offshore/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Aban Offshore Approximately 14 gigabytes of files hacked by Nefilim from Aban Offshore drilling, India&amp;rsquo;s largest offshore drilling services provider to oil companies. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES India TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 14 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 14 gigabytes of files hacked by Nefilim from Aban Offshore drilling, India&amp;rsquo;s largest offshore drilling services provider to oil companies, mainly for ONGC.</description></item><item><title>Adopt A Trucker Founder Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/adopt_a_trucker_founder_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/adopt_a_trucker_founder_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE 250 MB of emails and attachments from the Adopt A Trucker campaign founder, Chris Garrah. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Canada TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 250 MB MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
250 MB of emails and attachments from the Protonmail account of Adopt A Trucker campaign founder, Chris Garrah. The emails run from February 7th through the morning of February 21st.
The source noted that while they were able to remove some malware from the original inbox, it is possible that some was missed.</description></item><item><title>Akp</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/akp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/akp/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
AKP Hacked materials from the AKP, including portions not published by WikiLeaks. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Turkey TYPE Hack SOURCE Phineas Fisher FILE SIZE 98.7 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES Release notes EDITOR NOTES
Hacked materials from the AKP, including portions not published by WikiLeaks.
Limited Distribution Due to privacy concerns and at the request of the source, only a small portion of the data is available to the public.</description></item><item><title>Aliansce Sonae</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aliansce_sonae/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aliansce_sonae/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Aliansce Sonae 31 GB hacked of hacked files from Aliansce Sonae Shopping Centers SA, a Brazil-based company principally engaged in the development and operating of shopping centers in Brazil. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 31 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
31 GB hacked of hacked files from Aliansce Sonae Shopping Centers SA, formerly known as Sonae Sierra Brasil SA, a Brazil-based company principally engaged in the development and operating of shopping centers in Brazil.</description></item><item><title>Aniballeaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aniballeaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/aniballeaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
AnibalLeaks A hacked database of Argentine military personnel. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Argentina TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 40 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A hacked database of Argentine military personnel.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.</description></item><item><title>Apex Mobile</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/apex_mobile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/apex_mobile/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Apex Mobile 25 GB from Apex Mobile, a set of apps used by &amp;ldquo;over 150 civic, law enforcement and fire agencies across the US and Canada&amp;rdquo; for reporting and collecting information. The data includes over 36,000 reports, 18,000 images, and at least 15,000 messages. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 25 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Arteris</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/arteris/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/arteris/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Arteris Over 60 gigabytes hacked from Arteris, which is responsible for the restoration, modernization, monitoring, maintenance, and operation of more than 3,250 km of Brazilian highways. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 61 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 60 gigabytes hacked from Arteris, which is responsible for the restoration, modernization, monitoring, maintenance, and operation of more than 3,250 km of Brazilian highways.</description></item><item><title>Ashley Madison</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ashley_madison/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ashley_madison/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ashley Madison The 93% complete copy of the email box of the CEO of Avid Life Media, the company behind the Ashley Madison scandal. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 28.7 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET Link TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES The non-email files have been withheld. The 93% complete copy of the email box of the CEO of Avid Life Media, the company behind the Ashley Madison scandal.</description></item><item><title>Azusa Police Department</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/azusa_police_department/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/azusa_police_department/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Azusa Police Department Approximately 3.5 gigabytes (uncompressed) of data hacked from the police department in Azusa, CA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE DoppelPaymer FILE SIZE 2.85 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 3.5 gigabytes (uncompressed) of data hacked from the police department in Azusa, CA by DoppelPaymer. The dataset includes 3 gigabytes of case files, 100 megabytes of forms and training materials from their jail, payroll information for 2018-2021, shift assignments for 2016-2021 and 100 megabytes of miscellaneous information.</description></item><item><title>Bedford County, Pa Emails</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bedford_county_pa_emails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bedford_county_pa_emails/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Bedford County, PA Emails 5,000 emails leaked from a government server in Bedford County, Pennsylvania with material dated through February 5, 2021. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Leak SOURCE Hollidaysburg Community Watchdog FILE SIZE 2.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
5,000 emails leaked from a government server in Bedford County, Pennsylvania with material dated through February 5, 2021.</description></item><item><title>Bmk</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bmk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bmk/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
BMK A Saudi financial company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Saudi Arabia TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 30.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A Saudi financial company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Bouygues Construction</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bouygues_construction/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/bouygues_construction/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Bouygues Construction 57 gigabytes hacked from Bouygues Construction, which operates in over sixty countries in the sectors of building, civil works and energies and services. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES France TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 57 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
57 gigabytes hacked from Bouygues Construction, which operates in over sixty countries in the sectors of building, civil works and energies and services.</description></item><item><title>Casagrande Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/casagrande_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/casagrande_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Casagrande Group Files hacked from a drilling and foundation equipment manufacturer. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Italy TYPE Hack SOURCE BlackMatter FILE SIZE 10.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Files hacked from a drilling and foundation equipment manufacturer.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)</description></item><item><title>Cellebrite Mobilogy</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cellebrite_mobilogy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cellebrite_mobilogy/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Cellebrite Mobilogy 3.6 TB of backend data from Cellebrite Mobilogy, previously Cellebrite&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Lifecycle Division. Mobilogy software can be used for device diagnostics, content transfer, backup and restorations. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 3.6 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
3.6 TB of backend data from Cellebrite Mobilogy, previously Cellebrite&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Lifecycle Division. Mobilogy software can be used for device diagnostics, content transfer, backup and restorations.</description></item><item><title>Cellebrite Team Foundation Server</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cellebrite_team_foundation_server/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cellebrite_team_foundation_server/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Cellebrite Team Foundation Server Backup files for Cellebrite&amp;rsquo;s Team Foundation Server, a collaboration environment that&amp;rsquo;s since been replaced by the Azure DevOps Server. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 430 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Backup files for Cellebrite&amp;rsquo;s Team Foundation Server, a collaboration environment that&amp;rsquo;s since been replaced by the Azure DevOps Server.
Limited Distribution Due to the potential for abuse, this data is only being made available to journalists and researchers at this time.</description></item><item><title>Citizengo</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/citizengo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/citizengo/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
CitizenGo Over 17,000 documents hacked from right wing campaigning organizations Grupo CitizenGO &amp;amp; HazteOir hacked by ACABGang. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE ACABGang FILE SIZE 24 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES These files are the unredacted version of WikiLeaks&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Intolerance Network&amp;rdquo;. See also CitizenGo &amp;amp; HatzeOir databases Over 17,000 documents from right wing campaigning organizations Grupo CitizenGO &amp;amp; HazteOir hacked by ACABGang.</description></item><item><title>Condie Construction Company</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/condie_construction_company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/condie_construction_company/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Condie Construction Company 57 gigabytes hacked from Condie Construction Company, which specializes in pipeline and infrastructure installation. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 57 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
57 gigabytes hacked from Condie Construction Company, a general engineering construction company specializing in pipeline and infrastructure installation. Their projects have budgets of up to $40 million and include culinary waterlines, sewer lines, pressurized irrigation pipelines, storm drainage, waster water treatment facilities, roadway reconstruction and new roadway construction.</description></item><item><title>Cosan</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cosan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cosan/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Cosan Over 100 gigabytes of hacked files from Cosan, a Brazilian conglomerate producer of bioethanol, sugar and energy. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil, Argentina, Bolivia, Paraguay, Uruguay TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 105 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 100 gigabytes of hacked files from Cosan, a Brazilian conglomerate producer of bioethanol, sugar and energy. The company operates in Brazil, Argentina, Bolivia, Paraguay, Uruguay.</description></item><item><title>Cyberanakin</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cyberanakin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/cyberanakin/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
Files from a revenge hacking spree against Russian entities allegedly in response to the MH17 downing.
RELEASE
CyberAnakin Files from a revenge hacking spree against Russian entities allegedly in response to the MH17 downing. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE CyberAnakin FILE SIZE 2.1 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES VICE EDITOR NOTES Limited Distribution Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=CyberAnakin&amp;amp;oldid=1139&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Hack Limited Distribution Russia</description></item><item><title>Dept. For Church Charity And Social Service Of The Russian Orthodox Church</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dept._for_church_charity_and_social_service_of_the_russian_orthodox_church/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dept._for_church_charity_and_social_service_of_the_russian_orthodox_church/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Dept. for Church Charity and Social Service of the Russian Orthodox Church Roughly 57,500 emails from the Russian Orthodox Church&amp;rsquo;s charitable wing. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 15 GB MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Roughly 57,500 emails from the Russian Orthodox Church&amp;rsquo;s charitable wing.
Due to the nature of the data, at this time it is only being offered to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Doxxing Adventskalender</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/doxxing-adventskalender/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/doxxing-adventskalender/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Doxxing-Adventskalender The mass &amp;ldquo;doxxing&amp;rdquo; of German celebrities and politicians. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Germany TYPE Hack SOURCE 0rbit FILE SIZE 6.7 GB DOWNLOADS MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES ZDNet EDITOR NOTES Limited Distribution The mass &amp;ldquo;doxxing&amp;rdquo; of German celebrities and politicians. Also known as 0rbit leaks.
Retrieved from &amp;ldquo;https://ddosecrets.com/index.php?title=Doxxing-Adventskalender&amp;amp;oldid=1182&amp;rdquo;
Categories:
Germany Hack Limited Distribution</description></item><item><title>Durham</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/durham/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/durham/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Durham 14 gigabytes (uncompressed) hacked from the Durham region of Canada. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Canada TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 6.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
14 gigabytes (uncompressed) hacked from the Durham region of Canada.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)</description></item><item><title>Dussmann Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dussmann_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/dussmann_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Dussmann Group 222 gigabytes hacked from German multi-service provider with subsidiaries focusing on facility management, corporate childcare, nursing and care for the elderly, and business systems solutions, including HVAC, electrical work, and elevators. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES 222 gigabytes hacked from German multi-service provider with subsidiaries focusing on facility management, corporate childcare, nursing and care for the elderly, and business systems solutions, including HVAC, electrical work, and elevators.</description></item><item><title>Embassy Of Ecuador, Moscow</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/embassy_of_ecuador_moscow/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/embassy_of_ecuador_moscow/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Embassy of Ecuador, Moscow Over 30,000 emails ranging from 2018 to March, 2022 and 40,000 files from the Embassy of Ecuador, Moscow. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 53.3 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES The Daily Dot EDITOR NOTES
Over 30,000 emails ranging from 2018 to March, 2022 and 40,000 files from the Embassy of Ecuador, Moscow.</description></item><item><title>Ernst &amp; Young</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ernst__young/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ernst__young/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ernst &amp;amp; Young Internal files from the accounting firm Ernst &amp;amp; Young (EY). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 2 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Two terabytes of internal files from the accounting firm Ernst &amp;amp; Young (EY). Ernst &amp;amp; Young primarily provides accounting, tax, consulting and advisory services.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Ethiopia Financial Intelligence Service</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ethiopia_financial_intelligence_service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ethiopia_financial_intelligence_service/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ethiopia Financial Intelligence Service Approximately 19,000 emails from Ethiopia&amp;rsquo;s Financial Intelligence Service DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Ethiopia TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 45 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 19,000 emails from Ethiopia&amp;rsquo;s Financial Intelligence Service, previously known as the Financial Intelligence Center, the government agency responsible for monitoring suspicious financial transactions in the country.
Embargo During an initial embargo, the data was shared with the Platform to Protect Whistleblowers in Africa (PPLAAF), which shared its findings with various media partners: Bloomberg in the United States; Süddeutsche Zeitung in Germany; Tamedia in Switzerland; and The Continent in South Africa.</description></item><item><title>Fiscalia Of Colombia</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fiscalia_of_colombia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fiscalia_of_colombia/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fiscalía of Colombia 5 terabytes of emails hacked from the Office of the Attorney General of Colombia (Fiscalía General de la Nación) by Guacamaya, which has been linked to numerous kinds of corruption. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Colombia TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 5 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista 5 terabytes of emails hacked from the Office of the Attorney General of Colombia (Fiscalía General de la Nación) by Guacamaya, which has been linked to numerous kinds of corruption, including withholding evidence, ties to drug trafficking and paramilitary networks, espionage, acts of political persecution and murder.</description></item><item><title>Fisher &amp; Paykel</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fisher__paykel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fisher__paykel/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fisher &amp;amp; Paykel Over 30 gigabytes hacked from Fisher &amp;amp; Paykel, a major appliance manufacturer which is a subsidiary of home appliance manufacturer Haier, based in East Tamaki, New Zealand. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES New Zealand, Italy, United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 31 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 30 gigabytes hacked from Fisher &amp;amp; Paykel, a major appliance manufacturer which is a subsidiary of home appliance manufacturer Haier, based in East Tamaki, New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Fishrot Files</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fishrot_files/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/fishrot_files/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fishrot Files Approximately 75,000 files and emails from Samherji, exposing corruption in the fishing industry in a scandal extending from Iceland to Namibia, Norway and beyond. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Iceland, Namibia, Norway TYPE Leak SOURCE Jóhannes Stefánsson FILE SIZE 25.8 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES Wikipedia EDITOR NOTES This copy of the Fishrot Files was provided directly by the source and is restricted at his request due to PII concerns.</description></item><item><title>FundaçÃO Nacional De Artes</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/funda%C3%A7%C3%A3o_nacional_de_artes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/funda%C3%A7%C3%A3o_nacional_de_artes/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Fundação Nacional de Artes Over 1 million emails from Fundação Nacional de Artes (Funarte), the Brazilian government&amp;rsquo;s National Arts Foundation. Funarte develops policies to promote the arts, including music, dance, theater and the circus. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 302 GB How to Request Access MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 1 million emails from Fundação Nacional de Artes (Funarte), the Brazilian government&amp;rsquo;s National Arts Foundation.</description></item><item><title>Gableaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gableaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gableaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GabLeaks 70 GB of Gab public posts, private posts, user profiles, hashed passwords for users, DMs, and plaintext passwords for groups. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES International TYPE Hack SOURCE JaXpArO (they/them) &amp;amp; My Little Anonymous Revival Project FILE SIZE 70 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES Wired EDITOR NOTES Gab response to query from Wired The Gab data is an important but complicated dataset.</description></item><item><title>Givesendgo</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GiveSendGo Donor information for every GiveSendGo campaign as of February 2021. Note that this is unrelated to the February 2022 leaks. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES N/A TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 15 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES Fox Business, The Guardian, Medium, VICE EDITOR NOTES See also GiveSendGo 2.0, GiveSendGo 3.0, GiveSendGo 4.0 and GiveSendGo 5.0 Donor information for every campaign on the &amp;lsquo;Christian fundraising platform&amp;rsquo; GiveSendGo, best known for being used by far-right extremists like the Proud Boys.</description></item><item><title>Givesendgo 2.0</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_2.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_2.0/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | GiveSendGo | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Over 1,000 files consisting of | | | identification cards uploaded | | | onto GiveSendGo&amp;rsquo;s publicly | | | accessible Amazon-hosted S3 | | | bucket. The IDs seem to belong to | | | crowdfund creators, rather than | | | donors. | | | | | | | | | Note that this is unrelated to | | | the February 2021 leak of donor | | | informatio | | | n.</description></item><item><title>Givesendgo 3.0</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_3.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_3.0/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GiveSendGo 3.0 Donor information for the Freedom Convoy campaign from the GiveSendGo platform as of February 13, 2022 DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES N/A TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 33.6 MB MORE REFERENCES Vice EDITOR NOTES See also GiveSendGo, GiveSendGo 2.0, GiveSendGo 4.0 and GiveSendGo 5.0 Donor information for the Freedom Convoy campaign from the GiveSendGo platform ending on February 13, 2022, including names (self-reported), email addresses and zip codes.</description></item><item><title>Givesendgo 4.0</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_4.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_4.0/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GiveSendGo 4.0 5 GB of files including donor info for the Adopt A Trucker campaign, a full MySQL dump, sourcecode for their Bitbucket repo, their customer service systems, verification documents, and Stripe data for the Freedom Convoy and the Adopt A Trucker campaigns. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES N/A TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 5 GB MORE REFERENCES Daily Dot EDITOR NOTES See also GiveSendGo, GiveSendGo 2.</description></item><item><title>Givesendgo 5.0</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_5.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_5.0/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GiveSendGo 5.0 Updated Stripe and donor information for the Freedom Convoy campaign from the GiveSendGo platform as of February 23, 2022 DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES N/A TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 863.3 MB MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES See also GiveSendGo, GiveSendGo 2.0, GiveSendGo 3.0 and GiveSendGo 4.0 Updated Stripe and donor information for the Freedom Convoy campaign from the GiveSendGo platform as of February 23, 2022.</description></item><item><title>Givesendgo Freedom Convoy Donor Info</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_freedom_convoy_donor_info/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/givesendgo_freedom_convoy_donor_info/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from GiveSendGo Freedom Convoy donor info)]
RELEASE
GiveSendGo 3.0 Donor information for the Freedom Convoy campaign from the GiveSendGo platform as of February 13, 2022 DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES N/A TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 33.6 MB MORE REFERENCES Vice EDITOR NOTES See also GiveSendGo, GiveSendGo 2.0, GiveSendGo 4.0 and GiveSendGo 5.0 Donor information for the Freedom Convoy campaign from the GiveSendGo platform ending on February 13, 2022, including names (self-reported), email addresses and zip codes.</description></item><item><title>Gqleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gqleaks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/gqleaks/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
GQLeaks 120 GB of emails hacked from the Centro Nacional de la Informatización de la Administración Pública de Guinea Ecuatorial (CNIAPGE) or Equatorial Guinea&amp;rsquo;s National Center for the Computerization of Public Administration. The emails are dated between 2017 and early 2022. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Equatorial Guinea TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 120 GB DOWNLOADS (How to request access) MORE REFERENCES Diario Rombe EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Henning Harders</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/henning_harders/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/henning_harders/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Henning Harders 303 gigabytes hacked from Henning Harders, an Australian freight forwarding agent, trade consultancy and licensed customs broker. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Australia TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 303 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
303 gigabytes hacked from Henning Harders, an Australian freight forwarding agent, trade consultancy and licensed customs broker.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Hunter Biden Iphone And Ipad Backups</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hunter_biden_iphone_and_ipad_backups/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hunter_biden_iphone_and_ipad_backups/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Hunter Biden iPhone and iPad | | | Backups | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Backups of an iPhone and iPad | | | allegedly used by Hunter Biden, | | | released onto 4chan by | | | &amp;ldquo;Kiwianon.&amp;rdquo; | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | DATASET DETAILS | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | COUNTRIES | United States | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | TYPE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | SOURCE | 4chan / Kiwianon | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | FILE SIZE | 28.</description></item><item><title>Hunter Biden Laptop</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hunter_biden_laptop/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/hunter_biden_laptop/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Hunter Biden Laptop An alleged copy of the Hunter Biden laptop, released onto 4chan by someone apparently sometimes referred to as &amp;ldquo;Kiwianon.&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE SOURCE 4chan / KiwiAnon FILE SIZE 400 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES See the Hunter Biden emailsdataset for concerns and issues relating to data sourced from the same laptop that the backups appear to have been taken from.</description></item><item><title>Illinois Attorney General</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/illinois_attorney_general/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/illinois_attorney_general/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Illinois Attorney General A cache of files hacked from the Illinois Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s office. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE DoppelPaymer FILE SIZE About 200 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES ThreatPost EDITOR NOTES
A cache of files hacked from the Illinois Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s office by the ransomware crew DoppelPaymer. The total cache is allegedly &amp;ldquo;about 200 GB&amp;rdquo; that will be &amp;ldquo;progressively uploaded.</description></item><item><title>Intolerance Network</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/intolerance_network/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/intolerance_network/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Intolerance Network)]
RELEASE
CitizenGo Over 17,000 documents hacked from right wing campaigning organizations Grupo CitizenGO &amp;amp; HazteOir hacked by ACABGang. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE ACABGang FILE SIZE 24 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES These files are the unredacted version of WikiLeaks&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Intolerance Network&amp;rdquo;. See also CitizenGo &amp;amp; HatzeOir databases Over 17,000 documents from right wing campaigning organizations Grupo CitizenGO &amp;amp; HazteOir hacked by ACABGang.</description></item><item><title>J.Irwin Company</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/j.irwin_company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/j.irwin_company/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
J. Irwin Company 300 megabytes from J. Irwin Company, which installs pipeline and constructs processing plants, compressor stations and other facilities for gas, oil and water transportation. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Xing FILE SIZE 309 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
300 megabytes from J. Irwin Company, which installs pipelines and constructs processing plants, compressor stations and other facilities for gas, oil and water transportation.</description></item><item><title>Jones Day</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jones_day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/jones_day/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Jones Day Data hacked from the high profile Jones Day law firm, including data associated with the city of Chicago and Chicago PD, as well as data associated with the credit reporting agency Experian. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 85 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES VICE EDITOR NOTES
Data hacked from the high profile Jones Day lawfirm, including data associated with the city of Chicago and Chicago PD, as well as data associated with the credit reporting agency Experian.</description></item><item><title>Kcsa Strategic Communications</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/kcsa_strategic_communications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/kcsa_strategic_communications/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
KCSA Strategic Communications A public relations firm based in Boston, MA. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 152.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A public relations firm based in Boston, MA breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Latam Air</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/latam_air/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/latam_air/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from LATAM Air)]
RELEASE
LATAM Airlines 53 gigabytes of cargo manifests from LATAM Airlines, focusing on Colombia and Peru. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Colombia, Peru TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 53 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES 53 gigabytes of cargo manifests hacked from LATAM Airlines, focusing on Colombia and Peru.
Due to the presence of PII including copies of passports, the data is being offered only on a Limited Distribution basis.</description></item><item><title>Latam Airlines</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/latam_airlines/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/latam_airlines/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
LATAM Airlines 53 gigabytes of cargo manifests from LATAM Airlines, focusing on Colombia and Peru. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Colombia, Peru TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 53 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES 53 gigabytes of cargo manifests hacked from LATAM Airlines, focusing on Colombia and Peru.
Due to the presence of PII including copies of passports, the data is being offered only on a Limited Distribution basis.</description></item><item><title>Letmespy</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/letmespy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/letmespy/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
LetMeSpy Tens of thousands of database entries containing customer information, messages, call, GPS and other logs from devices compromised by the LetMeSpy stalkerware. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 68 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES LetMeSpy statement EDITOR NOTES
Tens of thousands of database entries containing customer information, messages, call, GPS and other logs from devices compromised by the LetMeSpy stalkerware.</description></item><item><title>Mas Holdings</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mas_holdings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/mas_holdings/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MAS Holdings 29 gigabytes of hacked files from MAS Holdings, South Asia&amp;rsquo;s largest manufacturer of lingerie and one of Sri Lanka&amp;rsquo;s largest apparel manufacturers. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Sri Lanka TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 29 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
29 gigabytes of hacked files from MAS Holdings, South Asia&amp;rsquo;s largest manufacturer of lingerie and one of Sri Lanka&amp;rsquo;s largest apparel manufacturers.</description></item><item><title>Medical Diagnostics Laboratories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/medical_diagnostics_laboratories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/medical_diagnostics_laboratories/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Medical Diagnostics Laboratories 83 gigabytes of data hacked from Medical Diagnostics Laboratories, which performs outsourced medical testing in addition to Research and Development (R&amp;amp;D). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 83 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
83 gigabytes of data hacked from Medical Diagnostics Laboratories, which performs outsourced medical testing in addition to Research and Development (R&amp;amp;D).</description></item><item><title>Meritservus And Meritkapital</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/meritservus_and_meritkapital/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/meritservus_and_meritkapital/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
MeritServus and MeritKapital Over 400,000 files and 72,000 emails from MeritServus and MeritKapital, which provide corporate registration and administration, asset management and holding company services along with golden passport services. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Cyprus TYPE Hack SOURCE F R E A K Y FILE SIZE 500 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 400,000 files and 72,000 emails from MeritServus and MeritKapital, which provide corporate registration, administration, asset management and holding company services along with golden passport services.</description></item><item><title>Metropolitan Police Department D.C.</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/metropolitan_police_department_d.c./</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/metropolitan_police_department_d.c./</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Ministerio De Ambiente Y Recursos Naturales</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministerio_de_ambiente_y_recursos_naturales/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministerio_de_ambiente_y_recursos_naturales/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ministerio de Ambiente y Recursos Naturales (MARN) Hacked emails from Ministerio de Ambiente y Recursos Naturales (MARN), which controls natural resources in Guatemala. MARN&amp;rsquo;s corruption has resulted in the destruction of natural resources. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Guatemala TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Hacked emails from Ministerio de Ambiente y Recursos Naturales (MARN), which controls natural resources in Guatemala.</description></item><item><title>Ministerio De Justicia Of Chile</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministerio_de_justicia_of_chile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/ministerio_de_justicia_of_chile/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Ministerio de Justicia of Chile Over 384,000 emails from the Ministerio de Justicia (Ministry of Justice) of Chile. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Chile TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 67 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES Ciper EDITOR NOTES
Over 384,000 emails from the Ministerio de Justicia (Ministry of Justice) of Chile.
Limited Distribution Due to the sensitivity of the data, the data is only being provided to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Municipal Court Of Princeton</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/municipal_court_of_princeton/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/municipal_court_of_princeton/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Municipal Court of Princeton Nearly 30 GB of appeal letters, accounting and audit information, amendment documents, tax information and chats. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Marketo FILE SIZE 28 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 30 GB of appeal letters, accounting and audit information, amendment documents, tax information and chats.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Myanmar Internal Revenue Department</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myanmar_internal_revenue_department/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myanmar_internal_revenue_department/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Myanmar Internal Revenue Department Tax filings from Myanmar&amp;rsquo;s Internal Revenue Department (IRD). The data includes all tax filings and supporting documents from 2021. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Myanmar TYPE Hack SOURCE Sugondese Electronic Army FILE SIZE 446 GB How to Request Access MORE REFERENCES ICIJ investigation EDITOR NOTES ReadMe.txt from the source Tax filings from the Myanmar&amp;rsquo;s Internal Revenue Department (IRD), a state agency that has been illegally controlled by the Myanmar military since the coup on February 1, 2021.</description></item><item><title>Myatt Blume &amp; Osburn</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myatt_blume__osburn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myatt_blume__osburn/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Myatt Blume &amp;amp; Osburn A Texas accounting firm with corporate and government clients. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 27.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A Texas accounting firm with corporate and government clients breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Myattcpa</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myattcpa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/myattcpa/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Myattcpa)]
RELEASE
Myatt Blume &amp;amp; Osburn A Texas accounting firm with corporate and government clients. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 27.7 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A Texas accounting firm with corporate and government clients breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>National Police Of Paraguay</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/national_police_of_paraguay/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/national_police_of_paraguay/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
National Police of Paraguay Over 500,000 internal documents, images and SQL databases from the National Police of Paraguay (Policía Nacional del Paraguay). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Paraguay TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 400 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 500,000 internal documents and images from the National Police of Paraguay (Policía Nacional del Paraguay), and 175 gigabytes of SQL databases.
The data includes documents from the Internal Affairs Directorate (Dirección de Asuntos Internos), the Identification Department (Departamento de Identificaciones) and the Foreigners Registry Department (Departamento Registro de Extranjeros), Technology and Development Division (Division de Tecnologia y Desarrollo), as well as other documents including orders from command, photographs of evidence and documents about wanted individuals.</description></item><item><title>Newbridge Securities</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/newbridge_securities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/newbridge_securities/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Newbridge Securities Corporation Approximately 90 gigabytes from Newbridge Securities, a securities brokerage, investment banking and wealth management services firm. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Marketo FILE SIZE 93 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 90 gigabytes from Newbridge Securities, a securities brokerage, investment banking and wealth management services firm.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>No Fly List</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/no_fly_list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/no_fly_list/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
No Fly List A copy of the United States&amp;rsquo; No Fly List from 2019, which CommuteAir left on an misconfigured (unsecured) development server. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE maia crimew FILE SIZE 90 MB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES maia.crimew, Daily Dot EDITOR NOTES
A copy of the United States&amp;rsquo; No Fly List from 2019, which CommuteAir left on an misconfigured (unsecured) development server.</description></item><item><title>North American Roofing</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/north_american_roofing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/north_american_roofing/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
North American Roofing 83 gigabytes hacked from the &amp;ldquo;most trusted and respected commercial roofing company in the U.S.&amp;rdquo; DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 83 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
83 gigabytes hacked from the &amp;ldquo;most trusted and respected commercial roofing company in the U.S.&amp;rdquo; The company not only boasts about the quality of its work and its community involvement, but about its sustainability program and green initiative.</description></item><item><title>Oakland City Hall</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oakland_city_hall/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/oakland_city_hall/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Oakland City Hall Internal documents from Oakland City Hall. The data includes policy documents, misconduct records and bank statements. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE PLAY FILE SIZE 11.7 GB and 600 GB How to Request Access MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Internal emails and files from Oakland City Hall, a mid-sized city in the San Francisco Bay area with a long history of human rights violations.</description></item><item><title>Odin Intelligence</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odin_intelligence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/odin_intelligence/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
ODIN Intelligence 19 GB including thousands of photos, audio recordings, reports and user information from ODIN Intelligence and SweepWizard, a pair of apps geared towards law enforcement that primarily target houseless people. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE All Cyber-cops Are Bastards FILE SIZE 19 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES VICE, Wired, TechCrunch EDITOR NOTES
19 GB including thousands of photos, audio recordings, reports and user information from ODIN Intelligence and SweepWizard, a pair of apps geared towards law enforcement that primarily target houseless people.</description></item><item><title>Optimeyes</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/optimeyes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/optimeyes/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
OptimEyes S3 buckets, git and database backups, and credentials from the risk assessment company OptimEyes. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE 4chan FILE SIZE 67.8 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
S3 buckets, git and database backups, and credentials from the risk assessment company OptimEyes.
Research Leaked data from tobacco giant Phillip Morris posted to 4chan (The Daily Dot)
Limited Distribution Due to the presence of critical AWS keys and other credentials, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Parkland</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/parkland/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/parkland/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Parkland Nearly 750 gigabytes (uncompressed) hacked from one of Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest gas station and convenience store chains. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Canada TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 499 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 750 gigabytes (uncompressed) hacked from one of Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest gas station and convenience store chains.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Petrolimex</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/petrolimex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/petrolimex/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Petrolimex 52 gigabytes from the Vietnam National Petroleum Group, which makes up 50% of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s petroleum market and is active in the fields of engineering, installation, mechanical and oil equipment DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Vietnam TYPE Hack SOURCE BlackByte FILE SIZE 52 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
52 gigabytes from the Vietnam National Petroleum Group, which makes up 50% of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s petroleum market and is active in the fields of engineering, installation, mechanical and oil equipment.</description></item><item><title>PolicíA Nacional Civil De El Salvador</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/polic%C3%ADa_nacional_civil_de_el_salvador/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/polic%C3%ADa_nacional_civil_de_el_salvador/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Policía Nacional Civil de El Salvador Over 10 million emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Policía Nacional Civil de El Salvador (National Civil Police of El Salvador). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES El Salvador TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 6.8 TB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista Over 10 million emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Policía Nacional Civil de El Salvador (National Civil Police of El Salvador).</description></item><item><title>Prepara Brasil</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/prepara_brasil/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/prepara_brasil/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Prepara Brasil A copy of the &amp;ldquo;Prepara Brasil&amp;rdquo; course from Eduardo Bolsonaro, the son of Jair Bolsonaro. The stated goal of the course is to prepare Brazilians to fight leftism, with topics including feminism, abortion, gender ideology, racism, Christianity and cultural weapons. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Brazil TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 38.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A copy of the &amp;ldquo;Prepara Brasil&amp;rdquo; course from Eduardo Bolsonaro, the son of Jair Bolsonaro.</description></item><item><title>Presque Isle Police Department</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/presque_isle_police_department/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/presque_isle_police_department/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Presque Isle Police Department Nearly 200 gigabytes of data hacked from Presque Isle Police Department. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Avaddon FILE SIZE 195 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Nearly 200 gigabytes of data hacked from Presque Isle Police Department, including over 15,000 emails. About 10% of the cache is the department&amp;rsquo;s music collection.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Pricewaterhousecoopers</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pricewaterhousecoopers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pricewaterhousecoopers/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from PricewaterhouseCoopers)]
RELEASE
PWC Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Pwc</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pwc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/pwc/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
PWC Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE CL0P FILE SIZE 222 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Roskomnadzor 2.0 (Grfc)</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/roskomnadzor_2.0_grfc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/roskomnadzor_2.0_grfc/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Roskomnadzor 2.0 (GRFC))]
RELEASE
[RussianCensorFiles] Documents and correspondence from the internal network of the General Radio Frequency Center (GRFC) subdivision of Roskomnadzor. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Belarusian Cyberpartisans FILE SIZE 335 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES See also Roskomnadzor Documents and correspondence from the internal network of the General Radio Frequency Center (GRFC) subdivision of Roskomnadzor.</description></item><item><title>Russian Soldier Leak</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/russian_soldier_leak/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/russian_soldier_leak/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Russian soldier leak Personal data of 120,000 Russian soldiers allegedly fighting in Ukraine, leaked by Pravda. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia, Ukraine TYPE Leak SOURCE Pravda FILE SIZE 22.1 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT DIRECT DOWNLOAD MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Personal data of 120,000 Russian soldiers allegedly fighting in Ukraine, leaked by Pravda. The data includes names, DOBs, addresses, unit affiliation and passport numbers.</description></item><item><title>Russiancensorfiles</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/russiancensorfiles/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/russiancensorfiles/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
[RussianCensorFiles] Documents and correspondence from the internal network of the General Radio Frequency Center (GRFC) subdivision of Roskomnadzor. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Belarusian Cyberpartisans FILE SIZE 335 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES See also Roskomnadzor Documents and correspondence from the internal network of the General Radio Frequency Center (GRFC) subdivision of Roskomnadzor. GRFC monitors social media and other open sources in order to implement the Kremlin censorship and provide data for decision makers.</description></item><item><title>SecretaríA De La Defensa Nacional De MéXico</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/secretar%C3%ADa_de_la_defensa_nacional_de_m%C3%A9xico/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/secretar%C3%ADa_de_la_defensa_nacional_de_m%C3%A9xico/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Secretaría de la Defensa Nacional de México 6 TB of emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Secretaría de la Defensa Nacional de México (SEDENA), the Secretariat of National Defense of Mexico. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Mexico TYPE Hack SOURCE Guacamaya FILE SIZE 6 TB DOWNLOADS: Request Access MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES Published simultaneously with Enlace Hacktivista 6 TB of emails hacked by Guacamaya from the Secretaría de la Defensa Nacional de México (SEDENA) (Secretariat of National Defense of Mexico).</description></item><item><title>Special:Categories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialcategories/</guid><description>Help
The following categories exist on the wiki, and may or may not be unused. Also see wanted categories.
[Categories]
[Display categories starting at:]
[Show]
(first | last) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Allegations of State Sponsorship‏‎ (22 members) Angola‏‎ (1 member) Anonymous‏‎ (86 members) Argentina‏‎ (4 members) Australia‏‎ (4 members) Azerbaijan‏‎ (2 members) Bahamas‏‎ (0 members) Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box‏‎ (25 members) Belarus‏‎ (2 members) Belgium‏‎ (1 member) Bolivia‏‎ (1 member) Brazil‏‎ (11 members) Bulgaria‏‎ (1 member) Cambodia‏‎ (1 member) Canada‏‎ (4 members) Cayman Islands‏‎ (1 member) Chile‏‎ (6 members) China‏‎ (2 members) Colombia‏‎ (6 members) Cook Islands‏‎ (1 member) Corporate‏‎ (136 members) Cyberwar‏‎ (54 members) Cyprus‏‎ (1 member) Dominican Republic‏‎ (1 member) Ecuador‏‎ (3 members) El Salvador‏‎ (3 members) Environmental‏‎ (41 members) Estonia‏‎ (1 member) Ethiopia‏‎ (1 member) European Union‏‎ (2 members) Extractivist Leaks‏‎ (7 members) Fascist‏‎ (23 members) France‏‎ (3 members) Fuerzas Represivas‏‎ (7 members) Germany‏‎ (5 members) Guatemala‏‎ (2 members) Guinea Ecuatorial‏‎ (1 member) Hack‏‎ (216 members) Iceland‏‎ (1 member) India‏‎ (1 member) Indonesia‏‎ (4 members) Iran‏‎ (4 members) Iraq‏‎ (1 member) Italy‏‎ (6 members) Jordan‏‎ (1 member) Leak‏‎ (24 members) Leak Markets‏‎ (3 members) Limited Distribution‏‎ (84 members) Mexico‏‎ (1 member) MilicoLeaks‏‎ (2 members) (first | last) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Special:Mostlinkedcategories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialmostlinkedcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialmostlinkedcategories/</guid><description>Showing below up to 50 results in range #1 to #50.
View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Hack‏‎ (216 members) Corporate‏‎ (136 members) Anonymous‏‎ (86 members) Limited Distribution‏‎ (84 members) United States of America‏‎ (72 members) Russia‏‎ (65 members) Cyberwar‏‎ (54 members) Ransomware‏‎ (53 members) Environmental‏‎ (41 members) Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box‏‎ (25 members) Leak‏‎ (24 members) Organization‏‎ (24 members) Fascist‏‎ (23 members) Allegations of State Sponsorship‏‎ (22 members) Brazil‏‎ (11 members) Researchers‏‎ (10 members) Ukraine‏‎ (8 members) Extractivist Leaks‏‎ (7 members) Fuerzas Represivas‏‎ (7 members) Italy‏‎ (6 members) Chile‏‎ (6 members) Scrape‏‎ (6 members) Colombia‏‎ (6 members) Germany‏‎ (5 members) Australia‏‎ (4 members) Iran‏‎ (4 members) Argentina‏‎ (4 members) United Kingdom‏‎ (4 members) Myanmar‏‎ (4 members) Indonesia‏‎ (4 members) Canada‏‎ (4 members) Thailand‏‎ (3 members) Syria‏‎ (3 members) Turkey‏‎ (3 members) France‏‎ (3 members) Paraguay‏‎ (3 members) Peru‏‎ (3 members) Leak Markets‏‎ (3 members) El Salvador‏‎ (3 members) Ecuador‏‎ (3 members) China‏‎ (2 members) European Union‏‎ (2 members) Azerbaijan‏‎ (2 members) Panama‏‎ (2 members) Venezuela‏‎ (2 members) Belarus‏‎ (2 members) Guatemala‏‎ (2 members) MilicoLeaks‏‎ (2 members) Angola‏‎ (1 member) Bulgaria‏‎ (1 member) View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Special:Uncategorizedcategories</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialuncategorizedcategories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/specialuncategorizedcategories/</guid><description>Help
Showing below up to 50 results in range #1 to #50.
View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)
Allegations of State Sponsorship Angola Anonymous Argentina Australia Azerbaijan Bahamas Banker&amp;rsquo;s Box Belarus Belgium Bolivia Brazil Bulgaria Cambodia Canada Cayman Islands Chile China Colombia Cook Islands Corporate Cyberwar Cyprus Dominican Republic Ecuador El Salvador Environmental Estonia Ethiopia European Union Extractivist Leaks Fascist France Fuerzas Represivas Germany Guatemala Guinea Ecuatorial Hack Iceland India Indonesia Iran Iraq Italy Jordan Leak Leak Markets Limited Distribution Mexico MilicoLeaks View (previous 50 | next 50) (20 | 50 | 100 | 250 | 500)</description></item><item><title>Spyhide</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/spyhide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/spyhide/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
SpyHide Source code and user data for the Android spyware software SpyHide. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Germany, Iran TYPE Hack SOURCE maia arson crimew FILE SIZE 100 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES maia arson crimew EDITOR NOTES
Source code and user data for the Android spyware software SpyHide dating from 2016 through mid-July 2023.
Although SpyHide&amp;rsquo;s software was made in Iran and the servers were hosted in Germany, TechCrunch&amp;rsquo;s analysis identified at least 750,000 users and about 60,000 compromised devices in a surveillance network that spans every continent.</description></item><item><title>Technoserv</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/technoserv/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/technoserv/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Technoserv Approximately 1.2 TB of files from Technoserv, a group of IT companies specializing in system integration, networking and cloud services, information security, and datamining. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES Russia TYPE Hack SOURCE Национальная республиканская армия / National Republican Army (of Russia) FILE SIZE 1.2 TB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES KyivPost EDITOR NOTES
Approximately 1.2 TB of files from Technoserv (now T1 Integration), a group of IT companies specializing in system integration, networking and cloud services, information security, and datamining.</description></item><item><title>Tetraedr</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tetraedr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/tetraedr/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+:&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;:+ | RELEASE | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | Tetraedr | | +&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;+ | | | .thumbinner style=&amp;ldquo;width:302px;&amp;rdquo;} | | | [![Anonymous Liberland and the | | | Pwn-Bär Hack Team Pom-Bear Mascot | | | About us Greetings citizens of | | | the world. Let us introduce | | | ourselves&amp;hellip; We are the Pwn-Bär | | | international hack team. We stand | | | for equal opportunity pwnage and | | | unrestricted access to | | | information.</description></item><item><title>Thailand Judicial Management Database</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thailand_judicial_management_database/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thailand_judicial_management_database/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Thailand Judicial Management Database A database of Thai judicial employees. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY Thailand TYPE Hack SOURCE Blink Hacker Group FILE SIZE 106 MB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES DataBreaches.net EDITOR NOTES Limited Distribution A database of Thai judicial employees.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)</description></item><item><title>Thsa</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thsa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/thsa/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
THSA TH Company (THSA), an industrial solutions company. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY TYPE Hack SOURCE Team Snatch FILE SIZE 37.2 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
TH Company (THSA), an industrial solutions company breached by Team Snatch / Boris the Blade.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers. (How to Request Access)</description></item><item><title>Toll Group</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/toll_group/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/toll_group/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Toll Group 84 gigabytes hacked from an Australian transportation and logistics company with operations in road, rail, sea, air and warehousing. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 150 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
150 gigabytes hacked from an Australian transportation and logistics company with operations in road, rail, sea, air and warehousing. A subsidiary of Japan Post Holdings, the company has three divisions; Global Express, Global Forwarding, and Global Logistics.</description></item><item><title>Trust Capital Funding</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/trust_capital_funding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/trust_capital_funding/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Trust Capital Funding Over 230 gigabytes from the financing company Trust Capital Funding, which provides funding for commercial real estate, franchise startups and businesses as well as merchant processing and other banking products. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE BlackMatter FILE SIZE 233 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
Over 230 gigabytes from the financing company Trust Capital Funding, which provides funding for commercial real estate, franchise startups and businesses as well as merchant processing and other banking products.</description></item><item><title>Truth Will Out Films Customer Database</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/truth_will_out_films_customer_database/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/truth_will_out_films_customer_database/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Truth Will Out Films Customer Database A 2019 database containing full customer information for the neo-Nazi film shop, Truth Will Out Films. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE Anonymous FILE SIZE 89 MB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET TORRENT MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
A 2019 database containing full customer information for the neo-Nazi film shop, Truth Will Out Films.
Due to the PII in the dataset, it is only being offered to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>W.L. Contractors</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/w.l._contractors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/w.l._contractors/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
W.L. Contractors 15 gigabytes hacked from a Colorado based traffic signal, Intelligent Transportation Systems, and CCTV contractor. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE MAZE FILE SIZE 15 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
15 gigabytes hacked from a based traffic signal, ITS (Intelligent Transportation Systems), and CCTV contractor operating throughout Colorado and Wyoming.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>W&amp;T Offshore</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/wt_offshore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/wt_offshore/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
W&amp;amp;T Offshore 19 gigabytes hacked from W&amp;amp;T Offshore, an independent oil and natural gas producer, exploring, developing, and acquiring oil and natural gas in the Gulf of Mexico. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Nefilim FILE SIZE 19 GB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
19 gigabytes hacked from W&amp;amp;T Offshore, an independent oil and natural gas producer, exploring, developing, and acquiring oil and natural gas in the Gulf of Mexico.</description></item><item><title>Washington County Sheriff</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_county_sheriff/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_county_sheriff/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
Washington County Sheriff 1,311 files hacked from the Washington County Sheriff by ransomware operator Conti. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Conti FILE SIZE 419 MB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
1,311 files hacked from the Washington County Sheriff by ransomware operator Conti.
Limited Distribution Due to the PII in this dataset, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item><item><title>Washington D.C. Metropolitan Pd</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Washington D.C. Metropolitan PD)]
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Washington D.C. Metropolitan Pd</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/washington_d.c._metropolitan_pd/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
[(Redirected from Washington D.C. Metropolitan PD)]
RELEASE
[Metropolitan Police Department D.C.] 250 gigabytes hacked from the Metropolitan D.C. police by the ransomware group known as Babuk. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES United States TYPE Hack SOURCE Babuk FILE SIZE 250 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Download) MAGNET Parts 0 and 1 (Samples),Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) TORRENT Parts 0 and 1 (Samples), Part 2.rar (HR On-Premise) DIRECT DOWNLOAD Link MORE REFERENCES The Hill, Partial ransomware negotiation transcript EDITOR NOTES</description></item><item><title>Webdetetive</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/webdetetive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/webdetetive/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
WebDetetive 150,000 files from the spyware reseller WebDetetive DATASET DETAILS COUNTRIES TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 1.5 GB DOWNLOADS (How to Request Access) REFERENCES
EDITOR NOTES
150,000 files from the spyware reseller WebDetetive, a phone monitoring app typically installed on phones without the user&amp;rsquo;s consent (or even knowledge). The software uploads the contents of the user&amp;rsquo;s phone to its servers, messages, call logs, phone call recordings, photos, ambient recordings from the phone&amp;rsquo;s microphone and GPS data.</description></item><item><title>Wtspy</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/wtspy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/hugo-markdown/wtspy/</guid><description>From Distributed Denial of Secrets
RELEASE
WtSpy A service built for whatsapp.com that provides an application designed for mobile devices that allows you to &amp;lsquo;spy&amp;rsquo; on other users. DATASET DETAILS COUNTRY TYPE Hack SOURCE FILE SIZE 112 MB (How to Request Access) MORE REFERENCES CyberWarNews EDITOR NOTES
A service built for whatsapp.com that provides an application designed for mobile devices that allows you to &amp;lsquo;spy&amp;rsquo; on other users account activity. Includes a copy of the software and client list.</description></item><item><title>29 Leaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/29-leaks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/29-leaks/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.
Background Formations House, now The London Office, facilitates international money laundering by taking advantage of the lax regulatory framework of the United Kingdom and many of its former colonies.
Journalist Oliver Bullough first wrote about Formations House in the Guardian in 2016, then in his book Moneyland: The Inside Story of the Crooks and Kleptocrats Who Rule the World.</description></item><item><title>Blueleaks</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/blueleaks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/blueleaks/</guid><description>Millions of emails, phone calls and faxes from London-based company formation agent The London Office (then called: Formations House) and its related companies, used to facilitate fraud in Africa, Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas.</description></item><item><title>National Police of Paraguay</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/national-police-of-paraguay/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/national-police-of-paraguay/</guid><description>Over 500,000 internal documents and images from the National Police of Paraguay (Policía Nacional del Paraguay), and 175 gigabytes of SQL databases.
The data includes documents from the Internal Affairs Directorate (Dirección de Asuntos Internos), the Identification Department (Departamento de Identificaciones) and the Foreigners Registry Department (Departamento Registro de Extranjeros), Technology and Development Division (Division de Tecnologia y Desarrollo), as well as other documents including orders from command, photographs of evidence and documents about wanted individuals.</description></item><item><title>Prime Minister of Iraq's Office</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pm-of-iraq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pm-of-iraq/</guid><description>2,500 emails from the Prime Minister of Iraq&amp;rsquo;s office sent between March 2021 and April 2022. The emails document the daily business of the office while Mustafa Al-Kadhimi (مصطفى عبد اللطيف مشتت) held it.</description></item><item><title>LetMeSpy</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/letmespy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/letmespy/</guid><description>Tens of thousands of database entries containing customer information, messages, call, GPS and other logs from devices compromised by the LetMeSpy stalkerware.
Research LetMeSpy, a phone tracking app spying on thousands, says it was hacked (TechCrunch)
Miscreants leak texts and info siphoned by Android stalkerware app LetMeSpy (The Register)
LetMeSpy data leak reveals users of digital stalking software (The Daily Dot)
#FuckStalkerware pt. 1 - the LetMeSpy hack (maia arson crimew)</description></item><item><title>PWC</title><link>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pwc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scidsg.github.io/ddosecrets-redesign/releases/pwc/</guid><description>Thousands of internal files from the accounting firm PricewaterhouseCoopers (PWC). The files include client review documents, HR files and employee file shares.
Limited Distribution Due to widespread presence of PII such as identification documents, the data is only being made available to journalists and researchers.</description></item></channel></rss>